[
  {
    "question": "Qual é o nome desta faca?",
    "picture": "https://res.cloudinary.com/dwm53cbu2/image/upload/a_320/a_hflip/w_1000,f_auto,q_auto:low,fl_lossy,fl_progressive,fl_strip_profile/v1760723596/SHADOW_DAGGERS-Black_Laminate_zm5cry.webp",
    "correct_answer": "SHADOW DAGGERS Black Laminate",
    "wrong_answers": [
      "SHADOW DAGGERS Rust Coat",
      "SHADOW DAGGERS Lore",
      "SHADOW DAGGERS Vanilla"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Qual é o nome desta faca?",
    "picture": "https://res.cloudinary.com/dwm53cbu2/image/upload/a_320/a_hflip/w_1000,f_auto,q_auto:low,fl_lossy,fl_progressive,fl_strip_profile/v1760723596/SHADOW_DAGGERS-Rust_Coat_b8yauk.webp",
    "correct_answer": "SHADOW DAGGERS Rust Coat",
    "wrong_answers": [
      "SHADOW DAGGERS Black Laminate",
      "SHADOW DAGGERS Lore",
      "SHADOW DAGGERS Vanilla"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Qual é o nome desta faca?",
    "picture": "https://res.cloudinary.com/dwm53cbu2/image/upload/a_320/a_hflip/w_1000,f_auto,q_auto:low,fl_lossy,fl_progressive,fl_strip_profile/v1760723593/SHADOW_DAGGERS-Lore_n2ptrw.webp",
    "correct_answer": "SHADOW DAGGERS Lore",
    "wrong_answers": [
      "SHADOW DAGGERS Black Laminate",
      "SHADOW DAGGERS Rust Coat",
      "SHADOW DAGGERS Vanilla"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Qual é o nome desta faca?",
    "picture": "https://res.cloudinary.com/dwm53cbu2/image/upload/a_320/a_hflip/w_1000,f_auto,q_auto:low,fl_lossy,fl_progressive,fl_strip_profile/v1760723591/SHADOW_DAGGERS-Vanilla_ufmoxo.webp",
    "correct_answer": "SHADOW DAGGERS Vanilla",
    "wrong_answers": [
      "SHADOW DAGGERS Black Laminate",
      "SHADOW DAGGERS Rust Coat",
      "SHADOW DAGGERS Lore"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Qual é o nome desta faca?",
    "picture": "https://res.cloudinary.com/dwm53cbu2/image/upload/a_320/a_hflip/w_1000,f_auto,q_auto:low,fl_lossy,fl_progressive,fl_strip_profile/v1760723589/SHADOW_DAGGERS-Autotronic_hcgcdb.webp",
    "correct_answer": "SHADOW DAGGERS Autotronic",
    "wrong_answers": [
      "SHADOW DAGGERS Black Laminate",
      "SHADOW DAGGERS Rust Coat",
      "SHADOW DAGGERS Lore"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Qual é o nome desta faca?",
    "picture": "https://res.cloudinary.com/dwm53cbu2/image/upload/a_320/a_hflip/w_1000,f_auto,q_auto:low,fl_lossy,fl_progressive,fl_strip_profile/v1760723587/KARAMBIT-Lore_gmikzp.webp",
    "correct_answer": "KARAMBIT Lore",
    "wrong_answers": [
      "BAYONET Lore",
      "KARAMBIT Black Laminate",
      "KARAMBIT Rust Coat"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Qual é o nome desta faca?",
    "picture": "https://res.cloudinary.com/dwm53cbu2/image/upload/a_320/a_hflip/w_1000,f_auto,q_auto:low,fl_lossy,fl_progressive,fl_strip_profile/v1760723586/KARAMBIT-Black_Laminate_qdwqw9.webp",
    "correct_answer": "KARAMBIT Black Laminate",
    "wrong_answers": [
      "BAYONET Black Laminate",
      "KARAMBIT Lore",
      "KARAMBIT Rust Coat"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Qual é o nome desta faca?",
    "picture": "https://res.cloudinary.com/dwm53cbu2/image/upload/a_320/a_hflip/w_1000,f_auto,q_auto:low,fl_lossy,fl_progressive,fl_strip_profile/v1760723583/URSUS_KNIFE-Rust_Coat_qukdps.webp",
    "correct_answer": "URSUS KNIFE Rust Coat",
    "wrong_answers": [
      "PARACORD KNIFE Rust Coat",
      "NAJAVA KNIFE Rust Coat",
      "TALON KNIFE Rust Coat"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Qual é o nome desta faca?",
    "picture": "https://res.cloudinary.com/dwm53cbu2/image/upload/a_320/a_hflip/w_1000,f_auto,q_auto:low,fl_lossy,fl_progressive,fl_strip_profile/v1760723581/SHADOW_DAGGERS-Case_Hardened_mv4ccr.webp",
    "correct_answer": "SHADOW DAGGERS Case Hardened",
    "wrong_answers": [
      "SHADOW DAGGERS Black Laminate",
      "SHADOW DAGGERS Rust Coat",
      "SHADOW DAGGERS Lore"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Qual é o nome desta faca?",
    "picture": "https://res.cloudinary.com/dwm53cbu2/image/upload/a_320/a_hflip/w_1000,f_auto,q_auto:low,fl_lossy,fl_progressive,fl_strip_profile/v1760723580/SHADOW_DAGGERS-Damascus_Steel_lm2xl0.webp",
    "correct_answer": "SHADOW DAGGERS Damascus Steel",
    "wrong_answers": [
      "SHADOW DAGGERS Black Laminate",
      "SHADOW DAGGERS Rust Coat",
      "SHADOW DAGGERS Lore"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Qual é o nome desta faca?",
    "picture": "https://res.cloudinary.com/dwm53cbu2/image/upload/a_320/a_hflip/w_1000,f_auto,q_auto:low,fl_lossy,fl_progressive,fl_strip_profile/v1760723578/GUT_KNIFE-Lore_xqxmri.webp",
    "correct_answer": "GUT KNIFE Lore",
    "wrong_answers": [
      "FLIP KNIFE Lore",
      "HUNTSMAN KNIFE Lore",
      "FALCHION KNIFE Lore"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Qual é o nome desta faca?",
    "picture": "https://res.cloudinary.com/dwm53cbu2/image/upload/a_320/a_hflip/w_1000,f_auto,q_auto:low,fl_lossy,fl_progressive,fl_strip_profile/v1760723575/PARACORD_KNIFE-Rust_Coat_s9bnls.webp",
    "correct_answer": "PARACORD KNIFE Rust Coat",
    "wrong_answers": [
      "URSUS KNIFE Rust Coat",
      "NAJAVA KNIFE Rust Coat",
      "TALON KNIFE Rust Coat"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Qual é o nome desta faca?",
    "picture": "https://res.cloudinary.com/dwm53cbu2/image/upload/a_320/a_hflip/w_1000,f_auto,q_auto:low,fl_lossy,fl_progressive,fl_strip_profile/v1760723574/NAJAVA_KNIFE-Rust_Coat_fs06h7.webp",
    "correct_answer": "NAJAVA KNIFE Rust Coat",
    "wrong_answers": [
      "URSUS KNIFE Rust Coat",
      "PARACORD KNIFE Rust Coat",
      "TALON KNIFE Rust Coat"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Qual é o nome desta faca?",
    "picture": "https://res.cloudinary.com/dwm53cbu2/image/upload/a_320/a_hflip/w_1000,f_auto,q_auto:low,fl_lossy,fl_progressive,fl_strip_profile/v1760723572/M9_BAYONET-Lore_qw3fn8.webp",
    "correct_answer": "M9 BAYONET Lore",
    "wrong_answers": [
      "M9 BAYONET Black Laminate",
      "M9 BAYONET Autotronic",
      "M9 BAYONET Rust Coat"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Qual é o nome desta faca?",
    "picture": "https://res.cloudinary.com/dwm53cbu2/image/upload/a_320/a_hflip/w_1000,f_auto,q_auto:low,fl_lossy,fl_progressive,fl_strip_profile/v1760723571/KARAMBIT-Rust_Coat_odx3gy.webp",
    "correct_answer": "KARAMBIT Rust Coat",
    "wrong_answers": [
      "SKELETON Rust Coat",
      "BAYONET Rust Coat",
      "KARAMBIT Lore"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Qual é o nome desta faca?",
    "picture": "https://res.cloudinary.com/dwm53cbu2/image/upload/a_320/a_hflip/w_1000,f_auto,q_auto:low,fl_lossy,fl_progressive,fl_strip_profile/v1760723569/SHADOW_DAGGERS-Freehand_fhprz1.webp",
    "correct_answer": "SHADOW DAGGERS Freehand",
    "wrong_answers": [
      "SHADOW DAGGERS Black Laminate",
      "SHADOW DAGGERS Rust Coat",
      "SHADOW DAGGERS Lore"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Qual é o nome desta faca?",
    "picture": "https://res.cloudinary.com/dwm53cbu2/image/upload/a_320/a_hflip/w_1000,f_auto,q_auto:low,fl_lossy,fl_progressive,fl_strip_profile/v1760723567/TALON_KNIFE-Rust_Coat_hsqbjf.webp",
    "correct_answer": "TALON KNIFE Rust Coat",
    "wrong_answers": [
      "URSUS KNIFE Rust Coat",
      "PARACORD KNIFE Rust Coat",
      "NAJAVA KNIFE Rust Coat"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Qual é o nome desta faca?",
    "picture": "https://res.cloudinary.com/dwm53cbu2/image/upload/a_320/a_hflip/w_1000,f_auto,q_auto:low,fl_lossy,fl_progressive,fl_strip_profile/v1760723565/KARAMBIT-Freehand_w9naq9.webp",
    "correct_answer": "KARAMBIT Freehand",
    "wrong_answers": [
      "BAYONET Freehand",
      "KARAMBIT Lore",
      "KARAMBIT Black Laminate"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Qual é o nome desta faca?",
    "picture": "https://res.cloudinary.com/dwm53cbu2/image/upload/a_320/a_hflip/w_1000,f_auto,q_auto:low,fl_lossy,fl_progressive,fl_strip_profile/v1760723563/KARAMBIT-Autotronic_lenivv.webp",
    "correct_answer": "KARAMBIT Autotronic",
    "wrong_answers": [
      "BAYONET Autotronic",
      "KARAMBIT Lore",
      "KARAMBIT Black Laminate"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Qual é o nome desta faca?",
    "picture": "https://res.cloudinary.com/dwm53cbu2/image/upload/a_320/a_hflip/w_1000,f_auto,q_auto:low,fl_lossy,fl_progressive,fl_strip_profile/v1760723561/GUT_KNIFE-Rust_Coat_jn3sxg.webp",
    "correct_answer": "GUT KNIFE Rust Coat",
    "wrong_answers": [
      "URSUS KNIFE Rust Coat",
      "PARACORD KNIFE Rust Coat",
      "NAJAVA KNIFE Rust Coat"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Qual é o nome desta faca?",
    "picture": "https://res.cloudinary.com/dwm53cbu2/image/upload/a_320/a_hflip/w_1000,f_auto,q_auto:low,fl_lossy,fl_progressive,fl_strip_profile/v1760723559/NOMAD_KNIFE-Rust_Coat_xb0lts.webp",
    "correct_answer": "NOMAD KNIFE Rust Coat",
    "wrong_answers": [
      "URSUS KNIFE Rust Coat",
      "PARACORD KNIFE Rust Coat",
      "NAJAVA KNIFE Rust Coat"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Qual é o nome desta faca?",
    "picture": "https://res.cloudinary.com/dwm53cbu2/image/upload/a_320/a_hflip/w_1000,f_auto,q_auto:low,fl_lossy,fl_progressive,fl_strip_profile/v1760723558/FLIP_KNIFE-Lore_bdmlzw.webp",
    "correct_answer": "FLIP KNIFE Lore",
    "wrong_answers": [
      "GUT KNIFE Lore",
      "HUNTSMAN KNIFE Lore",
      "FALCHION KNIFE Lore"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Qual é o nome desta faca?",
    "picture": "https://res.cloudinary.com/dwm53cbu2/image/upload/a_320/a_hflip/w_1000,f_auto,q_auto:low,fl_lossy,fl_progressive,fl_strip_profile/v1760723556/NAJAVA_KNIFE-Doppler_Phase_2_wefplq.webp",
    "correct_answer": "NAJAVA KNIFE Doppler Phase 2",
    "wrong_answers": [
      "URSUS KNIFE Doppler Phase 2",
      "TALON KNIFE Doppler Phase 2",
      "PARACORD KNIFE Doppler Phase 2"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Qual é o nome desta faca?",
    "picture": "https://res.cloudinary.com/dwm53cbu2/image/upload/a_320/a_hflip/w_1000,f_auto,q_auto:low,fl_lossy,fl_progressive,fl_strip_profile/v1760723554/KARAMBIT-Gamma_Doppler_Phase_1_kqnwrq.webp",
    "correct_answer": "KARAMBIT Gamma Doppler Phase 1",
    "wrong_answers": [
      "BAYONET Gamma Doppler Phase 1",
      "BAYONET Gamma Doppler Phase 1",
      "KARAMBIT Gamma Doppler Phase 3"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Qual é o nome desta faca?",
    "picture": "https://res.cloudinary.com/dwm53cbu2/image/upload/a_320/a_hflip/w_1000,f_auto,q_auto:low,fl_lossy,fl_progressive,fl_strip_profile/v1760723553/KARAMBIT-Gamma_Doppler_Phase_3_no2d57.webp",
    "correct_answer": "KARAMBIT Gamma Doppler Phase 3",
    "wrong_answers": [
      "BAYONET Gamma Doppler Phase 3",
      "KARAMBIT Gamma Doppler Phase 1",
      "KARAMBIT Gamma Doppler Phase 2"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Qual é o nome desta faca?",
    "picture": "https://res.cloudinary.com/dwm53cbu2/image/upload/a_320/a_hflip/w_1000,f_auto,q_auto:low,fl_lossy,fl_progressive,fl_strip_profile/v1760723551/URSUS_KNIFE-Vanilla_vjsuem.webp",
    "correct_answer": "URSUS KNIFE Vanilla",
    "wrong_answers": [
      "PARACORD KNIFE Vanilla",
      "NAJAVA KNIFE Vanilla",
      "NOMAD KNIFE Vanilla"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Qual é o nome desta faca?",
    "picture": "https://res.cloudinary.com/dwm53cbu2/image/upload/a_320/a_hflip/w_1000,f_auto,q_auto:low,fl_lossy,fl_progressive,fl_strip_profile/v1760723549/URSUS_KNIFE-Tiger_Tooth_paan8f.webp",
    "correct_answer": "URSUS KNIFE Tiger Tooth",
    "wrong_answers": [
      "NAJAVA KNIFE Tiger Tooth",
      "PARACORD KNIFE Tiger Tooth",
      "NOMAD KNIFE Tiger Tooth"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Qual é o nome desta faca?",
    "picture": "https://res.cloudinary.com/dwm53cbu2/image/upload/a_320/a_hflip/w_1000,f_auto,q_auto:low,fl_lossy,fl_progressive,fl_strip_profile/v1760723547/SHADOW_DAGGERS-Gamma_Doppler_Phase_3_zfagbt.webp",
    "correct_answer": "SHADOW DAGGERS Gamma Doppler Phase 3",
    "wrong_answers": [
      "SHADOW DAGGERS Black Laminate",
      "SHADOW DAGGERS Rust Coat",
      "SHADOW DAGGERS Lore"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Qual é o nome desta faca?",
    "picture": "https://res.cloudinary.com/dwm53cbu2/image/upload/a_320/a_hflip/w_1000,f_auto,q_auto:low,fl_lossy,fl_progressive,fl_strip_profile/v1760723546/SHADOW_DAGGERS-Tiger_Tooth_thtyxa.webp",
    "correct_answer": "SHADOW DAGGERS Tiger Tooth",
    "wrong_answers": [
      "SHADOW DAGGERS Black Laminate",
      "SHADOW DAGGERS Rust Coat",
      "SHADOW DAGGERS Lore"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Qual é o nome desta faca?",
    "picture": "https://res.cloudinary.com/dwm53cbu2/image/upload/a_320/a_hflip/w_1000,f_auto,q_auto:low,fl_lossy,fl_progressive,fl_strip_profile/v1760723543/SURVIVAL_KNIFE-Rust_Coat_bseicn.webp",
    "correct_answer": "SURVIVAL KNIFE Rust Coat",
    "wrong_answers": [
      "URSUS KNIFE Rust Coat",
      "PARACORD KNIFE Rust Coat",
      "NAJAVA KNIFE Rust Coat"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Qual é o nome desta faca?",
    "picture": "https://res.cloudinary.com/dwm53cbu2/image/upload/a_320/a_hflip/w_1000,f_auto,q_auto:low,fl_lossy,fl_progressive,fl_strip_profile/v1760723542/SHADOW_DAGGERS-Stained_skckgb.webp",
    "correct_answer": "SHADOW DAGGERS Stained",
    "wrong_answers": [
      "SHADOW DAGGERS Black Laminate",
      "SHADOW DAGGERS Rust Coat",
      "SHADOW DAGGERS Lore"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Qual é o nome desta faca?",
    "picture": "https://res.cloudinary.com/dwm53cbu2/image/upload/a_320/a_hflip/w_1000,f_auto,q_auto:low,fl_lossy,fl_progressive,fl_strip_profile/v1760723540/SHADOW_DAGGERS-Doppler_Phase_1_qumypo.webp",
    "correct_answer": "SHADOW DAGGERS Doppler Phase 1",
    "wrong_answers": [
      "SHADOW DAGGERS Black Laminate",
      "SHADOW DAGGERS Rust Coat",
      "SHADOW DAGGERS Lore"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Qual é o nome desta faca?",
    "picture": "https://res.cloudinary.com/dwm53cbu2/image/upload/a_320/a_hflip/w_1000,f_auto,q_auto:low,fl_lossy,fl_progressive,fl_strip_profile/v1760723538/KARAMBIT-Gamma_Doppler_Phase_2_w8kd3y.webp",
    "correct_answer": "KARAMBIT Gamma Doppler Phase 2",
    "wrong_answers": [
      "KARAMBIT Gamma Doppler Phase 1",
      "KARAMBIT Gamma Doppler Phase 3",
      "KARAMBIT Gamma Doppler Emerald"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Qual é o nome desta faca?",
    "picture": "https://res.cloudinary.com/dwm53cbu2/image/upload/a_320/a_hflip/w_1000,f_auto,q_auto:low,fl_lossy,fl_progressive,fl_strip_profile/v1760723537/KARAMBIT-Gamma_Doppler_Emerald_qovvq0.webp",
    "correct_answer": "KARAMBIT Gamma Doppler Emerald",
    "wrong_answers": [
      "KARAMBIT Gamma Doppler Phase 1",
      "KARAMBIT Gamma Doppler Phase 3",
      "KARAMBIT Gamma Doppler Phase 2"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Qual é o nome desta faca?",
    "picture": "https://res.cloudinary.com/dwm53cbu2/image/upload/a_320/a_hflip/w_1000,f_auto,q_auto:low,fl_lossy,fl_progressive,fl_strip_profile/v1760723534/KARAMBIT-Gamma_Doppler_Phase_4_zrgtwg.webp",
    "correct_answer": "KARAMBIT Gamma Doppler Phase 4",
    "wrong_answers": [
      "KARAMBIT Gamma Doppler Phase 1",
      "KARAMBIT Gamma Doppler Phase 3",
      "KARAMBIT Gamma Doppler Phase 2"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Qual é o nome desta faca?",
    "picture": "https://res.cloudinary.com/dwm53cbu2/image/upload/a_320/a_hflip/w_1000,f_auto,q_auto:low,fl_lossy,fl_progressive,fl_strip_profile/v1760723533/SHADOW_DAGGERS-Gamma_Doppler_Phase_2_hysspe.webp",
    "correct_answer": "SHADOW DAGGERS Gamma Doppler Phase 2",
    "wrong_answers": [
      "SHADOW DAGGERS Black Laminate",
      "SHADOW DAGGERS Rust Coat",
      "SHADOW DAGGERS Lore"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Qual é o nome desta faca?",
    "picture": "https://res.cloudinary.com/dwm53cbu2/image/upload/a_320/a_hflip/w_1000,f_auto,q_auto:low,fl_lossy,fl_progressive,fl_strip_profile/v1760723532/KARAMBIT-Fade_xjxbjj.webp",
    "correct_answer": "KARAMBIT Fade",
    "wrong_answers": [
      "SKELETON Fade",
      "BAYONET Fade",
      "KARAMBIT Lore"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Qual é o nome desta faca?",
    "picture": "https://res.cloudinary.com/dwm53cbu2/image/upload/a_320/a_hflip/w_1000,f_auto,q_auto:low,fl_lossy,fl_progressive,fl_strip_profile/v1760723529/SHADOW_DAGGERS-Gamma_Doppler_Phase_4_aiscgs.webp",
    "correct_answer": "SHADOW DAGGERS Gamma Doppler Phase 4",
    "wrong_answers": [
      "SHADOW DAGGERS Black Laminate",
      "SHADOW DAGGERS Rust Coat",
      "SHADOW DAGGERS Lore"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Qual é o nome desta faca?",
    "picture": "https://res.cloudinary.com/dwm53cbu2/image/upload/a_320/a_hflip/w_1000,f_auto,q_auto:low,fl_lossy,fl_progressive,fl_strip_profile/v1760723528/SHADOW_DAGGERS-Gamma_Doppler_Phase_1_jrtmhf.webp",
    "correct_answer": "SHADOW DAGGERS Gamma Doppler Phase 1",
    "wrong_answers": [
      "SHADOW DAGGERS Black Laminate",
      "SHADOW DAGGERS Rust Coat",
      "SHADOW DAGGERS Lore"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Qual é o nome desta faca?",
    "picture": "https://res.cloudinary.com/dwm53cbu2/image/upload/a_320/a_hflip/w_1000,f_auto,q_auto:low,fl_lossy,fl_progressive,fl_strip_profile/v1760723527/SHADOW_DAGGERS-Gamma_Doppler_Emerald_w7xbgr.webp",
    "correct_answer": "SHADOW DAGGERS Gamma Doppler Emerald",
    "wrong_answers": [
      "SHADOW DAGGERS Black Laminate",
      "SHADOW DAGGERS Rust Coat",
      "SHADOW DAGGERS Lore"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Qual é o nome desta faca?",
    "picture": "https://res.cloudinary.com/dwm53cbu2/image/upload/a_320/a_hflip/w_1000,f_auto,q_auto:low,fl_lossy,fl_progressive,fl_strip_profile/v1760723523/SHADOW_DAGGERS-Marble_Fade_xh37bp.webp",
    "correct_answer": "SHADOW DAGGERS Marble Fade",
    "wrong_answers": [
      "SHADOW DAGGERS Black Laminate",
      "SHADOW DAGGERS Rust Coat",
      "SHADOW DAGGERS Lore"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Qual é o nome desta faca?",
    "picture": "https://res.cloudinary.com/dwm53cbu2/image/upload/a_320/a_hflip/w_1000,f_auto,q_auto:low,fl_lossy,fl_progressive,fl_strip_profile/v1760723522/URSUS_KNIFE-Doppler_Phase_1_yqcwkt.webp",
    "correct_answer": "URSUS KNIFE Doppler Phase 1",
    "wrong_answers": [
      "NAJAVA KNIFE Doppler Phase 1",
      "PARACORD KNIFE Doppler Phase 1",
      "TALON KNIFE Doppler Phase 1"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Qual é o nome desta faca?",
    "picture": "https://res.cloudinary.com/dwm53cbu2/image/upload/a_320/a_hflip/w_1000,f_auto,q_auto:low,fl_lossy,fl_progressive,fl_strip_profile/v1760723521/HUNTSMAN_KNIFE-Black_Laminate_yqmixo.webp",
    "correct_answer": "HUNTSMAN KNIFE Black Laminate",
    "wrong_answers": [
      "GUT KNIFE Black Laminate",
      "FALCHION KNIFE Black Laminate",
      "FLIP KNIFE Black Laminate"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Qual é o nome desta faca?",
    "picture": "https://res.cloudinary.com/dwm53cbu2/image/upload/a_320/a_hflip/w_1000,f_auto,q_auto:low,fl_lossy,fl_progressive,fl_strip_profile/v1760723518/SHADOW_DAGGERS-Doppler_Ruby_l4dbzi.webp",
    "correct_answer": "SHADOW DAGGERS Doppler Ruby",
    "wrong_answers": [
      "SHADOW DAGGERS Black Laminate",
      "SHADOW DAGGERS Rust Coat",
      "SHADOW DAGGERS Lore"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Qual é o nome desta faca?",
    "picture": "https://res.cloudinary.com/dwm53cbu2/image/upload/a_320/a_hflip/w_1000,f_auto,q_auto:low,fl_lossy,fl_progressive,fl_strip_profile/v1760723516/HUNTSMAN_KNIFE-Rust_Coat_rbtm2o.webp",
    "correct_answer": "HUNTSMAN KNIFE Rust Coat",
    "wrong_answers": [
      "URSUS KNIFE Rust Coat",
      "PARACORD KNIFE Rust Coat",
      "NAJAVA KNIFE Rust Coat"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Qual é o nome desta faca?",
    "picture": "https://res.cloudinary.com/dwm53cbu2/image/upload/a_320/a_hflip/w_1000,f_auto,q_auto:low,fl_lossy,fl_progressive,fl_strip_profile/v1760723516/SHADOW_DAGGERS-Crimson_Web_ge8uek.webp",
    "correct_answer": "SHADOW DAGGERS Crimson Web",
    "wrong_answers": [
      "SHADOW DAGGERS Black Laminate",
      "SHADOW DAGGERS Rust Coat",
      "SHADOW DAGGERS Lore"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Qual é o nome desta faca?",
    "picture": "https://res.cloudinary.com/dwm53cbu2/image/upload/a_320/a_hflip/w_1000,f_auto,q_auto:low,fl_lossy,fl_progressive,fl_strip_profile/v1760723513/SHADOW_DAGGERS-Doppler_Sapphire_sw9fqk.webp",
    "correct_answer": "SHADOW DAGGERS Doppler Sapphire",
    "wrong_answers": [
      "SHADOW DAGGERS Black Laminate",
      "SHADOW DAGGERS Rust Coat",
      "SHADOW DAGGERS Lore"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Qual é o nome desta faca?",
    "picture": "https://res.cloudinary.com/dwm53cbu2/image/upload/a_320/a_hflip/w_1000,f_auto,q_auto:low,fl_lossy,fl_progressive,fl_strip_profile/v1760723511/URSUS_KNIFE-Marble_Fade_ckdnnz.webp",
    "correct_answer": "URSUS KNIFE Marble Fade",
    "wrong_answers": [
      "PARACORD KNIFE Marble Fade",
      "NAJAVA KNIFE Marble Fade",
      "TALON KNIFE Marble Fade"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Qual é o nome desta faca?",
    "picture": "https://res.cloudinary.com/dwm53cbu2/image/upload/a_320/a_hflip/w_1000,f_auto,q_auto:low,fl_lossy,fl_progressive,fl_strip_profile/v1760723509/SHADOW_DAGGERS-Doppler_Phase_2_wogeuf.webp",
    "correct_answer": "SHADOW DAGGERS Doppler Phase 2",
    "wrong_answers": [
      "SHADOW DAGGERS Black Laminate",
      "SHADOW DAGGERS Rust Coat",
      "SHADOW DAGGERS Lore"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Qual é o nome desta faca?",
    "picture": "https://res.cloudinary.com/dwm53cbu2/image/upload/a_320/a_hflip/w_1000,f_auto,q_auto:low,fl_lossy,fl_progressive,fl_strip_profile/v1760723507/PARACORD_KNIFE-Vanilla_hvpel3.webp",
    "correct_answer": "PARACORD KNIFE Vanilla",
    "wrong_answers": [
      "URSUS KNIFE Vanilla",
      "NAJAVA KNIFE Vanilla",
      "NOMAD KNIFE Vanilla"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Qual é o nome desta faca?",
    "picture": "https://res.cloudinary.com/dwm53cbu2/image/upload/a_320/a_hflip/w_1000,f_auto,q_auto:low,fl_lossy,fl_progressive,fl_strip_profile/v1760723507/URSUS_KNIFE-Doppler_Ruby_irllm2.webp",
    "correct_answer": "URSUS KNIFE Doppler Ruby",
    "wrong_answers": [
      "NAJAVA KNIFE Doppler Ruby",
      "TALON KNIFE Doppler Ruby",
      "PARACORD KNIFE Doppler Ruby"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Qual é o nome desta faca?",
    "picture": "https://res.cloudinary.com/dwm53cbu2/image/upload/a_320/a_hflip/w_1000,f_auto,q_auto:low,fl_lossy,fl_progressive,fl_strip_profile/v1760723504/URSUS_KNIFE-Doppler_Sapphire_nmfkp1.webp",
    "correct_answer": "URSUS KNIFE Doppler Sapphire",
    "wrong_answers": [
      "NAJAVA KNIFE Doppler Sapphire",
      "TALON KNIFE Doppler Sapphire",
      "PARACORD KNIFE Doppler Sapphire"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Qual é o nome desta faca?",
    "picture": "https://res.cloudinary.com/dwm53cbu2/image/upload/a_320/a_hflip/w_1000,f_auto,q_auto:low,fl_lossy,fl_progressive,fl_strip_profile/v1760723503/NAJAVA_KNIFE-Doppler_Ruby_t0xkgp.webp",
    "correct_answer": "NAJAVA KNIFE Doppler Ruby",
    "wrong_answers": [
      "URSUS KNIFE Doppler Ruby",
      "TALON KNIFE Doppler Ruby",
      "PARACORD KNIFE Doppler Ruby"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Qual é o nome desta faca?",
    "picture": "https://res.cloudinary.com/dwm53cbu2/image/upload/a_320/a_hflip/w_1000,f_auto,q_auto:low,fl_lossy,fl_progressive,fl_strip_profile/v1760723501/NAJAVA_KNIFE-Doppler_Phase_1_zfe3zt.webp",
    "correct_answer": "NAJAVA KNIFE Doppler Phase 1",
    "wrong_answers": [
      "URSUS KNIFE Doppler Phase 1",
      "PARACORD KNIFE Doppler Phase 1",
      "TALON KNIFE Doppler Phase 1"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Qual é o nome desta faca?",
    "picture": "https://res.cloudinary.com/dwm53cbu2/image/upload/a_320/a_hflip/w_1000,f_auto,q_auto:low,fl_lossy,fl_progressive,fl_strip_profile/v1760723498/NAJAVA_KNIFE-Case_Hardened_uufodb.webp",
    "correct_answer": "NAJAVA KNIFE Case Hardened",
    "wrong_answers": [
      "URSUS KNIFE Case Hardened",
      "TALON KNIFE Case Hardened",
      "PARACORD KNIFE Case Hardened"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Qual é o nome desta faca?",
    "picture": "https://res.cloudinary.com/dwm53cbu2/image/upload/a_320/a_hflip/w_1000,f_auto,q_auto:low,fl_lossy,fl_progressive,fl_strip_profile/v1760723497/KARAMBIT-Tiger_Tooth_cddcju.webp",
    "correct_answer": "KARAMBIT Tiger Tooth",
    "wrong_answers": [
      "SKELETON Tiger Tooth",
      "BAYONET Tiger Tooth",
      "KARAMBIT Lore"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Qual é o nome desta faca?",
    "picture": "https://res.cloudinary.com/dwm53cbu2/image/upload/a_320/a_hflip/w_1000,f_auto,q_auto:low,fl_lossy,fl_progressive,fl_strip_profile/v1760723494/URSUS_KNIFE-Doppler_Phase_2_whisql.webp",
    "correct_answer": "URSUS KNIFE Doppler Phase 2",
    "wrong_answers": [
      "NAJAVA KNIFE Doppler Phase 2",
      "TALON KNIFE Doppler Phase 2",
      "PARACORD KNIFE Doppler Phase 2"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Qual é o nome desta faca?",
    "picture": "https://res.cloudinary.com/dwm53cbu2/image/upload/a_320/a_hflip/w_1000,f_auto,q_auto:low,fl_lossy,fl_progressive,fl_strip_profile/v1760723493/NAJAVA_KNIFE-Tiger_Tooth_lx8shb.webp",
    "correct_answer": "NAJAVA KNIFE Tiger Tooth",
    "wrong_answers": [
      "URSUS KNIFE Tiger Tooth",
      "PARACORD KNIFE Tiger Tooth",
      "NOMAD KNIFE Tiger Tooth"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Qual é o nome desta faca?",
    "picture": "https://res.cloudinary.com/dwm53cbu2/image/upload/a_320/a_hflip/w_1000,f_auto,q_auto:low,fl_lossy,fl_progressive,fl_strip_profile/v1760723490/GUT_KNIFE-Black_Laminate_v24qiq.webp",
    "correct_answer": "GUT KNIFE Black Laminate",
    "wrong_answers": [
      "HUNTSMAN KNIFE Black Laminate",
      "FALCHION KNIFE Black Laminate",
      "FLIP KNIFE Black Laminate"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Qual é o nome desta faca?",
    "picture": "https://res.cloudinary.com/dwm53cbu2/image/upload/a_320/a_hflip/w_1000,f_auto,q_auto:low,fl_lossy,fl_progressive,fl_strip_profile/v1760723490/NAJAVA_KNIFE-Damascus_Steel_dapm05.webp",
    "correct_answer": "NAJAVA KNIFE Damascus Steel",
    "wrong_answers": [
      "GUT KNIFE Damascus Steel",
      "URSUS KNIFE Damascus Steel",
      "TALON KNIFE Damascus Steel"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Qual é o nome desta faca?",
    "picture": "https://res.cloudinary.com/dwm53cbu2/image/upload/a_320/a_hflip/w_1000,f_auto,q_auto:low,fl_lossy,fl_progressive,fl_strip_profile/v1760723489/GUT_KNIFE-Damascus_Steel_os17rc.webp",
    "correct_answer": "GUT KNIFE Damascus Steel",
    "wrong_answers": [
      "NAJAVA KNIFE Damascus Steel",
      "URSUS KNIFE Damascus Steel",
      "TALON KNIFE Damascus Steel"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Qual é o nome desta faca?",
    "picture": "https://res.cloudinary.com/dwm53cbu2/image/upload/a_320/a_hflip/w_1000,f_auto,q_auto:low,fl_lossy,fl_progressive,fl_strip_profile/v1760723486/NAJAVA_KNIFE-Doppler_Sapphire_tox5hp.webp",
    "correct_answer": "NAJAVA KNIFE Doppler Sapphire",
    "wrong_answers": [
      "URSUS KNIFE Doppler Sapphire",
      "TALON KNIFE Doppler Sapphire",
      "PARACORD KNIFE Doppler Sapphire"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Qual é o nome desta faca?",
    "picture": "https://res.cloudinary.com/dwm53cbu2/image/upload/a_320/a_hflip/w_1000,f_auto,q_auto:low,fl_lossy,fl_progressive,fl_strip_profile/v1760723484/NAJAVA_KNIFE-Vanilla_bogzac.webp",
    "correct_answer": "NAJAVA KNIFE Vanilla",
    "wrong_answers": [
      "URSUS KNIFE Vanilla",
      "PARACORD KNIFE Vanilla",
      "NOMAD KNIFE Vanilla"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Qual é o nome desta faca?",
    "picture": "https://res.cloudinary.com/dwm53cbu2/image/upload/a_320/a_hflip/w_1000,f_auto,q_auto:low,fl_lossy,fl_progressive,fl_strip_profile/v1760723483/NAJAVA_KNIFE-Doppler_Phase_3_fs0ekg.webp",
    "correct_answer": "NAJAVA KNIFE Doppler Phase 3",
    "wrong_answers": [
      "URSUS KNIFE Doppler Phase 3",
      "PARACORD KNIFE Doppler Phase 3",
      "TALON KNIFE Doppler Phase 3"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Qual é o nome desta faca?",
    "picture": "https://res.cloudinary.com/dwm53cbu2/image/upload/a_320/a_hflip/w_1000,f_auto,q_auto:low,fl_lossy,fl_progressive,fl_strip_profile/v1760723482/M9_BAYONET-Black_Laminate_oyqnu1.webp",
    "correct_answer": "M9 BAYONET Black Laminate",
    "wrong_answers": [
      "M9 BAYONET Lore",
      "M9 BAYONET Autotronic",
      "M9 BAYONET Rust Coat"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Qual é o nome desta faca?",
    "picture": "https://res.cloudinary.com/dwm53cbu2/image/upload/a_320/a_hflip/w_1000,f_auto,q_auto:low,fl_lossy,fl_progressive,fl_strip_profile/v1760723479/KARAMBIT-Slaughter_tsna3d.webp",
    "correct_answer": "KARAMBIT Slaughter",
    "wrong_answers": [
      "SKELETON Slaughter",
      "BAYONET Slaughter",
      "KARAMBIT Lore"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Qual é o nome desta faca?",
    "picture": "https://res.cloudinary.com/dwm53cbu2/image/upload/a_320/a_hflip/w_1000,f_auto,q_auto:low,fl_lossy,fl_progressive,fl_strip_profile/v1760723478/NAJAVA_KNIFE-Stained_qgpdqk.webp",
    "correct_answer": "NAJAVA KNIFE Stained",
    "wrong_answers": [
      "PARACORD KNIFE Stained",
      "URSUS KNIFE Stained",
      "TALON KNIFE Stained"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Qual é o nome desta faca?",
    "picture": "https://res.cloudinary.com/dwm53cbu2/image/upload/a_320/a_hflip/w_1000,f_auto,q_auto:low,fl_lossy,fl_progressive,fl_strip_profile/v1760723476/URSUS_KNIFE-Case_Hardened_oc1awq.webp",
    "correct_answer": "URSUS KNIFE Case Hardened",
    "wrong_answers": [
      "NAJAVA KNIFE Case Hardened",
      "TALON KNIFE Case Hardened",
      "PARACORD KNIFE Case Hardened"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Qual é o nome desta faca?",
    "picture": "https://res.cloudinary.com/dwm53cbu2/image/upload/a_320/a_hflip/w_1000,f_auto,q_auto:low,fl_lossy,fl_progressive,fl_strip_profile/v1760723473/KARAMBIT-Vanilla_pr8w3h.webp",
    "correct_answer": "KARAMBIT Vanilla",
    "wrong_answers": [
      "SKELETON Vanilla",
      "BAYONET Vanilla",
      "KARAMBIT Lore"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Qual é o nome desta faca?",
    "picture": "https://res.cloudinary.com/dwm53cbu2/image/upload/a_320/a_hflip/w_1000,f_auto,q_auto:low,fl_lossy,fl_progressive,fl_strip_profile/v1760723472/NAJAVA_KNIFE-Fade_tlomaf.webp",
    "correct_answer": "NAJAVA KNIFE Fade",
    "wrong_answers": [
      "URSUS KNIFE Fade",
      "PARACORD KNIFE Fade",
      "TALON KNIFE Fade"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Qual é o nome desta faca?",
    "picture": "https://res.cloudinary.com/dwm53cbu2/image/upload/a_320/a_hflip/w_1000,f_auto,q_auto:low,fl_lossy,fl_progressive,fl_strip_profile/v1760723471/KARAMBIT-Doppler_Phase_1_nlzfmx.webp",
    "correct_answer": "KARAMBIT Doppler Phase 1",
    "wrong_answers": [
      "SKELETON Doppler Phase 1",
      "BAYONET Doppler Phase 1",
      "KARAMBIT Doppler Sapphire"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Qual é o nome desta faca?",
    "picture": "https://res.cloudinary.com/dwm53cbu2/image/upload/a_320/a_hflip/w_1000,f_auto,q_auto:low,fl_lossy,fl_progressive,fl_strip_profile/v1760723468/TALON_KNIFE-Case_Hardened_l2cwnk.webp",
    "correct_answer": "TALON KNIFE Case Hardened",
    "wrong_answers": [
      "NAJAVA KNIFE Case Hardened",
      "URSUS KNIFE Case Hardened",
      "PARACORD KNIFE Case Hardened"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Qual é o nome desta faca?",
    "picture": "https://res.cloudinary.com/dwm53cbu2/image/upload/a_320/a_hflip/w_1000,f_auto,q_auto:low,fl_lossy,fl_progressive,fl_strip_profile/v1760723466/TALON_KNIFE-Doppler_Sapphire_g05vko.webp",
    "correct_answer": "TALON KNIFE Doppler Sapphire",
    "wrong_answers": [
      "URSUS KNIFE Doppler Sapphire",
      "NAJAVA KNIFE Doppler Sapphire",
      "PARACORD KNIFE Doppler Sapphire"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Qual é o nome desta faca?",
    "picture": "https://res.cloudinary.com/dwm53cbu2/image/upload/a_320/a_hflip/w_1000,f_auto,q_auto:low,fl_lossy,fl_progressive,fl_strip_profile/v1760723465/URSUS_KNIFE-Damascus_Steel_m4qw26.webp",
    "correct_answer": "URSUS KNIFE Damascus Steel",
    "wrong_answers": [
      "NAJAVA KNIFE Damascus Steel",
      "GUT KNIFE Damascus Steel",
      "TALON KNIFE Damascus Steel"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Qual é o nome desta faca?",
    "picture": "https://res.cloudinary.com/dwm53cbu2/image/upload/a_320/a_hflip/w_1000,f_auto,q_auto:low,fl_lossy,fl_progressive,fl_strip_profile/v1760723462/TALON_KNIFE-Damascus_Steel_s1qvcx.webp",
    "correct_answer": "TALON KNIFE Damascus Steel",
    "wrong_answers": [
      "NAJAVA KNIFE Damascus Steel",
      "GUT KNIFE Damascus Steel",
      "URSUS KNIFE Damascus Steel"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Qual é o nome desta faca?",
    "picture": "https://res.cloudinary.com/dwm53cbu2/image/upload/a_320/a_hflip/w_1000,f_auto,q_auto:low,fl_lossy,fl_progressive,fl_strip_profile/v1760723461/TALON_KNIFE-Doppler_Ruby_kqwmka.webp",
    "correct_answer": "TALON KNIFE Doppler Ruby",
    "wrong_answers": [
      "URSUS KNIFE Doppler Ruby",
      "NAJAVA KNIFE Doppler Ruby",
      "PARACORD KNIFE Doppler Ruby"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Qual é o nome desta faca?",
    "picture": "https://res.cloudinary.com/dwm53cbu2/image/upload/a_320/a_hflip/w_1000,f_auto,q_auto:low,fl_lossy,fl_progressive,fl_strip_profile/v1760723458/TALON_KNIFE-Doppler_Phase_2_nr2xkx.webp",
    "correct_answer": "TALON KNIFE Doppler Phase 2",
    "wrong_answers": [
      "NAJAVA KNIFE Doppler Phase 2",
      "URSUS KNIFE Doppler Phase 2",
      "PARACORD KNIFE Doppler Phase 2"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Qual é o nome desta faca?",
    "picture": "https://res.cloudinary.com/dwm53cbu2/image/upload/a_320/a_hflip/w_1000,f_auto,q_auto:low,fl_lossy,fl_progressive,fl_strip_profile/v1760723457/TALON_KNIFE-Doppler_Phase_4_swi96z.webp",
    "correct_answer": "TALON KNIFE Doppler Phase 4",
    "wrong_answers": [
      "URSUS KNIFE Doppler Phase 4",
      "PARACORD KNIFE Doppler Phase 4",
      "NAJAVA KNIFE Doppler Phase 4"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Qual é o nome desta faca?",
    "picture": "https://res.cloudinary.com/dwm53cbu2/image/upload/a_320/a_hflip/w_1000,f_auto,q_auto:low,fl_lossy,fl_progressive,fl_strip_profile/v1760723456/KARAMBIT-Stained_jl85ad.webp",
    "correct_answer": "KARAMBIT Stained",
    "wrong_answers": [
      "SKELETON Stained",
      "BAYONET Stained",
      "KARAMBIT Lore"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Qual é o nome desta faca?",
    "picture": "https://res.cloudinary.com/dwm53cbu2/image/upload/a_320/a_hflip/w_1000,f_auto,q_auto:low,fl_lossy,fl_progressive,fl_strip_profile/v1760723454/SKELETON-Rust_Coat_vynaqs.webp",
    "correct_answer": "SKELETON Rust Coat",
    "wrong_answers": [
      "KARAMBIT Rust Coat",
      "BAYONET Rust Coat",
      "SKELETON Vanilla"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Qual é o nome desta faca?",
    "picture": "https://res.cloudinary.com/dwm53cbu2/image/upload/a_320/a_hflip/w_1000,f_auto,q_auto:low,fl_lossy,fl_progressive,fl_strip_profile/v1760723452/KARAMBIT-Marble_Fade_yzlfsl.webp",
    "correct_answer": "KARAMBIT Marble Fade",
    "wrong_answers": [
      "SKELETON Marble Fade",
      "BAYONET Marble Fade",
      "KARAMBIT Lore"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Qual é o nome desta faca?",
    "picture": "https://res.cloudinary.com/dwm53cbu2/image/upload/a_320/a_hflip/w_1000,f_auto,q_auto:low,fl_lossy,fl_progressive,fl_strip_profile/v1760723451/SHADOW_DAGGERS-Slaughter_ay01zv.webp",
    "correct_answer": "SHADOW DAGGERS Slaughter",
    "wrong_answers": [
      "SHADOW DAGGERS Black Laminate",
      "SHADOW DAGGERS Rust Coat",
      "SHADOW DAGGERS Lore"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Qual é o nome desta faca?",
    "picture": "https://res.cloudinary.com/dwm53cbu2/image/upload/a_320/a_hflip/w_1000,f_auto,q_auto:low,fl_lossy,fl_progressive,fl_strip_profile/v1760723448/M9_BAYONET-Autotronic_q5rfla.webp",
    "correct_answer": "M9 BAYONET Autotronic",
    "wrong_answers": [
      "M9 BAYONET Lore",
      "M9 BAYONET Black Laminate",
      "M9 BAYONET Rust Coat"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Qual é o nome desta faca?",
    "picture": "https://res.cloudinary.com/dwm53cbu2/image/upload/a_320/a_hflip/w_1000,f_auto,q_auto:low,fl_lossy,fl_progressive,fl_strip_profile/v1760723446/KARAMBIT-Doppler_Sapphire_ref3wq.webp",
    "correct_answer": "KARAMBIT Doppler Sapphire",
    "wrong_answers": [
      "SKELETON Doppler Sapphire",
      "BAYONET Doppler Sapphire",
      "KARAMBIT Doppler Phase 1"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Qual é o nome desta faca?",
    "picture": "https://res.cloudinary.com/dwm53cbu2/image/upload/a_320/a_hflip/w_1000,f_auto,q_auto:low,fl_lossy,fl_progressive,fl_strip_profile/v1760723444/KARAMBIT-Doppler_Phase_4_ok0yad.webp",
    "correct_answer": "KARAMBIT Doppler Phase 4",
    "wrong_answers": [
      "SKELETON Doppler Phase 4",
      "BAYONET Doppler Phase 4",
      "KARAMBIT Doppler Phase 1"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Qual é o nome desta faca?",
    "picture": "https://res.cloudinary.com/dwm53cbu2/image/upload/a_320/a_hflip/w_1000,f_auto,q_auto:low,fl_lossy,fl_progressive,fl_strip_profile/v1760723442/KARAMBIT-Doppler_Ruby_mnqnz8.webp",
    "correct_answer": "KARAMBIT Doppler Ruby",
    "wrong_answers": [
      "SKELETON Doppler Ruby",
      "KARAMBIT Doppler Phase 1",
      "KARAMBIT Doppler Sapphire"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Qual é o nome desta faca?",
    "picture": "https://res.cloudinary.com/dwm53cbu2/image/upload/a_320/a_hflip/w_1000,f_auto,q_auto:low,fl_lossy,fl_progressive,fl_strip_profile/v1760723441/KARAMBIT-Doppler_Phase_3_u8p5sf.webp",
    "correct_answer": "KARAMBIT Doppler Phase 3",
    "wrong_answers": [
      "SKELETON Doppler Phase 3",
      "KARAMBIT Doppler Phase 1",
      "KARAMBIT Doppler Sapphire"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Qual é o nome desta faca?",
    "picture": "https://res.cloudinary.com/dwm53cbu2/image/upload/a_320/a_hflip/w_1000,f_auto,q_auto:low,fl_lossy,fl_progressive,fl_strip_profile/v1760723439/KARAMBIT-Doppler_Black_Pearl_spgg5d.webp",
    "correct_answer": "KARAMBIT Doppler Black Pearl",
    "wrong_answers": [
      "SKELETON Doppler Black Pearl",
      "KARAMBIT Doppler Phase 1",
      "KARAMBIT Doppler Sapphire"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Qual é o nome desta faca?",
    "picture": "https://res.cloudinary.com/dwm53cbu2/image/upload/a_320/a_hflip/w_1000,f_auto,q_auto:low,fl_lossy,fl_progressive,fl_strip_profile/v1760723438/KARAMBIT-Doppler_Phase_2_toudyg.webp",
    "correct_answer": "KARAMBIT Doppler Phase 2",
    "wrong_answers": [
      "SKELETON Doppler Phase 2",
      "BAYONET Doppler Phase 2",
      "KARAMBIT Doppler Phase 1"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Qual é o nome desta faca?",
    "picture": "https://res.cloudinary.com/dwm53cbu2/image/upload/a_320/a_hflip/w_1000,f_auto,q_auto:low,fl_lossy,fl_progressive,fl_strip_profile/v1760723435/URSUS_KNIFE-Slaughter_oqmqpm.webp",
    "correct_answer": "URSUS KNIFE Slaughter",
    "wrong_answers": [
      "PARACORD KNIFE Slaughter",
      "NAJAVA KNIFE Slaughter",
      "TALON KNIFE Slaughter"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Qual é o nome desta faca?",
    "picture": "https://res.cloudinary.com/dwm53cbu2/image/upload/a_320/a_hflip/w_1000,f_auto,q_auto:low,fl_lossy,fl_progressive,fl_strip_profile/v1760723433/KARAMBIT-Damascus_Steel_fzcr23.webp",
    "correct_answer": "KARAMBIT Damascus Steel",
    "wrong_answers": [
      "SKELETON Damascus Steel",
      "BAYONET Damascus Steel",
      "KARAMBIT Lore"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Qual é o nome desta faca?",
    "picture": "https://res.cloudinary.com/dwm53cbu2/image/upload/a_320/a_hflip/w_1000,f_auto,q_auto:low,fl_lossy,fl_progressive,fl_strip_profile/v1760723433/KARAMBIT-Case_Hardened_froffk.webp",
    "correct_answer": "KARAMBIT Case Hardened",
    "wrong_answers": [
      "SKELETON Case Hardened",
      "BAYONET Case Hardened",
      "KARAMBIT Lore"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Qual é o nome desta faca?",
    "picture": "https://res.cloudinary.com/dwm53cbu2/image/upload/a_320/a_hflip/w_1000,f_auto,q_auto:low,fl_lossy,fl_progressive,fl_strip_profile/v1760723431/FALCHION_KNIFE-Rust_Coat_skkotp.webp",
    "correct_answer": "FALCHION KNIFE Rust Coat",
    "wrong_answers": [
      "URSUS KNIFE Rust Coat",
      "PARACORD KNIFE Rust Coat",
      "NAJAVA KNIFE Rust Coat"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Qual é o nome desta faca?",
    "picture": "https://res.cloudinary.com/dwm53cbu2/image/upload/a_320/a_hflip/w_1000,f_auto,q_auto:low,fl_lossy,fl_progressive,fl_strip_profile/v1760723429/HUNTSMAN_KNIFE-Lore_vsgdtb.webp",
    "correct_answer": "HUNTSMAN KNIFE Lore",
    "wrong_answers": [
      "GUT KNIFE Lore",
      "FLIP KNIFE Lore",
      "FALCHION KNIFE Lore"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Qual é o nome desta faca?",
    "picture": "https://res.cloudinary.com/dwm53cbu2/image/upload/a_320/a_hflip/w_1000,f_auto,q_auto:low,fl_lossy,fl_progressive,fl_strip_profile/v1760723427/URSUS_KNIFE-Doppler_Phase_4_itdtpq.webp",
    "correct_answer": "URSUS KNIFE Doppler Phase 4",
    "wrong_answers": [
      "TALON KNIFE Doppler Phase 4",
      "PARACORD KNIFE Doppler Phase 4",
      "NAJAVA KNIFE Doppler Phase 4"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Qual é o nome desta faca?",
    "picture": "https://res.cloudinary.com/dwm53cbu2/image/upload/a_320/a_hflip/w_1000,f_auto,q_auto:low,fl_lossy,fl_progressive,fl_strip_profile/v1760723424/FALCHION_KNIFE-Lore_ejgp1u.webp",
    "correct_answer": "FALCHION KNIFE Lore",
    "wrong_answers": [
      "GUT KNIFE Lore",
      "FLIP KNIFE Lore",
      "HUNTSMAN KNIFE Lore"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Qual é o nome desta faca?",
    "picture": "https://res.cloudinary.com/dwm53cbu2/image/upload/a_320/a_hflip/w_1000,f_auto,q_auto:low,fl_lossy,fl_progressive,fl_strip_profile/v1760723423/SHADOW_DAGGERS-Forest_DDPAT_bufb2s.webp",
    "correct_answer": "SHADOW DAGGERS Forest DDPAT",
    "wrong_answers": [
      "SHADOW DAGGERS Black Laminate",
      "SHADOW DAGGERS Rust Coat",
      "SHADOW DAGGERS Lore"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Qual é o nome desta faca?",
    "picture": "https://res.cloudinary.com/dwm53cbu2/image/upload/a_320/a_hflip/w_1000,f_auto,q_auto:low,fl_lossy,fl_progressive,fl_strip_profile/v1760723421/SHADOW_DAGGERS-Doppler_Phase_3_ib8pkd.webp",
    "correct_answer": "SHADOW DAGGERS Doppler Phase 3",
    "wrong_answers": [
      "SHADOW DAGGERS Black Laminate",
      "SHADOW DAGGERS Rust Coat",
      "SHADOW DAGGERS Lore"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Qual é o nome desta faca?",
    "picture": "https://res.cloudinary.com/dwm53cbu2/image/upload/a_320/a_hflip/w_1000,f_auto,q_auto:low,fl_lossy,fl_progressive,fl_strip_profile/v1760723420/URSUS_KNIFE-Scorched_r3jehv.webp",
    "correct_answer": "URSUS KNIFE Scorched",
    "wrong_answers": [
      "PARACORD KNIFE Scorched",
      "NOMAD KNIFE Scorched",
      "TALON KNIFE Scorched"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Qual é o nome desta faca?",
    "picture": "https://res.cloudinary.com/dwm53cbu2/image/upload/a_320/a_hflip/w_1000,f_auto,q_auto:low,fl_lossy,fl_progressive,fl_strip_profile/v1760723417/SHADOW_DAGGERS-Doppler_Phase_4_bhuce7.webp",
    "correct_answer": "SHADOW DAGGERS Doppler Phase 4",
    "wrong_answers": [
      "SHADOW DAGGERS Black Laminate",
      "SHADOW DAGGERS Rust Coat",
      "SHADOW DAGGERS Lore"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Qual é o nome desta faca?",
    "picture": "https://res.cloudinary.com/dwm53cbu2/image/upload/a_320/a_hflip/w_1000,f_auto,q_auto:low,fl_lossy,fl_progressive,fl_strip_profile/v1760723416/FALCHION_KNIFE-Black_Laminate_dvcadx.webp",
    "correct_answer": "FALCHION KNIFE Black Laminate",
    "wrong_answers": [
      "HUNTSMAN KNIFE Black Laminate",
      "GUT KNIFE Black Laminate",
      "FLIP KNIFE Black Laminate"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Qual é o nome desta faca?",
    "picture": "https://res.cloudinary.com/dwm53cbu2/image/upload/a_320/a_hflip/w_1000,f_auto,q_auto:low,fl_lossy,fl_progressive,fl_strip_profile/v1760723413/SHADOW_DAGGERS-Bright_Water_apmh0j.webp",
    "correct_answer": "SHADOW DAGGERS Bright Water",
    "wrong_answers": [
      "SHADOW DAGGERS Black Laminate",
      "SHADOW DAGGERS Rust Coat",
      "SHADOW DAGGERS Lore"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Qual é o nome desta faca?",
    "picture": "https://res.cloudinary.com/dwm53cbu2/image/upload/a_320/a_hflip/w_1000,f_auto,q_auto:low,fl_lossy,fl_progressive,fl_strip_profile/v1760723412/SHADOW_DAGGERS-Doppler_Black_Pearl_rofa08.webp",
    "correct_answer": "SHADOW DAGGERS Doppler Black Pearl",
    "wrong_answers": [
      "SHADOW DAGGERS Black Laminate",
      "SHADOW DAGGERS Rust Coat",
      "SHADOW DAGGERS Lore"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Qual é o nome desta faca?",
    "picture": "https://res.cloudinary.com/dwm53cbu2/image/upload/a_320/a_hflip/w_1000,f_auto,q_auto:low,fl_lossy,fl_progressive,fl_strip_profile/v1760723411/SHADOW_DAGGERS-Boreal_Forest_hhxboe.webp",
    "correct_answer": "SHADOW DAGGERS Boreal Forest",
    "wrong_answers": [
      "SHADOW DAGGERS Black Laminate",
      "SHADOW DAGGERS Rust Coat",
      "SHADOW DAGGERS Lore"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Qual é o nome desta faca?",
    "picture": "https://res.cloudinary.com/dwm53cbu2/image/upload/a_320/a_hflip/w_1000,f_auto,q_auto:low,fl_lossy,fl_progressive,fl_strip_profile/v1760723408/SHADOW_DAGGERS-Blue_Steel_o3mzt1.webp",
    "correct_answer": "SHADOW DAGGERS Blue Steel",
    "wrong_answers": [
      "SHADOW DAGGERS Black Laminate",
      "SHADOW DAGGERS Rust Coat",
      "SHADOW DAGGERS Lore"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Qual é o nome desta faca?",
    "picture": "https://res.cloudinary.com/dwm53cbu2/image/upload/a_320/a_hflip/w_1000,f_auto,q_auto:low,fl_lossy,fl_progressive,fl_strip_profile/v1760723407/PARACORD_KNIFE-Urban_Masked_owoxvq.webp",
    "correct_answer": "PARACORD KNIFE Urban Masked",
    "wrong_answers": [
      "NOMAD KNIFE Urban Masked",
      "URSUS KNIFE Urban Masked",
      "TALON KNIFE Urban Masked"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Qual é o nome desta faca?",
    "picture": "https://res.cloudinary.com/dwm53cbu2/image/upload/a_320/a_hflip/w_1000,f_auto,q_auto:low,fl_lossy,fl_progressive,fl_strip_profile/v1760723406/PARACORD_KNIFE-Tiger_Tooth_l5vlwi.webp",
    "correct_answer": "PARACORD KNIFE Tiger Tooth",
    "wrong_answers": [
      "URSUS KNIFE Tiger Tooth",
      "NAJAVA KNIFE Tiger Tooth",
      "NOMAD KNIFE Tiger Tooth"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Qual é o nome desta faca?",
    "picture": "https://res.cloudinary.com/dwm53cbu2/image/upload/a_320/a_hflip/w_1000,f_auto,q_auto:low,fl_lossy,fl_progressive,fl_strip_profile/v1760723403/URSUS_KNIFE-Fade_bfx6bv.webp",
    "correct_answer": "URSUS KNIFE Fade",
    "wrong_answers": [
      "NAJAVA KNIFE Fade",
      "PARACORD KNIFE Fade",
      "TALON KNIFE Fade"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Qual é o nome desta faca?",
    "picture": "https://res.cloudinary.com/dwm53cbu2/image/upload/a_320/a_hflip/w_1000,f_auto,q_auto:low,fl_lossy,fl_progressive,fl_strip_profile/v1760723401/PARACORD_KNIFE-Stained_kzig3q.webp",
    "correct_answer": "PARACORD KNIFE Stained",
    "wrong_answers": [
      "NAJAVA KNIFE Stained",
      "URSUS KNIFE Stained",
      "TALON KNIFE Stained"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Qual é o nome desta faca?",
    "picture": "https://res.cloudinary.com/dwm53cbu2/image/upload/a_320/a_hflip/w_1000,f_auto,q_auto:low,fl_lossy,fl_progressive,fl_strip_profile/v1760723399/PARACORD_KNIFE-Slaughter_vm6df7.webp",
    "correct_answer": "PARACORD KNIFE Slaughter",
    "wrong_answers": [
      "URSUS KNIFE Slaughter",
      "NAJAVA KNIFE Slaughter",
      "TALON KNIFE Slaughter"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Qual é o nome desta faca?",
    "picture": "https://res.cloudinary.com/dwm53cbu2/image/upload/a_320/a_hflip/w_1000,f_auto,q_auto:low,fl_lossy,fl_progressive,fl_strip_profile/v1760723397/PARACORD_KNIFE-Scorched_qbbtwu.webp",
    "correct_answer": "PARACORD KNIFE Scorched",
    "wrong_answers": [
      "URSUS KNIFE Scorched",
      "NOMAD KNIFE Scorched",
      "TALON KNIFE Scorched"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Qual é o nome desta faca?",
    "picture": "https://res.cloudinary.com/dwm53cbu2/image/upload/a_320/a_hflip/w_1000,f_auto,q_auto:low,fl_lossy,fl_progressive,fl_strip_profile/v1760723396/PARACORD_KNIFE-Marble_Fade_cw8y4i.webp",
    "correct_answer": "PARACORD KNIFE Marble Fade",
    "wrong_answers": [
      "URSUS KNIFE Marble Fade",
      "NAJAVA KNIFE Marble Fade",
      "TALON KNIFE Marble Fade"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Qual é o nome desta faca?",
    "picture": "https://res.cloudinary.com/dwm53cbu2/image/upload/a_320/a_hflip/w_1000,f_auto,q_auto:low,fl_lossy,fl_progressive,fl_strip_profile/v1760723394/URSUS_KNIFE-Doppler_Phase_3_d3veln.webp",
    "correct_answer": "URSUS KNIFE Doppler Phase 3",
    "wrong_answers": [
      "NAJAVA KNIFE Doppler Phase 3",
      "PARACORD KNIFE Doppler Phase 3",
      "TALON KNIFE Doppler Phase 3"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Qual é o nome desta faca?",
    "picture": "https://res.cloudinary.com/dwm53cbu2/image/upload/a_320/a_hflip/w_1000,f_auto,q_auto:low,fl_lossy,fl_progressive,fl_strip_profile/v1760723392/PARACORD_KNIFE-Fade_ojcuco.webp",
    "correct_answer": "PARACORD KNIFE Fade",
    "wrong_answers": [
      "NAJAVA KNIFE Fade",
      "URSUS KNIFE Fade",
      "TALON KNIFE Fade"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Qual é o nome desta faca?",
    "picture": "https://res.cloudinary.com/dwm53cbu2/image/upload/a_320/a_hflip/w_1000,f_auto,q_auto:low,fl_lossy,fl_progressive,fl_strip_profile/v1760723391/PARACORD_KNIFE-Doppler_Sapphire_pvppzt.webp",
    "correct_answer": "PARACORD KNIFE Doppler Sapphire",
    "wrong_answers": [
      "URSUS KNIFE Doppler Sapphire",
      "NAJAVA KNIFE Doppler Sapphire",
      "TALON KNIFE Doppler Sapphire"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Qual é o nome desta faca?",
    "picture": "https://res.cloudinary.com/dwm53cbu2/image/upload/a_320/a_hflip/w_1000,f_auto,q_auto:low,fl_lossy,fl_progressive,fl_strip_profile/v1760723389/PARACORD_KNIFE-Doppler_Phase_4_in7cof.webp",
    "correct_answer": "PARACORD KNIFE Doppler Phase 4",
    "wrong_answers": [
      "TALON KNIFE Doppler Phase 4",
      "URSUS KNIFE Doppler Phase 4",
      "NAJAVA KNIFE Doppler Phase 4"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Qual é o nome desta faca?",
    "picture": "https://res.cloudinary.com/dwm53cbu2/image/upload/a_320/a_hflip/w_1000,f_auto,q_auto:low,fl_lossy,fl_progressive,fl_strip_profile/v1760723387/PARACORD_KNIFE-Doppler_Ruby_ss6na9.webp",
    "correct_answer": "PARACORD KNIFE Doppler Ruby",
    "wrong_answers": [
      "URSUS KNIFE Doppler Ruby",
      "NAJAVA KNIFE Doppler Ruby",
      "TALON KNIFE Doppler Ruby"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Qual é o nome desta faca?",
    "picture": "https://res.cloudinary.com/dwm53cbu2/image/upload/a_320/a_hflip/w_1000,f_auto,q_auto:low,fl_lossy,fl_progressive,fl_strip_profile/v1760723386/PARACORD_KNIFE-Doppler_Phase_2_gea7w5.webp",
    "correct_answer": "PARACORD KNIFE Doppler Phase 2",
    "wrong_answers": [
      "NAJAVA KNIFE Doppler Phase 2",
      "URSUS KNIFE Doppler Phase 2",
      "TALON KNIFE Doppler Phase 2"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Qual é o nome desta faca?",
    "picture": "https://res.cloudinary.com/dwm53cbu2/image/upload/a_320/a_hflip/w_1000,f_auto,q_auto:low,fl_lossy,fl_progressive,fl_strip_profile/v1760723383/NOMAD_KNIFE-Tiger_Tooth_flnkyl.webp",
    "correct_answer": "NOMAD KNIFE Tiger Tooth",
    "wrong_answers": [
      "URSUS KNIFE Tiger Tooth",
      "NAJAVA KNIFE Tiger Tooth",
      "PARACORD KNIFE Tiger Tooth"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Qual é o nome desta faca?",
    "picture": "https://res.cloudinary.com/dwm53cbu2/image/upload/a_320/a_hflip/w_1000,f_auto,q_auto:low,fl_lossy,fl_progressive,fl_strip_profile/v1760723382/GUT_KNIFE-Freehand_acmwdd.webp",
    "correct_answer": "GUT KNIFE Freehand",
    "wrong_answers": [
      "HUNTSMAN KNIFE Freehand",
      "FLIP KNIFE Freehand",
      "FALCHION KNIFE Freehand"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Qual é o nome desta faca?",
    "picture": "https://res.cloudinary.com/dwm53cbu2/image/upload/a_320/a_hflip/w_1000,f_auto,q_auto:low,fl_lossy,fl_progressive,fl_strip_profile/v1760723381/PARACORD_KNIFE-Doppler_Phase_3_tscytc.webp",
    "correct_answer": "PARACORD KNIFE Doppler Phase 3",
    "wrong_answers": [
      "NAJAVA KNIFE Doppler Phase 3",
      "URSUS KNIFE Doppler Phase 3",
      "TALON KNIFE Doppler Phase 3"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Qual é o nome desta faca?",
    "picture": "https://res.cloudinary.com/dwm53cbu2/image/upload/a_320/a_hflip/w_1000,f_auto,q_auto:low,fl_lossy,fl_progressive,fl_strip_profile/v1760723378/PARACORD_KNIFE-Doppler_Phase_1_ux28u9.webp",
    "correct_answer": "PARACORD KNIFE Doppler Phase 1",
    "wrong_answers": [
      "URSUS KNIFE Doppler Phase 1",
      "NAJAVA KNIFE Doppler Phase 1",
      "TALON KNIFE Doppler Phase 1"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Qual é o nome desta faca?",
    "picture": "https://res.cloudinary.com/dwm53cbu2/image/upload/a_320/a_hflip/w_1000,f_auto,q_auto:low,fl_lossy,fl_progressive,fl_strip_profile/v1760723376/NOMAD_KNIFE-Vanilla_rsmm5d.webp",
    "correct_answer": "NOMAD KNIFE Vanilla",
    "wrong_answers": [
      "URSUS KNIFE Vanilla",
      "PARACORD KNIFE Vanilla",
      "NAJAVA KNIFE Vanilla"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Qual é o nome desta faca?",
    "picture": "https://res.cloudinary.com/dwm53cbu2/image/upload/a_320/a_hflip/w_1000,f_auto,q_auto:low,fl_lossy,fl_progressive,fl_strip_profile/v1760723374/PARACORD_KNIFE-Damascus_Steel_xqwoub.webp",
    "correct_answer": "PARACORD KNIFE Damascus Steel",
    "wrong_answers": [
      "NAJAVA KNIFE Damascus Steel",
      "GUT KNIFE Damascus Steel",
      "URSUS KNIFE Damascus Steel"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Qual é o nome desta faca?",
    "picture": "https://res.cloudinary.com/dwm53cbu2/image/upload/a_320/a_hflip/w_1000,f_auto,q_auto:low,fl_lossy,fl_progressive,fl_strip_profile/v1760723372/PARACORD_KNIFE-Boreal_Forest_l4yiyd.webp",
    "correct_answer": "PARACORD KNIFE Boreal Forest",
    "wrong_answers": [
      "URSUS KNIFE Boreal Forest",
      "NOMAD KNIFE Boreal Forest",
      "TALON KNIFE Boreal Forest"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Qual é o nome desta faca?",
    "picture": "https://res.cloudinary.com/dwm53cbu2/image/upload/a_320/a_hflip/w_1000,f_auto,q_auto:low,fl_lossy,fl_progressive,fl_strip_profile/v1760723371/NOMAD_KNIFE-Doppler_Phase_2_yofgee.webp",
    "correct_answer": "NOMAD KNIFE Doppler Phase 2",
    "wrong_answers": [
      "NAJAVA KNIFE Doppler Phase 2",
      "URSUS KNIFE Doppler Phase 2",
      "TALON KNIFE Doppler Phase 2"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Qual é o nome desta faca?",
    "picture": "https://res.cloudinary.com/dwm53cbu2/image/upload/a_320/a_hflip/w_1000,f_auto,q_auto:low,fl_lossy,fl_progressive,fl_strip_profile/v1760723369/NOMAD_KNIFE-Doppler_Ruby_gtwiid.webp",
    "correct_answer": "NOMAD KNIFE Doppler Ruby",
    "wrong_answers": [
      "URSUS KNIFE Doppler Ruby",
      "NAJAVA KNIFE Doppler Ruby",
      "TALON KNIFE Doppler Ruby"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Qual é o nome desta faca?",
    "picture": "https://res.cloudinary.com/dwm53cbu2/image/upload/a_320/a_hflip/w_1000,f_auto,q_auto:low,fl_lossy,fl_progressive,fl_strip_profile/v1760723368/PARACORD_KNIFE-Case_Hardened_oolskl.webp",
    "correct_answer": "PARACORD KNIFE Case Hardened",
    "wrong_answers": [
      "NAJAVA KNIFE Case Hardened",
      "URSUS KNIFE Case Hardened",
      "TALON KNIFE Case Hardened"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Qual é o nome desta faca?",
    "picture": "https://res.cloudinary.com/dwm53cbu2/image/upload/a_320/a_hflip/w_1000,f_auto,q_auto:low,fl_lossy,fl_progressive,fl_strip_profile/v1760723366/NOMAD_KNIFE-Damascus_Steel_e6usc8.webp",
    "correct_answer": "NOMAD KNIFE Damascus Steel",
    "wrong_answers": [
      "NAJAVA KNIFE Damascus Steel",
      "GUT KNIFE Damascus Steel",
      "URSUS KNIFE Damascus Steel"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Qual é o nome desta faca?",
    "picture": "https://res.cloudinary.com/dwm53cbu2/image/upload/a_320/a_hflip/w_1000,f_auto,q_auto:low,fl_lossy,fl_progressive,fl_strip_profile/v1760723364/PARACORD_KNIFE-Crimson_Web_dljkzy.webp",
    "correct_answer": "PARACORD KNIFE Crimson Web",
    "wrong_answers": [
      "URSUS KNIFE Crimson Web",
      "HUNTSMAN KNIFE Crimson Web",
      "NOMAD KNIFE Crimson Web"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Qual é o nome desta faca?",
    "picture": "https://res.cloudinary.com/dwm53cbu2/image/upload/a_320/a_hflip/w_1000,f_auto,q_auto:low,fl_lossy,fl_progressive,fl_strip_profile/v1760723362/NAJAVA_KNIFE-Marble_Fade_sh7z8w.webp",
    "correct_answer": "NAJAVA KNIFE Marble Fade",
    "wrong_answers": [
      "URSUS KNIFE Marble Fade",
      "PARACORD KNIFE Marble Fade",
      "TALON KNIFE Marble Fade"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Qual é o nome desta faca?",
    "picture": "https://res.cloudinary.com/dwm53cbu2/image/upload/a_320/a_hflip/w_1000,f_auto,q_auto:low,fl_lossy,fl_progressive,fl_strip_profile/v1760723360/NOMAD_KNIFE-Scorched_ka1tfy.webp",
    "correct_answer": "NOMAD KNIFE Scorched",
    "wrong_answers": [
      "URSUS KNIFE Scorched",
      "PARACORD KNIFE Scorched",
      "TALON KNIFE Scorched"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Qual é o nome desta faca?",
    "picture": "https://res.cloudinary.com/dwm53cbu2/image/upload/a_320/a_hflip/w_1000,f_auto,q_auto:low,fl_lossy,fl_progressive,fl_strip_profile/v1760723358/NAJAVA_KNIFE-Doppler_Black_Pearl_o7fctn.webp",
    "correct_answer": "NAJAVA KNIFE Doppler Black Pearl",
    "wrong_answers": [
      "URSUS KNIFE Doppler Black Pearl",
      "TALON KNIFE Doppler Black Pearl",
      "PARACORD KNIFE Doppler Black Pearl"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Qual é o nome desta faca?",
    "picture": "https://res.cloudinary.com/dwm53cbu2/image/upload/a_320/a_hflip/w_1000,f_auto,q_auto:low,fl_lossy,fl_progressive,fl_strip_profile/v1760723356/NOMAD_KNIFE-Doppler_Sapphire_oraiqd.webp",
    "correct_answer": "NOMAD KNIFE Doppler Sapphire",
    "wrong_answers": [
      "URSUS KNIFE Doppler Sapphire",
      "NAJAVA KNIFE Doppler Sapphire",
      "TALON KNIFE Doppler Sapphire"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Qual é o nome desta faca?",
    "picture": "https://res.cloudinary.com/dwm53cbu2/image/upload/a_320/a_hflip/w_1000,f_auto,q_auto:low,fl_lossy,fl_progressive,fl_strip_profile/v1760723355/NAJAVA_KNIFE-Doppler_Phase_4_oueqjj.webp",
    "correct_answer": "NAJAVA KNIFE Doppler Phase 4",
    "wrong_answers": [
      "TALON KNIFE Doppler Phase 4",
      "URSUS KNIFE Doppler Phase 4",
      "PARACORD KNIFE Doppler Phase 4"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Qual é o nome desta faca?",
    "picture": "https://res.cloudinary.com/dwm53cbu2/image/upload/a_320/a_hflip/w_1000,f_auto,q_auto:low,fl_lossy,fl_progressive,fl_strip_profile/v1760723353/GUT_KNIFE-Autotronic_wjuzcr.webp",
    "correct_answer": "GUT KNIFE Autotronic",
    "wrong_answers": [
      "HUNTSMAN KNIFE Autotronic",
      "FALCHION KNIFE Autotronic",
      "FLIP KNIFE Autotronic"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Qual é o nome desta faca?",
    "picture": "https://res.cloudinary.com/dwm53cbu2/image/upload/a_320/a_hflip/w_1000,f_auto,q_auto:low,fl_lossy,fl_progressive,fl_strip_profile/v1760723351/URSUS_KNIFE-Stained_ajxdik.webp",
    "correct_answer": "URSUS KNIFE Stained",
    "wrong_answers": [
      "NAJAVA KNIFE Stained",
      "PARACORD KNIFE Stained",
      "TALON KNIFE Stained"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Qual é o nome desta faca?",
    "picture": "https://res.cloudinary.com/dwm53cbu2/image/upload/a_320/a_hflip/w_1000,f_auto,q_auto:low,fl_lossy,fl_progressive,fl_strip_profile/v1760723349/NOMAD_KNIFE-Case_Hardened_kpvjnu.webp",
    "correct_answer": "NOMAD KNIFE Case Hardened",
    "wrong_answers": [
      "NAJAVA KNIFE Case Hardened",
      "URSUS KNIFE Case Hardened",
      "TALON KNIFE Case Hardened"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Qual é o nome desta faca?",
    "picture": "https://res.cloudinary.com/dwm53cbu2/image/upload/a_320/a_hflip/w_1000,f_auto,q_auto:low,fl_lossy,fl_progressive,fl_strip_profile/v1760723348/TALON_KNIFE-Vanilla_angxbe.webp",
    "correct_answer": "TALON KNIFE Vanilla",
    "wrong_answers": [
      "URSUS KNIFE Vanilla",
      "PARACORD KNIFE Vanilla",
      "NAJAVA KNIFE Vanilla"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Qual é o nome desta faca?",
    "picture": "https://res.cloudinary.com/dwm53cbu2/image/upload/a_320/a_hflip/w_1000,f_auto,q_auto:low,fl_lossy,fl_progressive,fl_strip_profile/v1760723348/URSUS_KNIFE-Doppler_Black_Pearl_th3oxh.webp",
    "correct_answer": "URSUS KNIFE Doppler Black Pearl",
    "wrong_answers": [
      "NAJAVA KNIFE Doppler Black Pearl",
      "TALON KNIFE Doppler Black Pearl",
      "PARACORD KNIFE Doppler Black Pearl"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Qual é o nome desta faca?",
    "picture": "https://res.cloudinary.com/dwm53cbu2/image/upload/a_320/a_hflip/w_1000,f_auto,q_auto:low,fl_lossy,fl_progressive,fl_strip_profile/v1760723344/NAJAVA_KNIFE-Blue_Steel_trzh28.webp",
    "correct_answer": "NAJAVA KNIFE Blue Steel",
    "wrong_answers": [
      "URSUS KNIFE Blue Steel",
      "TALON KNIFE Blue Steel",
      "PARACORD KNIFE Blue Steel"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Qual é o nome desta faca?",
    "picture": "https://res.cloudinary.com/dwm53cbu2/image/upload/a_320/a_hflip/w_1000,f_auto,q_auto:low,fl_lossy,fl_progressive,fl_strip_profile/v1760723342/NAJAVA_KNIFE-Slaughter_u9anzr.webp",
    "correct_answer": "NAJAVA KNIFE Slaughter",
    "wrong_answers": [
      "URSUS KNIFE Slaughter",
      "PARACORD KNIFE Slaughter",
      "TALON KNIFE Slaughter"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Qual é o nome desta faca?",
    "picture": "https://res.cloudinary.com/dwm53cbu2/image/upload/a_320/a_hflip/w_1000,f_auto,q_auto:low,fl_lossy,fl_progressive,fl_strip_profile/v1760723341/URSUS_KNIFE-Blue_Steel_xmhuqf.webp",
    "correct_answer": "URSUS KNIFE Blue Steel",
    "wrong_answers": [
      "NAJAVA KNIFE Blue Steel",
      "TALON KNIFE Blue Steel",
      "PARACORD KNIFE Blue Steel"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Qual é o nome desta faca?",
    "picture": "https://res.cloudinary.com/dwm53cbu2/image/upload/a_320/a_hflip/w_1000,f_auto,q_auto:low,fl_lossy,fl_progressive,fl_strip_profile/v1760723338/TALON_KNIFE-Blue_Steel_jm08sf.webp",
    "correct_answer": "TALON KNIFE Blue Steel",
    "wrong_answers": [
      "NAJAVA KNIFE Blue Steel",
      "URSUS KNIFE Blue Steel",
      "PARACORD KNIFE Blue Steel"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Qual é o nome desta faca?",
    "picture": "https://res.cloudinary.com/dwm53cbu2/image/upload/a_320/a_hflip/w_1000,f_auto,q_auto:low,fl_lossy,fl_progressive,fl_strip_profile/v1760723337/TALON_KNIFE-Tiger_Tooth_znibub.webp",
    "correct_answer": "TALON KNIFE Tiger Tooth",
    "wrong_answers": [
      "URSUS KNIFE Tiger Tooth",
      "NAJAVA KNIFE Tiger Tooth",
      "PARACORD KNIFE Tiger Tooth"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Qual é o nome desta faca?",
    "picture": "https://res.cloudinary.com/dwm53cbu2/image/upload/a_320/a_hflip/w_1000,f_auto,q_auto:low,fl_lossy,fl_progressive,fl_strip_profile/v1760723336/TALON_KNIFE-Fade_jonsrf.webp",
    "correct_answer": "TALON KNIFE Fade",
    "wrong_answers": [
      "NAJAVA KNIFE Fade",
      "URSUS KNIFE Fade",
      "PARACORD KNIFE Fade"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Qual é o nome desta faca?",
    "picture": "https://res.cloudinary.com/dwm53cbu2/image/upload/a_320/a_hflip/w_1000,f_auto,q_auto:low,fl_lossy,fl_progressive,fl_strip_profile/v1760723333/TALON_KNIFE-Stained_qr1t8p.webp",
    "correct_answer": "TALON KNIFE Stained",
    "wrong_answers": [
      "NAJAVA KNIFE Stained",
      "PARACORD KNIFE Stained",
      "URSUS KNIFE Stained"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Qual é o nome desta faca?",
    "picture": "https://res.cloudinary.com/dwm53cbu2/image/upload/a_320/a_hflip/w_1000,f_auto,q_auto:low,fl_lossy,fl_progressive,fl_strip_profile/v1760723332/TALON_KNIFE-Marble_Fade_ikdgr5.webp",
    "correct_answer": "TALON KNIFE Marble Fade",
    "wrong_answers": [
      "URSUS KNIFE Marble Fade",
      "PARACORD KNIFE Marble Fade",
      "NAJAVA KNIFE Marble Fade"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Qual é o nome desta faca?",
    "picture": "https://res.cloudinary.com/dwm53cbu2/image/upload/a_320/a_hflip/w_1000,f_auto,q_auto:low,fl_lossy,fl_progressive,fl_strip_profile/v1760723329/URSUS_KNIFE-Crimson_Web_aioeya.webp",
    "correct_answer": "URSUS KNIFE Crimson Web",
    "wrong_answers": [
      "PARACORD KNIFE Crimson Web",
      "HUNTSMAN KNIFE Crimson Web",
      "NOMAD KNIFE Crimson Web"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Qual é o nome desta faca?",
    "picture": "https://res.cloudinary.com/dwm53cbu2/image/upload/a_320/a_hflip/w_1000,f_auto,q_auto:low,fl_lossy,fl_progressive,fl_strip_profile/v1760723328/URSUS_KNIFE-Boreal_Forest_cxryuc.webp",
    "correct_answer": "URSUS KNIFE Boreal Forest",
    "wrong_answers": [
      "PARACORD KNIFE Boreal Forest",
      "NOMAD KNIFE Boreal Forest",
      "TALON KNIFE Boreal Forest"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Qual é o nome desta faca?",
    "picture": "https://res.cloudinary.com/dwm53cbu2/image/upload/a_320/a_hflip/w_1000,f_auto,q_auto:low,fl_lossy,fl_progressive,fl_strip_profile/v1760723326/TALON_KNIFE-Doppler_Phase_1_tv4swf.webp",
    "correct_answer": "TALON KNIFE Doppler Phase 1",
    "wrong_answers": [
      "URSUS KNIFE Doppler Phase 1",
      "NAJAVA KNIFE Doppler Phase 1",
      "PARACORD KNIFE Doppler Phase 1"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Qual é o nome desta faca?",
    "picture": "https://res.cloudinary.com/dwm53cbu2/image/upload/a_320/a_hflip/w_1000,f_auto,q_auto:low,fl_lossy,fl_progressive,fl_strip_profile/v1760723324/M9_BAYONET-Rust_Coat_uzrz1m.webp",
    "correct_answer": "M9 BAYONET Rust Coat",
    "wrong_answers": [
      "M9 BAYONET Lore",
      "M9 BAYONET Black Laminate",
      "M9 BAYONET Autotronic"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Qual é o nome desta faca?",
    "picture": "https://res.cloudinary.com/dwm53cbu2/image/upload/a_320/a_hflip/w_1000,f_auto,q_auto:low,fl_lossy,fl_progressive,fl_strip_profile/v1760723323/TALON_KNIFE-Slaughter_nrzh5y.webp",
    "correct_answer": "TALON KNIFE Slaughter",
    "wrong_answers": [
      "URSUS KNIFE Slaughter",
      "PARACORD KNIFE Slaughter",
      "NAJAVA KNIFE Slaughter"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Qual é o nome desta faca?",
    "picture": "https://res.cloudinary.com/dwm53cbu2/image/upload/a_320/a_hflip/w_1000,f_auto,q_auto:low,fl_lossy,fl_progressive,fl_strip_profile/v1760723320/TALON_KNIFE-Doppler_Black_Pearl_ahih6f.webp",
    "correct_answer": "TALON KNIFE Doppler Black Pearl",
    "wrong_answers": [
      "NAJAVA KNIFE Doppler Black Pearl",
      "URSUS KNIFE Doppler Black Pearl",
      "PARACORD KNIFE Doppler Black Pearl"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Qual é o nome desta faca?",
    "picture": "https://res.cloudinary.com/dwm53cbu2/image/upload/a_320/a_hflip/w_1000,f_auto,q_auto:low,fl_lossy,fl_progressive,fl_strip_profile/v1760723320/TALON_KNIFE-Doppler_Phase_3_s9ugej.webp",
    "correct_answer": "TALON KNIFE Doppler Phase 3",
    "wrong_answers": [
      "NAJAVA KNIFE Doppler Phase 3",
      "URSUS KNIFE Doppler Phase 3",
      "PARACORD KNIFE Doppler Phase 3"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Qual é o nome desta faca?",
    "picture": "https://res.cloudinary.com/dwm53cbu2/image/upload/a_320/a_hflip/w_1000,f_auto,q_auto:low,fl_lossy,fl_progressive,fl_strip_profile/v1760723317/STILETTO_KNIFE-Rust_Coat_y3ds7e.webp",
    "correct_answer": "STILETTO KNIFE Rust Coat",
    "wrong_answers": [
      "URSUS KNIFE Rust Coat",
      "PARACORD KNIFE Rust Coat",
      "NAJAVA KNIFE Rust Coat"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Qual é o nome desta faca?",
    "picture": "https://res.cloudinary.com/dwm53cbu2/image/upload/a_320/a_hflip/w_1000,f_auto,q_auto:low,fl_lossy,fl_progressive,fl_strip_profile/v1760723315/SHADOW_DAGGERS-Ultraviolet_ubf8sw.webp",
    "correct_answer": "SHADOW DAGGERS Ultraviolet",
    "wrong_answers": [
      "SHADOW DAGGERS Black Laminate",
      "SHADOW DAGGERS Rust Coat",
      "SHADOW DAGGERS Lore"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Qual é o nome desta faca?",
    "picture": "https://res.cloudinary.com/dwm53cbu2/image/upload/a_320/a_hflip/w_1000,f_auto,q_auto:low,fl_lossy,fl_progressive,fl_strip_profile/v1760723314/SHADOW_DAGGERS-Night_wdbuvy.webp",
    "correct_answer": "SHADOW DAGGERS Night",
    "wrong_answers": [
      "SHADOW DAGGERS Black Laminate",
      "SHADOW DAGGERS Rust Coat",
      "SHADOW DAGGERS Lore"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Qual é o nome desta faca?",
    "picture": "https://res.cloudinary.com/dwm53cbu2/image/upload/a_320/a_hflip/w_1000,f_auto,q_auto:low,fl_lossy,fl_progressive,fl_strip_profile/v1760723312/KARAMBIT-Forest_DDPAT_n0qn1m.webp",
    "correct_answer": "KARAMBIT Forest DDPAT",
    "wrong_answers": [
      "SKELETON Forest DDPAT",
      "BAYONET Forest DDPAT",
      "KARAMBIT Lore"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Qual é o nome desta faca?",
    "picture": "https://res.cloudinary.com/dwm53cbu2/image/upload/a_320/a_hflip/w_1000,f_auto,q_auto:low,fl_lossy,fl_progressive,fl_strip_profile/v1760723311/KARAMBIT-Blue_Steel_bckcca.webp",
    "correct_answer": "KARAMBIT Blue Steel",
    "wrong_answers": [
      "SKELETON Blue Steel",
      "BAYONET Blue Steel",
      "KARAMBIT Lore"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Qual é o nome desta faca?",
    "picture": "https://res.cloudinary.com/dwm53cbu2/image/upload/a_320/a_hflip/w_1000,f_auto,q_auto:low,fl_lossy,fl_progressive,fl_strip_profile/v1760723308/HUNTSMAN_KNIFE-Gamma_Doppler_Phase_1_lc1tih.webp",
    "correct_answer": "HUNTSMAN KNIFE Gamma Doppler Phase 1",
    "wrong_answers": [
      "GUT KNIFE Gamma Doppler Phase 1",
      "FALCHION KNIFE Gamma Doppler Phase 1",
      "FLIP KNIFE Gamma Doppler Phase 1"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Qual é o nome desta faca?",
    "picture": "https://res.cloudinary.com/dwm53cbu2/image/upload/a_320/a_hflip/w_1000,f_auto,q_auto:low,fl_lossy,fl_progressive,fl_strip_profile/v1760723307/SHADOW_DAGGERS-Fade_d31nbf.webp",
    "correct_answer": "SHADOW DAGGERS Fade",
    "wrong_answers": [
      "SHADOW DAGGERS Black Laminate",
      "SHADOW DAGGERS Rust Coat",
      "SHADOW DAGGERS Lore"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Qual é o nome desta faca?",
    "picture": "https://res.cloudinary.com/dwm53cbu2/image/upload/a_320/a_hflip/w_1000,f_auto,q_auto:low,fl_lossy,fl_progressive,fl_strip_profile/v1760723304/HUNTSMAN_KNIFE-Freehand_xei7lm.webp",
    "correct_answer": "HUNTSMAN KNIFE Freehand",
    "wrong_answers": [
      "GUT KNIFE Freehand",
      "FLIP KNIFE Freehand",
      "FALCHION KNIFE Freehand"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Qual é o nome desta faca?",
    "picture": "https://res.cloudinary.com/dwm53cbu2/image/upload/a_320/a_hflip/w_1000,f_auto,q_auto:low,fl_lossy,fl_progressive,fl_strip_profile/v1760723303/HUNTSMAN_KNIFE-Gamma_Doppler_Phase_3_ezq3gi.webp",
    "correct_answer": "HUNTSMAN KNIFE Gamma Doppler Phase 3",
    "wrong_answers": [
      "GUT KNIFE Gamma Doppler Phase 3",
      "FALCHION KNIFE Gamma Doppler Phase 3",
      "FLIP KNIFE Gamma Doppler Phase 3"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Qual é o nome desta faca?",
    "picture": "https://res.cloudinary.com/dwm53cbu2/image/upload/a_320/a_hflip/w_1000,f_auto,q_auto:low,fl_lossy,fl_progressive,fl_strip_profile/v1760723300/HUNTSMAN_KNIFE-Crimson_Web_dhsggi.webp",
    "correct_answer": "HUNTSMAN KNIFE Crimson Web",
    "wrong_answers": [
      "PARACORD KNIFE Crimson Web",
      "URSUS KNIFE Crimson Web",
      "NOMAD KNIFE Crimson Web"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Qual é o nome desta faca?",
    "picture": "https://res.cloudinary.com/dwm53cbu2/image/upload/a_320/a_hflip/w_1000,f_auto,q_auto:low,fl_lossy,fl_progressive,fl_strip_profile/v1760723299/HUNTSMAN_KNIFE-Autotronic_gh3vcm.webp",
    "correct_answer": "HUNTSMAN KNIFE Autotronic",
    "wrong_answers": [
      "GUT KNIFE Autotronic",
      "FALCHION KNIFE Autotronic",
      "FLIP KNIFE Autotronic"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Qual é o nome desta faca?",
    "picture": "https://res.cloudinary.com/dwm53cbu2/image/upload/a_320/a_hflip/w_1000,f_auto,q_auto:low,fl_lossy,fl_progressive,fl_strip_profile/v1760723298/GUT_KNIFE-Stained_gqgpzc.webp",
    "correct_answer": "GUT KNIFE Stained",
    "wrong_answers": [
      "NAJAVA KNIFE Stained",
      "PARACORD KNIFE Stained",
      "URSUS KNIFE Stained"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Qual é o nome desta faca?",
    "picture": "https://res.cloudinary.com/dwm53cbu2/image/upload/a_320/a_hflip/w_1000,f_auto,q_auto:low,fl_lossy,fl_progressive,fl_strip_profile/v1760723296/GUT_KNIFE-Vanilla_cgs5bo.webp",
    "correct_answer": "GUT KNIFE Vanilla",
    "wrong_answers": [
      "URSUS KNIFE Vanilla",
      "PARACORD KNIFE Vanilla",
      "NAJAVA KNIFE Vanilla"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Qual é o nome desta faca?",
    "picture": "https://res.cloudinary.com/dwm53cbu2/image/upload/a_320/a_hflip/w_1000,f_auto,q_auto:low,fl_lossy,fl_progressive,fl_strip_profile/v1760723293/GUT_KNIFE-Slaughter_szbysj.webp",
    "correct_answer": "GUT KNIFE Slaughter",
    "wrong_answers": [
      "URSUS KNIFE Slaughter",
      "PARACORD KNIFE Slaughter",
      "NAJAVA KNIFE Slaughter"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Qual é o nome desta faca?",
    "picture": "https://res.cloudinary.com/dwm53cbu2/image/upload/a_320/a_hflip/w_1000,f_auto,q_auto:low,fl_lossy,fl_progressive,fl_strip_profile/v1760723292/GUT_KNIFE-Tiger_Tooth_bthsn4.webp",
    "correct_answer": "GUT KNIFE Tiger Tooth",
    "wrong_answers": [
      "URSUS KNIFE Tiger Tooth",
      "NAJAVA KNIFE Tiger Tooth",
      "PARACORD KNIFE Tiger Tooth"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Qual é o nome desta faca?",
    "picture": "https://res.cloudinary.com/dwm53cbu2/image/upload/a_320/a_hflip/w_1000,f_auto,q_auto:low,fl_lossy,fl_progressive,fl_strip_profile/v1760723291/GUT_KNIFE-Gamma_Doppler_Phase_3_si5eta.webp",
    "correct_answer": "GUT KNIFE Gamma Doppler Phase 3",
    "wrong_answers": [
      "HUNTSMAN KNIFE Gamma Doppler Phase 3",
      "FALCHION KNIFE Gamma Doppler Phase 3",
      "FLIP KNIFE Gamma Doppler Phase 3"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Qual é o nome desta faca?",
    "picture": "https://res.cloudinary.com/dwm53cbu2/image/upload/a_320/a_hflip/w_1000,f_auto,q_auto:low,fl_lossy,fl_progressive,fl_strip_profile/v1760723289/PARACORD_KNIFE-Forest_DDPAT_abpcau.webp",
    "correct_answer": "PARACORD KNIFE Forest DDPAT",
    "wrong_answers": [
      "URSUS KNIFE Forest DDPAT",
      "TALON KNIFE Forest DDPAT",
      "GUT KNIFE Forest DDPAT"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Qual é o nome desta faca?",
    "picture": "https://res.cloudinary.com/dwm53cbu2/image/upload/a_320/a_hflip/w_1000,f_auto,q_auto:low,fl_lossy,fl_progressive,fl_strip_profile/v1760723288/PARACORD_KNIFE-Ultraviolet_sglud9.webp",
    "correct_answer": "PARACORD KNIFE Ultraviolet",
    "wrong_answers": [
      "NOMAD KNIFE Ultraviolet",
      "URSUS KNIFE Ultraviolet",
      "TALON KNIFE Ultraviolet"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Qual é o nome desta faca?",
    "picture": "https://res.cloudinary.com/dwm53cbu2/image/upload/a_320/a_hflip/w_1000,f_auto,q_auto:low,fl_lossy,fl_progressive,fl_strip_profile/v1760723286/GUT_KNIFE-Gamma_Doppler_Phase_4_uwbtth.webp",
    "correct_answer": "GUT KNIFE Gamma Doppler Phase 4",
    "wrong_answers": [
      "FLIP KNIFE Gamma Doppler Phase 4",
      "HUNTSMAN KNIFE Gamma Doppler Phase 4",
      "FALCHION KNIFE Gamma Doppler Phase 4"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Qual é o nome desta faca?",
    "picture": "https://res.cloudinary.com/dwm53cbu2/image/upload/a_320/a_hflip/w_1000,f_auto,q_auto:low,fl_lossy,fl_progressive,fl_strip_profile/v1760723283/GUT_KNIFE-Gamma_Doppler_Phase_2_rmmqaa.webp",
    "correct_answer": "GUT KNIFE Gamma Doppler Phase 2",
    "wrong_answers": [
      "FLIP KNIFE Gamma Doppler Phase 2",
      "HUNTSMAN KNIFE Gamma Doppler Phase 2",
      "FALCHION KNIFE Gamma Doppler Phase 2"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Qual é o nome desta faca?",
    "picture": "https://res.cloudinary.com/dwm53cbu2/image/upload/a_320/a_hflip/w_1000,f_auto,q_auto:low,fl_lossy,fl_progressive,fl_strip_profile/v1760723282/PARACORD_KNIFE-Safari_Mesh_ncln7f.webp",
    "correct_answer": "PARACORD KNIFE Safari Mesh",
    "wrong_answers": [
      "NOMAD KNIFE Safari Mesh",
      "URSUS KNIFE Safari Mesh",
      "TALON KNIFE Safari Mesh"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Qual é o nome desta faca?",
    "picture": "https://res.cloudinary.com/dwm53cbu2/image/upload/a_320/a_hflip/w_1000,f_auto,q_auto:low,fl_lossy,fl_progressive,fl_strip_profile/v1760723279/GUT_KNIFE-Gamma_Doppler_Phase_1_pnqnnh.webp",
    "correct_answer": "GUT KNIFE Gamma Doppler Phase 1",
    "wrong_answers": [
      "HUNTSMAN KNIFE Gamma Doppler Phase 1",
      "FALCHION KNIFE Gamma Doppler Phase 1",
      "FLIP KNIFE Gamma Doppler Phase 1"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Qual é o nome desta faca?",
    "picture": "https://res.cloudinary.com/dwm53cbu2/image/upload/a_320/a_hflip/w_1000,f_auto,q_auto:low,fl_lossy,fl_progressive,fl_strip_profile/v1760723277/GUT_KNIFE-Gamma_Doppler_Emerald_xoptfn.webp",
    "correct_answer": "GUT KNIFE Gamma Doppler Emerald",
    "wrong_answers": [
      "FLIP KNIFE Gamma Doppler Emerald",
      "HUNTSMAN KNIFE Gamma Doppler Emerald",
      "FALCHION KNIFE Gamma Doppler Emerald"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Qual é o nome desta faca?",
    "picture": "https://res.cloudinary.com/dwm53cbu2/image/upload/a_320/a_hflip/w_1000,f_auto,q_auto:low,fl_lossy,fl_progressive,fl_strip_profile/v1760723275/NOMAD_KNIFE-Stained_odmgxv.webp",
    "correct_answer": "NOMAD KNIFE Stained",
    "wrong_answers": [
      "NAJAVA KNIFE Stained",
      "PARACORD KNIFE Stained",
      "URSUS KNIFE Stained"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Qual é o nome desta faca?",
    "picture": "https://res.cloudinary.com/dwm53cbu2/image/upload/a_320/a_hflip/w_1000,f_auto,q_auto:low,fl_lossy,fl_progressive,fl_strip_profile/v1760723275/PARACORD_KNIFE-Doppler_Black_Pearl_oq7f9s.webp",
    "correct_answer": "PARACORD KNIFE Doppler Black Pearl",
    "wrong_answers": [
      "NAJAVA KNIFE Doppler Black Pearl",
      "URSUS KNIFE Doppler Black Pearl",
      "TALON KNIFE Doppler Black Pearl"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Qual é o nome desta faca?",
    "picture": "https://res.cloudinary.com/dwm53cbu2/image/upload/a_320/a_hflip/w_1000,f_auto,q_auto:low,fl_lossy,fl_progressive,fl_strip_profile/v1760723274/NOMAD_KNIFE-Ultraviolet_cvqyc2.webp",
    "correct_answer": "NOMAD KNIFE Ultraviolet",
    "wrong_answers": [
      "PARACORD KNIFE Ultraviolet",
      "URSUS KNIFE Ultraviolet",
      "TALON KNIFE Ultraviolet"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Qual é o nome desta faca?",
    "picture": "https://res.cloudinary.com/dwm53cbu2/image/upload/a_320/a_hflip/w_1000,f_auto,q_auto:low,fl_lossy,fl_progressive,fl_strip_profile/v1760723229/PARACORD_KNIFE-Blue_Steel_kbzolb.webp",
    "correct_answer": "PARACORD KNIFE Blue Steel",
    "wrong_answers": [
      "NAJAVA KNIFE Blue Steel",
      "URSUS KNIFE Blue Steel",
      "TALON KNIFE Blue Steel"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Qual é o nome desta faca?",
    "picture": "https://res.cloudinary.com/dwm53cbu2/image/upload/a_320/a_hflip/w_1000,f_auto,q_auto:low,fl_lossy,fl_progressive,fl_strip_profile/v1760723228/BOWIE_KNIFE-Rust_Coat_ajsip6.webp",
    "correct_answer": "BOWIE KNIFE Rust Coat",
    "wrong_answers": [
      "URSUS KNIFE Rust Coat",
      "PARACORD KNIFE Rust Coat",
      "NAJAVA KNIFE Rust Coat"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Qual é o nome desta faca?",
    "picture": "https://res.cloudinary.com/dwm53cbu2/image/upload/a_320/a_hflip/w_1000,f_auto,q_auto:low,fl_lossy,fl_progressive,fl_strip_profile/v1760723226/NOMAD_KNIFE-Safari_Mesh_lsbxry.webp",
    "correct_answer": "NOMAD KNIFE Safari Mesh",
    "wrong_answers": [
      "PARACORD KNIFE Safari Mesh",
      "URSUS KNIFE Safari Mesh",
      "TALON KNIFE Safari Mesh"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Qual é o nome desta faca?",
    "picture": "https://res.cloudinary.com/dwm53cbu2/image/upload/a_320/a_hflip/w_1000,f_auto,q_auto:low,fl_lossy,fl_progressive,fl_strip_profile/v1760723224/NOMAD_KNIFE-Urban_Masked_ne0k7c.webp",
    "correct_answer": "NOMAD KNIFE Urban Masked",
    "wrong_answers": [
      "PARACORD KNIFE Urban Masked",
      "URSUS KNIFE Urban Masked",
      "TALON KNIFE Urban Masked"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Qual é o nome desta faca?",
    "picture": "https://res.cloudinary.com/dwm53cbu2/image/upload/a_320/a_hflip/w_1000,f_auto,q_auto:low,fl_lossy,fl_progressive,fl_strip_profile/v1760723222/NOMAD_KNIFE-Night_Stripe_nkvj7y.webp",
    "correct_answer": "NOMAD KNIFE Night Stripe",
    "wrong_answers": [
      "URSUS KNIFE Night Stripe",
      "PARACORD KNIFE Night Stripe",
      "TALON KNIFE Night Stripe"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Qual é o nome desta faca?",
    "picture": "https://res.cloudinary.com/dwm53cbu2/image/upload/a_320/a_hflip/w_1000,f_auto,q_auto:low,fl_lossy,fl_progressive,fl_strip_profile/v1760723221/NOMAD_KNIFE-Boreal_Forest_zljigs.webp",
    "correct_answer": "NOMAD KNIFE Boreal Forest",
    "wrong_answers": [
      "PARACORD KNIFE Boreal Forest",
      "URSUS KNIFE Boreal Forest",
      "TALON KNIFE Boreal Forest"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Qual é o nome desta faca?",
    "picture": "https://res.cloudinary.com/dwm53cbu2/image/upload/a_320/a_hflip/w_1000,f_auto,q_auto:low,fl_lossy,fl_progressive,fl_strip_profile/v1760723218/NOMAD_KNIFE-Doppler_Black_Pearl_loefme.webp",
    "correct_answer": "NOMAD KNIFE Doppler Black Pearl",
    "wrong_answers": [
      "NAJAVA KNIFE Doppler Black Pearl",
      "URSUS KNIFE Doppler Black Pearl",
      "TALON KNIFE Doppler Black Pearl"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Qual é o nome desta faca?",
    "picture": "https://res.cloudinary.com/dwm53cbu2/image/upload/a_320/a_hflip/w_1000,f_auto,q_auto:low,fl_lossy,fl_progressive,fl_strip_profile/v1760723217/GUT_KNIFE-Doppler_Sapphire_g3ot02.webp",
    "correct_answer": "GUT KNIFE Doppler Sapphire",
    "wrong_answers": [
      "URSUS KNIFE Doppler Sapphire",
      "NAJAVA KNIFE Doppler Sapphire",
      "TALON KNIFE Doppler Sapphire"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Qual é o nome desta faca?",
    "picture": "https://res.cloudinary.com/dwm53cbu2/image/upload/a_320/a_hflip/w_1000,f_auto,q_auto:low,fl_lossy,fl_progressive,fl_strip_profile/v1760723216/NOMAD_KNIFE-Crimson_Web_m2pnsf.webp",
    "correct_answer": "NOMAD KNIFE Crimson Web",
    "wrong_answers": [
      "PARACORD KNIFE Crimson Web",
      "URSUS KNIFE Crimson Web",
      "HUNTSMAN KNIFE Crimson Web"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Qual é o nome desta faca?",
    "picture": "https://res.cloudinary.com/dwm53cbu2/image/upload/a_320/a_hflip/w_1000,f_auto,q_auto:low,fl_lossy,fl_progressive,fl_strip_profile/v1760723213/NOMAD_KNIFE-Marble_Fade_qobrcq.webp",
    "correct_answer": "NOMAD KNIFE Marble Fade",
    "wrong_answers": [
      "URSUS KNIFE Marble Fade",
      "PARACORD KNIFE Marble Fade",
      "NAJAVA KNIFE Marble Fade"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Qual é o nome desta faca?",
    "picture": "https://res.cloudinary.com/dwm53cbu2/image/upload/a_320/a_hflip/w_1000,f_auto,q_auto:low,fl_lossy,fl_progressive,fl_strip_profile/v1760723211/NOMAD_KNIFE-Slaughter_ixjhqc.webp",
    "correct_answer": "NOMAD KNIFE Slaughter",
    "wrong_answers": [
      "URSUS KNIFE Slaughter",
      "PARACORD KNIFE Slaughter",
      "NAJAVA KNIFE Slaughter"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Qual é o nome desta faca?",
    "picture": "https://res.cloudinary.com/dwm53cbu2/image/upload/a_320/a_hflip/w_1000,f_auto,q_auto:low,fl_lossy,fl_progressive,fl_strip_profile/v1760723210/GUT_KNIFE-Fade_wnhm7b.webp",
    "correct_answer": "GUT KNIFE Fade",
    "wrong_answers": [
      "NAJAVA KNIFE Fade",
      "URSUS KNIFE Fade",
      "PARACORD KNIFE Fade"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Qual é o nome desta faca?",
    "picture": "https://res.cloudinary.com/dwm53cbu2/image/upload/a_320/a_hflip/w_1000,f_auto,q_auto:low,fl_lossy,fl_progressive,fl_strip_profile/v1760723207/GUT_KNIFE-Doppler_Phase_2_c8zgpj.webp",
    "correct_answer": "GUT KNIFE Doppler Phase 2",
    "wrong_answers": [
      "NAJAVA KNIFE Doppler Phase 2",
      "URSUS KNIFE Doppler Phase 2",
      "TALON KNIFE Doppler Phase 2"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Qual é o nome desta faca?",
    "picture": "https://res.cloudinary.com/dwm53cbu2/image/upload/a_320/a_hflip/w_1000,f_auto,q_auto:low,fl_lossy,fl_progressive,fl_strip_profile/v1760723206/GUT_KNIFE-Doppler_Phase_1_ayy0in.webp",
    "correct_answer": "GUT KNIFE Doppler Phase 1",
    "wrong_answers": [
      "URSUS KNIFE Doppler Phase 1",
      "NAJAVA KNIFE Doppler Phase 1",
      "PARACORD KNIFE Doppler Phase 1"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Qual é o nome desta faca?",
    "picture": "https://res.cloudinary.com/dwm53cbu2/image/upload/a_320/a_hflip/w_1000,f_auto,q_auto:low,fl_lossy,fl_progressive,fl_strip_profile/v1760723205/NOMAD_KNIFE-Doppler_Fase_3_s14qsp.webp",
    "correct_answer": "NOMAD KNIFE Doppler Fase 3",
    "wrong_answers": [
      "NOMAD KNIFE Rust Coat",
      "NOMAD KNIFE Tiger Tooth",
      "NOMAD KNIFE Vanilla"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Qual é o nome desta faca?",
    "picture": "https://res.cloudinary.com/dwm53cbu2/image/upload/a_320/a_hflip/w_1000,f_auto,q_auto:low,fl_lossy,fl_progressive,fl_strip_profile/v1760722263/NOMAD_KNIFE-Doppler_Phase_4_ho461m.webp",
    "correct_answer": "NOMAD KNIFE Doppler Phase 4",
    "wrong_answers": [
      "TALON KNIFE Doppler Phase 4",
      "URSUS KNIFE Doppler Phase 4",
      "PARACORD KNIFE Doppler Phase 4"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Qual é o nome desta faca?",
    "picture": "https://res.cloudinary.com/dwm53cbu2/image/upload/a_320/a_hflip/w_1000,f_auto,q_auto:low,fl_lossy,fl_progressive,fl_strip_profile/v1760720997/GUT_KNIFE-Doppler_Phase_4_bh9ghn.webp",
    "correct_answer": "GUT KNIFE Doppler Phase 4",
    "wrong_answers": [
      "TALON KNIFE Doppler Phase 4",
      "URSUS KNIFE Doppler Phase 4",
      "PARACORD KNIFE Doppler Phase 4"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Qual é o nome desta faca?",
    "picture": "https://res.cloudinary.com/dwm53cbu2/image/upload/a_320/a_hflip/w_1000,f_auto,q_auto:low,fl_lossy,fl_progressive,fl_strip_profile/v1760720994/GUT_KNIFE-Doppler_Ruby_f7btpn.webp",
    "correct_answer": "GUT KNIFE Doppler Ruby",
    "wrong_answers": [
      "URSUS KNIFE Doppler Ruby",
      "NAJAVA KNIFE Doppler Ruby",
      "TALON KNIFE Doppler Ruby"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Qual é o nome desta faca?",
    "picture": "https://res.cloudinary.com/dwm53cbu2/image/upload/a_320/a_hflip/w_1000,f_auto,q_auto:low,fl_lossy,fl_progressive,fl_strip_profile/v1760720964/NOMAD_KNIFE-Fade_yorjab.webp",
    "correct_answer": "NOMAD KNIFE Fade",
    "wrong_answers": [
      "NAJAVA KNIFE Fade",
      "URSUS KNIFE Fade",
      "PARACORD KNIFE Fade"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Qual é o nome desta faca?",
    "picture": "https://res.cloudinary.com/dwm53cbu2/image/upload/a_320/a_hflip/w_1000,f_auto,q_auto:low,fl_lossy,fl_progressive,fl_strip_profile/v1760720962/URSUS_KNIFE-Urban_Masked_as61sj.webp",
    "correct_answer": "URSUS KNIFE Urban Masked",
    "wrong_answers": [
      "PARACORD KNIFE Urban Masked",
      "NOMAD KNIFE Urban Masked",
      "TALON KNIFE Urban Masked"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Qual é o nome desta faca?",
    "picture": "https://res.cloudinary.com/dwm53cbu2/image/upload/a_320/a_hflip/w_1000,f_auto,q_auto:low,fl_lossy,fl_progressive,fl_strip_profile/v1760720960/NOMAD_KNIFE-Blue_Steel_fsfnsx.webp",
    "correct_answer": "NOMAD KNIFE Blue Steel",
    "wrong_answers": [
      "NAJAVA KNIFE Blue Steel",
      "URSUS KNIFE Blue Steel",
      "TALON KNIFE Blue Steel"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Qual é o nome desta faca?",
    "picture": "https://res.cloudinary.com/dwm53cbu2/image/upload/a_320/a_hflip/w_1000,f_auto,q_auto:low,fl_lossy,fl_progressive,fl_strip_profile/v1760720958/BUTTERFLY_KNIFE-Rust_Coat_q6t7sr.webp",
    "correct_answer": "BUTTERFLY KNIFE Rust Coat",
    "wrong_answers": [
      "URSUS KNIFE Rust Coat",
      "PARACORD KNIFE Rust Coat",
      "NAJAVA KNIFE Rust Coat"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Qual é o nome desta faca?",
    "picture": "https://res.cloudinary.com/dwm53cbu2/image/upload/a_320/a_hflip/w_1000,f_auto,q_auto:low,fl_lossy,fl_progressive,fl_strip_profile/v1760720957/GUT_KNIFE-Case_Hardened_x9hmqb.webp",
    "correct_answer": "GUT KNIFE Case Hardened",
    "wrong_answers": [
      "NAJAVA KNIFE Case Hardened",
      "URSUS KNIFE Case Hardened",
      "TALON KNIFE Case Hardened"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Qual é o nome desta faca?",
    "picture": "https://res.cloudinary.com/dwm53cbu2/image/upload/a_320/a_hflip/w_1000,f_auto,q_auto:low,fl_lossy,fl_progressive,fl_strip_profile/v1760720955/FLIP_KNIFE-Rust_Coat_q0nzz5.webp",
    "correct_answer": "FLIP KNIFE Rust Coat",
    "wrong_answers": [
      "URSUS KNIFE Rust Coat",
      "PARACORD KNIFE Rust Coat",
      "NAJAVA KNIFE Rust Coat"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Qual é o nome desta faca?",
    "picture": "https://res.cloudinary.com/dwm53cbu2/image/upload/a_320/a_hflip/w_1000,f_auto,q_auto:low,fl_lossy,fl_progressive,fl_strip_profile/v1760720953/URSUS_KNIFE-Safari_Mesh_y4z3cr.webp",
    "correct_answer": "URSUS KNIFE Safari Mesh",
    "wrong_answers": [
      "PARACORD KNIFE Safari Mesh",
      "NOMAD KNIFE Safari Mesh",
      "TALON KNIFE Safari Mesh"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Qual é o nome desta faca?",
    "picture": "https://res.cloudinary.com/dwm53cbu2/image/upload/a_320/a_hflip/w_1000,f_auto,q_auto:low,fl_lossy,fl_progressive,fl_strip_profile/v1760720951/URSUS_KNIFE-Ultraviolet_stno1w.webp",
    "correct_answer": "URSUS KNIFE Ultraviolet",
    "wrong_answers": [
      "PARACORD KNIFE Ultraviolet",
      "NOMAD KNIFE Ultraviolet",
      "TALON KNIFE Ultraviolet"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Qual é o nome desta faca?",
    "picture": "https://res.cloudinary.com/dwm53cbu2/image/upload/a_320/a_hflip/w_1000,f_auto,q_auto:low,fl_lossy,fl_progressive,fl_strip_profile/v1760720950/FLIP_KNIFE-Gamma_Doppler_Phase_4_gnlnbl.webp",
    "correct_answer": "FLIP KNIFE Gamma Doppler Phase 4",
    "wrong_answers": [
      "GUT KNIFE Gamma Doppler Phase 4",
      "HUNTSMAN KNIFE Gamma Doppler Phase 4",
      "FALCHION KNIFE Gamma Doppler Phase 4"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Qual é o nome desta faca?",
    "picture": "https://res.cloudinary.com/dwm53cbu2/image/upload/a_320/a_hflip/w_1000,f_auto,q_auto:low,fl_lossy,fl_progressive,fl_strip_profile/v1760720948/URSUS_KNIFE-Night_Stripe_pockrr.webp",
    "correct_answer": "URSUS KNIFE Night Stripe",
    "wrong_answers": [
      "NOMAD KNIFE Night Stripe",
      "PARACORD KNIFE Night Stripe",
      "TALON KNIFE Night Stripe"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Qual é o nome desta faca?",
    "picture": "https://res.cloudinary.com/dwm53cbu2/image/upload/a_320/a_hflip/w_1000,f_auto,q_auto:low,fl_lossy,fl_progressive,fl_strip_profile/v1760720946/KARAMBIT-Urban_Masked_hp1mke.webp",
    "correct_answer": "KARAMBIT Urban Masked",
    "wrong_answers": [
      "SKELETON Urban Masked",
      "BAYONET Urban Masked",
      "KARAMBIT Lore"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Qual é o nome desta faca?",
    "picture": "https://res.cloudinary.com/dwm53cbu2/image/upload/a_320/a_hflip/w_1000,f_auto,q_auto:low,fl_lossy,fl_progressive,fl_strip_profile/v1760720945/M9_BAYONET-Freehand_wcct0d.webp",
    "correct_answer": "M9 BAYONET Freehand",
    "wrong_answers": [
      "M9 BAYONET Lore",
      "M9 BAYONET Black Laminate",
      "M9 BAYONET Autotronic"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Qual é o nome desta faca?",
    "picture": "https://res.cloudinary.com/dwm53cbu2/image/upload/a_320/a_hflip/w_1000,f_auto,q_auto:low,fl_lossy,fl_progressive,fl_strip_profile/v1760720942/FLIP_KNIFE-Gamma_Doppler_Emerald_vtvshv.webp",
    "correct_answer": "FLIP KNIFE Gamma Doppler Emerald",
    "wrong_answers": [
      "GUT KNIFE Gamma Doppler Emerald",
      "HUNTSMAN KNIFE Gamma Doppler Emerald",
      "FALCHION KNIFE Gamma Doppler Emerald"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Qual é o nome desta faca?",
    "picture": "https://res.cloudinary.com/dwm53cbu2/image/upload/a_320/a_hflip/w_1000,f_auto,q_auto:low,fl_lossy,fl_progressive,fl_strip_profile/v1760720941/M9_BAYONET-Gamma_Doppler_Emerald_iwcp9b.webp",
    "correct_answer": "M9 BAYONET Gamma Doppler Emerald",
    "wrong_answers": [
      "M9 BAYONET Lore",
      "M9 BAYONET Black Laminate",
      "M9 BAYONET Autotronic"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Qual é o nome desta faca?",
    "picture": "https://res.cloudinary.com/dwm53cbu2/image/upload/a_320/a_hflip/w_1000,f_auto,q_auto:low,fl_lossy,fl_progressive,fl_strip_profile/v1760720939/FLIP_KNIFE-Gamma_Doppler_Phase_2_qakpav.webp",
    "correct_answer": "FLIP KNIFE Gamma Doppler Phase 2",
    "wrong_answers": [
      "GUT KNIFE Gamma Doppler Phase 2",
      "HUNTSMAN KNIFE Gamma Doppler Phase 2",
      "FALCHION KNIFE Gamma Doppler Phase 2"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Qual é o nome desta faca?",
    "picture": "https://res.cloudinary.com/dwm53cbu2/image/upload/a_320/a_hflip/w_1000,f_auto,q_auto:low,fl_lossy,fl_progressive,fl_strip_profile/v1760720937/URSUS_KNIFE-Forest_DDPAT_jztful.webp",
    "correct_answer": "URSUS KNIFE Forest DDPAT",
    "wrong_answers": [
      "PARACORD KNIFE Forest DDPAT",
      "TALON KNIFE Forest DDPAT",
      "GUT KNIFE Forest DDPAT"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Qual é o nome desta faca?",
    "picture": "https://res.cloudinary.com/dwm53cbu2/image/upload/a_320/a_hflip/w_1000,f_auto,q_auto:low,fl_lossy,fl_progressive,fl_strip_profile/v1760720936/FLIP_KNIFE-Freehand_ju4rdn.webp",
    "correct_answer": "FLIP KNIFE Freehand",
    "wrong_answers": [
      "GUT KNIFE Freehand",
      "HUNTSMAN KNIFE Freehand",
      "FALCHION KNIFE Freehand"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Qual é o nome desta faca?",
    "picture": "https://res.cloudinary.com/dwm53cbu2/image/upload/a_320/a_hflip/w_1000,f_auto,q_auto:low,fl_lossy,fl_progressive,fl_strip_profile/v1760720933/TALON_KNIFE-Urban_Masked_ukoa0l.webp",
    "correct_answer": "TALON KNIFE Urban Masked",
    "wrong_answers": [
      "PARACORD KNIFE Urban Masked",
      "NOMAD KNIFE Urban Masked",
      "URSUS KNIFE Urban Masked"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Qual é o nome desta faca?",
    "picture": "https://res.cloudinary.com/dwm53cbu2/image/upload/a_320/a_hflip/w_1000,f_auto,q_auto:low,fl_lossy,fl_progressive,fl_strip_profile/v1760720932/TALON_KNIFE-Ultraviolet_s1ffh3.webp",
    "correct_answer": "TALON KNIFE Ultraviolet",
    "wrong_answers": [
      "PARACORD KNIFE Ultraviolet",
      "NOMAD KNIFE Ultraviolet",
      "URSUS KNIFE Ultraviolet"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Qual é o nome desta faca?",
    "picture": "https://res.cloudinary.com/dwm53cbu2/image/upload/a_320/a_hflip/w_1000,f_auto,q_auto:low,fl_lossy,fl_progressive,fl_strip_profile/v1760720930/FLIP_KNIFE-Black_Laminate_iagy2m.webp",
    "correct_answer": "FLIP KNIFE Black Laminate",
    "wrong_answers": [
      "HUNTSMAN KNIFE Black Laminate",
      "GUT KNIFE Black Laminate",
      "FALCHION KNIFE Black Laminate"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Qual é o nome desta faca?",
    "picture": "https://res.cloudinary.com/dwm53cbu2/image/upload/a_320/a_hflip/w_1000,f_auto,q_auto:low,fl_lossy,fl_progressive,fl_strip_profile/v1760720929/TALON_KNIFE-Scorched_gcozlk.webp",
    "correct_answer": "TALON KNIFE Scorched",
    "wrong_answers": [
      "URSUS KNIFE Scorched",
      "PARACORD KNIFE Scorched",
      "NOMAD KNIFE Scorched"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Qual é o nome desta faca?",
    "picture": "https://res.cloudinary.com/dwm53cbu2/image/upload/a_320/a_hflip/w_1000,f_auto,q_auto:low,fl_lossy,fl_progressive,fl_strip_profile/v1760720927/KARAMBIT-Crimson_Web_crrseo.webp",
    "correct_answer": "KARAMBIT Crimson Web",
    "wrong_answers": [
      "SKELETON Crimson Web",
      "BAYONET Crimson Web",
      "KARAMBIT Lore"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Qual é o nome desta faca?",
    "picture": "https://res.cloudinary.com/dwm53cbu2/image/upload/a_320/a_hflip/w_1000,f_auto,q_auto:low,fl_lossy,fl_progressive,fl_strip_profile/v1760720925/TALON_KNIFE-Forest_DDPAT_vjn4x1.webp",
    "correct_answer": "TALON KNIFE Forest DDPAT",
    "wrong_answers": [
      "PARACORD KNIFE Forest DDPAT",
      "URSUS KNIFE Forest DDPAT",
      "GUT KNIFE Forest DDPAT"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Qual é o nome desta faca?",
    "picture": "https://res.cloudinary.com/dwm53cbu2/image/upload/a_320/a_hflip/w_1000,f_auto,q_auto:low,fl_lossy,fl_progressive,fl_strip_profile/v1760720923/KARAMBIT-Bright_Water_b3tj56.webp",
    "correct_answer": "KARAMBIT Bright Water",
    "wrong_answers": [
      "BAYONET Bright Water",
      "KARAMBIT Lore",
      "KARAMBIT Black Laminate"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Qual é o nome desta faca?",
    "picture": "https://res.cloudinary.com/dwm53cbu2/image/upload/a_320/a_hflip/w_1000,f_auto,q_auto:low,fl_lossy,fl_progressive,fl_strip_profile/v1760720922/KARAMBIT-Boreal_Forest_u19yyy.webp",
    "correct_answer": "KARAMBIT Boreal Forest",
    "wrong_answers": [
      "SKELETON Boreal Forest",
      "BAYONET Boreal Forest",
      "KARAMBIT Lore"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Qual é o nome desta faca?",
    "picture": "https://res.cloudinary.com/dwm53cbu2/image/upload/a_320/a_hflip/w_1000,f_auto,q_auto:low,fl_lossy,fl_progressive,fl_strip_profile/v1760720920/TALON_KNIFE-Crimson_Web_iu98et.webp",
    "correct_answer": "TALON KNIFE Crimson Web",
    "wrong_answers": [
      "PARACORD KNIFE Crimson Web",
      "URSUS KNIFE Crimson Web",
      "HUNTSMAN KNIFE Crimson Web"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Qual é o nome desta faca?",
    "picture": "https://res.cloudinary.com/dwm53cbu2/image/upload/a_320/a_hflip/w_1000,f_auto,q_auto:low,fl_lossy,fl_progressive,fl_strip_profile/v1760720919/TALON_KNIFE-Safari_Mesh_oxb7up.webp",
    "correct_answer": "TALON KNIFE Safari Mesh",
    "wrong_answers": [
      "PARACORD KNIFE Safari Mesh",
      "NOMAD KNIFE Safari Mesh",
      "URSUS KNIFE Safari Mesh"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Qual é o nome desta faca?",
    "picture": "https://res.cloudinary.com/dwm53cbu2/image/upload/a_320/a_hflip/w_1000,f_auto,q_auto:low,fl_lossy,fl_progressive,fl_strip_profile/v1760720918/HUNTSMAN_KNIFE-Vanilla_hijmd2.webp",
    "correct_answer": "HUNTSMAN KNIFE Vanilla",
    "wrong_answers": [
      "URSUS KNIFE Vanilla",
      "PARACORD KNIFE Vanilla",
      "NAJAVA KNIFE Vanilla"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Qual é o nome desta faca?",
    "picture": "https://res.cloudinary.com/dwm53cbu2/image/upload/a_320/a_hflip/w_1000,f_auto,q_auto:low,fl_lossy,fl_progressive,fl_strip_profile/v1760720917/TALON_KNIFE-Boreal_Forest_fidghb.webp",
    "correct_answer": "TALON KNIFE Boreal Forest",
    "wrong_answers": [
      "PARACORD KNIFE Boreal Forest",
      "URSUS KNIFE Boreal Forest",
      "NOMAD KNIFE Boreal Forest"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Qual é o nome desta faca?",
    "picture": "https://res.cloudinary.com/dwm53cbu2/image/upload/a_320/a_hflip/w_1000,f_auto,q_auto:low,fl_lossy,fl_progressive,fl_strip_profile/v1760720915/SURVIVAL_KNIFE-Crimson_Web_kocrqd.webp",
    "correct_answer": "SURVIVAL KNIFE Crimson Web",
    "wrong_answers": [
      "PARACORD KNIFE Crimson Web",
      "URSUS KNIFE Crimson Web",
      "HUNTSMAN KNIFE Crimson Web"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Qual é o nome desta faca?",
    "picture": "https://res.cloudinary.com/dwm53cbu2/image/upload/a_320/a_hflip/w_1000,f_auto,q_auto:low,fl_lossy,fl_progressive,fl_strip_profile/v1760720914/HUNTSMAN_KNIFE-Boreal_Forest_w6rjoc.webp",
    "correct_answer": "HUNTSMAN KNIFE Boreal Forest",
    "wrong_answers": [
      "PARACORD KNIFE Boreal Forest",
      "URSUS KNIFE Boreal Forest",
      "NOMAD KNIFE Boreal Forest"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Qual é o nome desta faca?",
    "picture": "https://res.cloudinary.com/dwm53cbu2/image/upload/a_320/a_hflip/w_1000,f_auto,q_auto:low,fl_lossy,fl_progressive,fl_strip_profile/v1760720913/HUNTSMAN_KNIFE-Tiger_Tooth_skwdw2.webp",
    "correct_answer": "HUNTSMAN KNIFE Tiger Tooth",
    "wrong_answers": [
      "URSUS KNIFE Tiger Tooth",
      "NAJAVA KNIFE Tiger Tooth",
      "PARACORD KNIFE Tiger Tooth"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Qual é o nome desta faca?",
    "picture": "https://res.cloudinary.com/dwm53cbu2/image/upload/a_320/a_hflip/w_1000,f_auto,q_auto:low,fl_lossy,fl_progressive,fl_strip_profile/v1760720911/HUNTSMAN_KNIFE-Gamma_Doppler_Emerald_qqtdl0.webp",
    "correct_answer": "HUNTSMAN KNIFE Gamma Doppler Emerald",
    "wrong_answers": [
      "GUT KNIFE Gamma Doppler Emerald",
      "FLIP KNIFE Gamma Doppler Emerald",
      "FALCHION KNIFE Gamma Doppler Emerald"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Qual é o nome desta faca?",
    "picture": "https://res.cloudinary.com/dwm53cbu2/image/upload/a_320/a_hflip/w_1000,f_auto,q_auto:low,fl_lossy,fl_progressive,fl_strip_profile/v1760720906/HUNTSMAN_KNIFE-Gamma_Doppler_Phase_2_n6thch.webp",
    "correct_answer": "HUNTSMAN KNIFE Gamma Doppler Phase 2",
    "wrong_answers": [
      "GUT KNIFE Gamma Doppler Phase 2",
      "FLIP KNIFE Gamma Doppler Phase 2",
      "FALCHION KNIFE Gamma Doppler Phase 2"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Qual é o nome desta faca?",
    "picture": "https://res.cloudinary.com/dwm53cbu2/image/upload/a_320/a_hflip/w_1000,f_auto,q_auto:low,fl_lossy,fl_progressive,fl_strip_profile/v1760720905/STILETTO_KNIFE-Doppler_Ruby_i5paiy.webp",
    "correct_answer": "STILETTO KNIFE Doppler Ruby",
    "wrong_answers": [
      "URSUS KNIFE Doppler Ruby",
      "NAJAVA KNIFE Doppler Ruby",
      "TALON KNIFE Doppler Ruby"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Qual é o nome desta faca?",
    "picture": "https://res.cloudinary.com/dwm53cbu2/image/upload/a_320/a_hflip/w_1000,f_auto,q_auto:low,fl_lossy,fl_progressive,fl_strip_profile/v1760720904/HUNTSMAN_KNIFE-Doppler_Phase_1_zkrlab.webp",
    "correct_answer": "HUNTSMAN KNIFE Doppler Phase 1",
    "wrong_answers": [
      "URSUS KNIFE Doppler Phase 1",
      "NAJAVA KNIFE Doppler Phase 1",
      "PARACORD KNIFE Doppler Phase 1"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Qual é o nome desta faca?",
    "picture": "https://res.cloudinary.com/dwm53cbu2/image/upload/a_320/a_hflip/w_1000,f_auto,q_auto:low,fl_lossy,fl_progressive,fl_strip_profile/v1760720902/STILETTO_KNIFE-Doppler_Phase_2_km3i2d.webp",
    "correct_answer": "STILETTO KNIFE Doppler Phase 2",
    "wrong_answers": [
      "NAJAVA KNIFE Doppler Phase 2",
      "URSUS KNIFE Doppler Phase 2",
      "TALON KNIFE Doppler Phase 2"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Qual é o nome desta faca?",
    "picture": "https://res.cloudinary.com/dwm53cbu2/image/upload/a_320/a_hflip/w_1000,f_auto,q_auto:low,fl_lossy,fl_progressive,fl_strip_profile/v1760720901/HUNTSMAN_KNIFE-Doppler_Sapphire_c51sdo.webp",
    "correct_answer": "HUNTSMAN KNIFE Doppler Sapphire",
    "wrong_answers": [
      "URSUS KNIFE Doppler Sapphire",
      "NAJAVA KNIFE Doppler Sapphire",
      "TALON KNIFE Doppler Sapphire"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Qual é o nome desta faca?",
    "picture": "https://res.cloudinary.com/dwm53cbu2/image/upload/a_320/a_hflip/w_1000,f_auto,q_auto:low,fl_lossy,fl_progressive,fl_strip_profile/v1760720899/STILETTO_KNIFE-Case_Hardened_h7uauu.webp",
    "correct_answer": "STILETTO KNIFE Case Hardened",
    "wrong_answers": [
      "NAJAVA KNIFE Case Hardened",
      "URSUS KNIFE Case Hardened",
      "TALON KNIFE Case Hardened"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Qual é o nome desta faca?",
    "picture": "https://res.cloudinary.com/dwm53cbu2/image/upload/a_320/a_hflip/w_1000,f_auto,q_auto:low,fl_lossy,fl_progressive,fl_strip_profile/v1760720898/HUNTSMAN_KNIFE-Doppler_Ruby_fbhdru.webp",
    "correct_answer": "HUNTSMAN KNIFE Doppler Ruby",
    "wrong_answers": [
      "URSUS KNIFE Doppler Ruby",
      "NAJAVA KNIFE Doppler Ruby",
      "TALON KNIFE Doppler Ruby"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Qual é o nome desta faca?",
    "picture": "https://res.cloudinary.com/dwm53cbu2/image/upload/a_320/a_hflip/w_1000,f_auto,q_auto:low,fl_lossy,fl_progressive,fl_strip_profile/v1760720896/STILETTO_KNIFE-Doppler_Phase_1_m0vsyf.webp",
    "correct_answer": "STILETTO KNIFE Doppler Phase 1",
    "wrong_answers": [
      "URSUS KNIFE Doppler Phase 1",
      "NAJAVA KNIFE Doppler Phase 1",
      "PARACORD KNIFE Doppler Phase 1"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Qual é o nome desta faca?",
    "picture": "https://res.cloudinary.com/dwm53cbu2/image/upload/a_320/a_hflip/w_1000,f_auto,q_auto:low,fl_lossy,fl_progressive,fl_strip_profile/v1760720895/HUNTSMAN_KNIFE-Doppler_Phase_2_ofhvo5.webp",
    "correct_answer": "HUNTSMAN KNIFE Doppler Phase 2",
    "wrong_answers": [
      "NAJAVA KNIFE Doppler Phase 2",
      "URSUS KNIFE Doppler Phase 2",
      "TALON KNIFE Doppler Phase 2"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Qual é o nome desta faca?",
    "picture": "https://res.cloudinary.com/dwm53cbu2/image/upload/a_320/a_hflip/w_1000,f_auto,q_auto:low,fl_lossy,fl_progressive,fl_strip_profile/v1760720894/SKELETON-Vanilla_avxq11.webp",
    "correct_answer": "SKELETON Vanilla",
    "wrong_answers": [
      "KARAMBIT Vanilla",
      "BAYONET Vanilla",
      "SKELETON Rust Coat"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Qual é o nome desta faca?",
    "picture": "https://res.cloudinary.com/dwm53cbu2/image/upload/a_320/a_hflip/w_1000,f_auto,q_auto:low,fl_lossy,fl_progressive,fl_strip_profile/v1760720893/HUNTSMAN_KNIFE-Damascus_Steel_davmbb.webp",
    "correct_answer": "HUNTSMAN KNIFE Damascus Steel",
    "wrong_answers": [
      "NAJAVA KNIFE Damascus Steel",
      "GUT KNIFE Damascus Steel",
      "URSUS KNIFE Damascus Steel"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Qual é o nome desta faca?",
    "picture": "https://res.cloudinary.com/dwm53cbu2/image/upload/a_320/a_hflip/w_1000,f_auto,q_auto:low,fl_lossy,fl_progressive,fl_strip_profile/v1760720892/HUNTSMAN_KNIFE-Case_Hardened_vv7ygl.webp",
    "correct_answer": "HUNTSMAN KNIFE Case Hardened",
    "wrong_answers": [
      "NAJAVA KNIFE Case Hardened",
      "URSUS KNIFE Case Hardened",
      "TALON KNIFE Case Hardened"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Qual é o nome desta faca?",
    "picture": "https://res.cloudinary.com/dwm53cbu2/image/upload/a_320/a_hflip/w_1000,f_auto,q_auto:low,fl_lossy,fl_progressive,fl_strip_profile/v1760720890/SKELETON-Doppler_Ruby_a2h36c.webp",
    "correct_answer": "SKELETON Doppler Ruby",
    "wrong_answers": [
      "KARAMBIT Doppler Ruby",
      "SKELETON Doppler Phase 4",
      "SKELETON Doppler Sapphire"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Qual é o nome desta faca?",
    "picture": "https://res.cloudinary.com/dwm53cbu2/image/upload/a_320/a_hflip/w_1000,f_auto,q_auto:low,fl_lossy,fl_progressive,fl_strip_profile/v1760720889/HUNTSMAN_KNIFE-Bright_Water_zdhe90.webp",
    "correct_answer": "HUNTSMAN KNIFE Bright Water",
    "wrong_answers": [
      "GUT KNIFE Bright Water",
      "FLIP KNIFE Bright Water",
      "FALCHION KNIFE Bright Water"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Qual é o nome desta faca?",
    "picture": "https://res.cloudinary.com/dwm53cbu2/image/upload/a_320/a_hflip/w_1000,f_auto,q_auto:low,fl_lossy,fl_progressive,fl_strip_profile/v1760720888/HUNTSMAN_KNIFE-Gamma_Doppler_Phase_4_bcak44.webp",
    "correct_answer": "HUNTSMAN KNIFE Gamma Doppler Phase 4",
    "wrong_answers": [
      "GUT KNIFE Gamma Doppler Phase 4",
      "FLIP KNIFE Gamma Doppler Phase 4",
      "FALCHION KNIFE Gamma Doppler Phase 4"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Qual é o nome desta faca?",
    "picture": "https://res.cloudinary.com/dwm53cbu2/image/upload/a_320/a_hflip/w_1000,f_auto,q_auto:low,fl_lossy,fl_progressive,fl_strip_profile/v1760720887/SHADOW_DAGGERS-Scorched_q2br2s.webp",
    "correct_answer": "SHADOW DAGGERS Scorched",
    "wrong_answers": [
      "SHADOW DAGGERS Black Laminate",
      "SHADOW DAGGERS Rust Coat",
      "SHADOW DAGGERS Lore"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Qual é o nome desta faca?",
    "picture": "https://res.cloudinary.com/dwm53cbu2/image/upload/a_320/a_hflip/w_1000,f_auto,q_auto:low,fl_lossy,fl_progressive,fl_strip_profile/v1760720886/SHADOW_DAGGERS-Safari_Mesh_roqllt.webp",
    "correct_answer": "SHADOW DAGGERS Safari Mesh",
    "wrong_answers": [
      "SHADOW DAGGERS Black Laminate",
      "SHADOW DAGGERS Rust Coat",
      "SHADOW DAGGERS Lore"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Qual é o nome desta faca?",
    "picture": "https://res.cloudinary.com/dwm53cbu2/image/upload/a_320/a_hflip/w_1000,f_auto,q_auto:low,fl_lossy,fl_progressive,fl_strip_profile/v1760720884/GUT_KNIFE-Marble_Fade_vsiglw.webp",
    "correct_answer": "GUT KNIFE Marble Fade",
    "wrong_answers": [
      "URSUS KNIFE Marble Fade",
      "PARACORD KNIFE Marble Fade",
      "NAJAVA KNIFE Marble Fade"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Qual é o nome desta faca?",
    "picture": "https://res.cloudinary.com/dwm53cbu2/image/upload/a_320/a_hflip/w_1000,f_auto,q_auto:low,fl_lossy,fl_progressive,fl_strip_profile/v1760720883/FALCHION_KNIFE-Autotronic_a8uhc2.webp",
    "correct_answer": "FALCHION KNIFE Autotronic",
    "wrong_answers": [
      "GUT KNIFE Autotronic",
      "HUNTSMAN KNIFE Autotronic",
      "FLIP KNIFE Autotronic"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Qual é o nome desta faca?",
    "picture": "https://res.cloudinary.com/dwm53cbu2/image/upload/a_320/a_hflip/w_1000,f_auto,q_auto:low,fl_lossy,fl_progressive,fl_strip_profile/v1760720882/PARACORD_KNIFE-Night_Stripe_anshpw.webp",
    "correct_answer": "PARACORD KNIFE Night Stripe",
    "wrong_answers": [
      "NOMAD KNIFE Night Stripe",
      "URSUS KNIFE Night Stripe",
      "TALON KNIFE Night Stripe"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Qual é o nome desta faca?",
    "picture": "https://res.cloudinary.com/dwm53cbu2/image/upload/a_320/a_hflip/w_1000,f_auto,q_auto:low,fl_lossy,fl_progressive,fl_strip_profile/v1760720881/GUT_KNIFE-Forest_DDPAT_zpv6o5.webp",
    "correct_answer": "GUT KNIFE Forest DDPAT",
    "wrong_answers": [
      "PARACORD KNIFE Forest DDPAT",
      "URSUS KNIFE Forest DDPAT",
      "TALON KNIFE Forest DDPAT"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Qual é o nome desta faca?",
    "picture": "https://res.cloudinary.com/dwm53cbu2/image/upload/a_320/a_hflip/w_1000,f_auto,q_auto:low,fl_lossy,fl_progressive,fl_strip_profile/v1760720880/GUT_KNIFE-Crimson_Web_t1ufcx.webp",
    "correct_answer": "GUT KNIFE Crimson Web",
    "wrong_answers": [
      "PARACORD KNIFE Crimson Web",
      "URSUS KNIFE Crimson Web",
      "HUNTSMAN KNIFE Crimson Web"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Qual é o nome desta faca?",
    "picture": "https://res.cloudinary.com/dwm53cbu2/image/upload/a_320/a_hflip/w_1000,f_auto,q_auto:low,fl_lossy,fl_progressive,fl_strip_profile/v1760720879/NOMAD_KNIFE-Forest_DDPAT_bt5h9r.webp",
    "correct_answer": "NOMAD KNIFE Forest DDPAT",
    "wrong_answers": [
      "PARACORD KNIFE Forest DDPAT",
      "URSUS KNIFE Forest DDPAT",
      "TALON KNIFE Forest DDPAT"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Qual é o nome desta faca?",
    "picture": "https://res.cloudinary.com/dwm53cbu2/image/upload/a_320/a_hflip/w_1000,f_auto,q_auto:low,fl_lossy,fl_progressive,fl_strip_profile/v1760720878/GUT_KNIFE-Doppler_Phase_3_of8klf.webp",
    "correct_answer": "GUT KNIFE Doppler Phase 3",
    "wrong_answers": [
      "NAJAVA KNIFE Doppler Phase 3",
      "URSUS KNIFE Doppler Phase 3",
      "PARACORD KNIFE Doppler Phase 3"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Qual é o nome desta faca?",
    "picture": "https://res.cloudinary.com/dwm53cbu2/image/upload/a_320/a_hflip/w_1000,f_auto,q_auto:low,fl_lossy,fl_progressive,fl_strip_profile/v1760720876/GUT_KNIFE-Blue_Steel_mls0zf.webp",
    "correct_answer": "GUT KNIFE Blue Steel",
    "wrong_answers": [
      "NAJAVA KNIFE Blue Steel",
      "URSUS KNIFE Blue Steel",
      "TALON KNIFE Blue Steel"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Qual é o nome desta faca?",
    "picture": "https://res.cloudinary.com/dwm53cbu2/image/upload/a_320/a_hflip/w_1000,f_auto,q_auto:low,fl_lossy,fl_progressive,fl_strip_profile/v1760720875/FLIP_KNIFE-Scorched_dwn2ze.webp",
    "correct_answer": "FLIP KNIFE Scorched",
    "wrong_answers": [
      "URSUS KNIFE Scorched",
      "PARACORD KNIFE Scorched",
      "NOMAD KNIFE Scorched"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Qual é o nome desta faca?",
    "picture": "https://res.cloudinary.com/dwm53cbu2/image/upload/a_320/a_hflip/w_1000,f_auto,q_auto:low,fl_lossy,fl_progressive,fl_strip_profile/v1760720874/GUT_KNIFE-Boreal_Forest_yn6tpa.webp",
    "correct_answer": "GUT KNIFE Boreal Forest",
    "wrong_answers": [
      "PARACORD KNIFE Boreal Forest",
      "URSUS KNIFE Boreal Forest",
      "NOMAD KNIFE Boreal Forest"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Qual é o nome desta faca?",
    "picture": "https://res.cloudinary.com/dwm53cbu2/image/upload/a_320/a_hflip/w_1000,f_auto,q_auto:low,fl_lossy,fl_progressive,fl_strip_profile/v1760720873/FLIP_KNIFE-Tiger_Tooth_oqrrpj.webp",
    "correct_answer": "FLIP KNIFE Tiger Tooth",
    "wrong_answers": [
      "URSUS KNIFE Tiger Tooth",
      "NAJAVA KNIFE Tiger Tooth",
      "PARACORD KNIFE Tiger Tooth"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Qual é o nome desta faca?",
    "picture": "https://res.cloudinary.com/dwm53cbu2/image/upload/a_320/a_hflip/w_1000,f_auto,q_auto:low,fl_lossy,fl_progressive,fl_strip_profile/v1760720871/GUT_KNIFE-Doppler_Black_Pearl_uusabf.webp",
    "correct_answer": "GUT KNIFE Doppler Black Pearl",
    "wrong_answers": [
      "NAJAVA KNIFE Doppler Black Pearl",
      "URSUS KNIFE Doppler Black Pearl",
      "TALON KNIFE Doppler Black Pearl"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Qual é o nome desta faca?",
    "picture": "https://res.cloudinary.com/dwm53cbu2/image/upload/a_320/a_hflip/w_1000,f_auto,q_auto:low,fl_lossy,fl_progressive,fl_strip_profile/v1760720870/FLIP_KNIFE-Safari_Mesh_dpkqrx.webp",
    "correct_answer": "FLIP KNIFE Safari Mesh",
    "wrong_answers": [
      "PARACORD KNIFE Safari Mesh",
      "NOMAD KNIFE Safari Mesh",
      "URSUS KNIFE Safari Mesh"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Qual é o nome desta faca?",
    "picture": "https://res.cloudinary.com/dwm53cbu2/image/upload/a_320/a_hflip/w_1000,f_auto,q_auto:low,fl_lossy,fl_progressive,fl_strip_profile/v1760720869/M9_BAYONET-Marble_Fade_hwieao.webp",
    "correct_answer": "M9 BAYONET Marble Fade",
    "wrong_answers": [
      "M9 BAYONET Lore",
      "M9 BAYONET Black Laminate",
      "M9 BAYONET Autotronic"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Qual é o nome desta faca?",
    "picture": "https://res.cloudinary.com/dwm53cbu2/image/upload/a_320/a_hflip/w_1000,f_auto,q_auto:low,fl_lossy,fl_progressive,fl_strip_profile/v1760720868/BUTTERFLY_KNIFE-Lore_k9wwrd.webp",
    "correct_answer": "BUTTERFLY KNIFE Lore",
    "wrong_answers": [
      "GUT KNIFE Lore",
      "FLIP KNIFE Lore",
      "HUNTSMAN KNIFE Lore"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Qual é o nome desta faca?",
    "picture": "https://res.cloudinary.com/dwm53cbu2/image/upload/a_320/a_hflip/w_1000,f_auto,q_auto:low,fl_lossy,fl_progressive,fl_strip_profile/v1760720867/M9_BAYONET-Slaughter_le2jwk.webp",
    "correct_answer": "M9 BAYONET Slaughter",
    "wrong_answers": [
      "M9 BAYONET Lore",
      "M9 BAYONET Black Laminate",
      "M9 BAYONET Autotronic"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Qual é o nome desta faca?",
    "picture": "https://res.cloudinary.com/dwm53cbu2/image/upload/a_320/a_hflip/w_1000,f_auto,q_auto:low,fl_lossy,fl_progressive,fl_strip_profile/v1760720866/M9_BAYONET-Vanilla_bxksdo.webp",
    "correct_answer": "M9 BAYONET Vanilla",
    "wrong_answers": [
      "M9 BAYONET Lore",
      "M9 BAYONET Black Laminate",
      "M9 BAYONET Autotronic"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Qual é o nome desta faca?",
    "picture": "https://res.cloudinary.com/dwm53cbu2/image/upload/a_320/a_hflip/w_1000,f_auto,q_auto:low,fl_lossy,fl_progressive,fl_strip_profile/v1760720864/M9_BAYONET-Stained_gy4xv2.webp",
    "correct_answer": "M9 BAYONET Stained",
    "wrong_answers": [
      "M9 BAYONET Lore",
      "M9 BAYONET Black Laminate",
      "M9 BAYONET Autotronic"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Qual é o nome desta faca?",
    "picture": "https://res.cloudinary.com/dwm53cbu2/image/upload/a_320/a_hflip/w_1000,f_auto,q_auto:low,fl_lossy,fl_progressive,fl_strip_profile/v1760720863/M9_BAYONET-Safari_Mesh_klbtxq.webp",
    "correct_answer": "M9 BAYONET Safari Mesh",
    "wrong_answers": [
      "M9 BAYONET Lore",
      "M9 BAYONET Black Laminate",
      "M9 BAYONET Autotronic"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Qual é o nome desta faca?",
    "picture": "https://res.cloudinary.com/dwm53cbu2/image/upload/a_320/a_hflip/w_1000,f_auto,q_auto:low,fl_lossy,fl_progressive,fl_strip_profile/v1760720862/M9_BAYONET-Scorched_xvm78a.webp",
    "correct_answer": "M9 BAYONET Scorched",
    "wrong_answers": [
      "M9 BAYONET Lore",
      "M9 BAYONET Black Laminate",
      "M9 BAYONET Autotronic"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Qual é o nome desta faca?",
    "picture": "https://res.cloudinary.com/dwm53cbu2/image/upload/a_320/a_hflip/w_1000,f_auto,q_auto:low,fl_lossy,fl_progressive,fl_strip_profile/v1760720861/M9_BAYONET-Tiger_Tooth_qltlzn.webp",
    "correct_answer": "M9 BAYONET Tiger Tooth",
    "wrong_answers": [
      "M9 BAYONET Lore",
      "M9 BAYONET Black Laminate",
      "M9 BAYONET Autotronic"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Qual é o nome desta faca?",
    "picture": "https://res.cloudinary.com/dwm53cbu2/image/upload/a_320/a_hflip/w_1000,f_auto,q_auto:low,fl_lossy,fl_progressive,fl_strip_profile/v1760720860/M9_BAYONET-Gamma_Doppler_Phase_3_cked7k.webp",
    "correct_answer": "M9 BAYONET Gamma Doppler Phase 3",
    "wrong_answers": [
      "M9 BAYONET Lore",
      "M9 BAYONET Black Laminate",
      "M9 BAYONET Autotronic"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Qual é o nome desta faca?",
    "picture": "https://res.cloudinary.com/dwm53cbu2/image/upload/a_320/a_hflip/w_1000,f_auto,q_auto:low,fl_lossy,fl_progressive,fl_strip_profile/v1760720858/M9_BAYONET-Fade_z4iatc.webp",
    "correct_answer": "M9 BAYONET Fade",
    "wrong_answers": [
      "M9 BAYONET Lore",
      "M9 BAYONET Black Laminate",
      "M9 BAYONET Autotronic"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Qual é o nome desta faca?",
    "picture": "https://res.cloudinary.com/dwm53cbu2/image/upload/a_320/a_hflip/w_1000,f_auto,q_auto:low,fl_lossy,fl_progressive,fl_strip_profile/v1760720858/M9_BAYONET-Gamma_Doppler_Phase_4_c7vslt.webp",
    "correct_answer": "M9 BAYONET Gamma Doppler Phase 4",
    "wrong_answers": [
      "M9 BAYONET Lore",
      "M9 BAYONET Black Laminate",
      "M9 BAYONET Autotronic"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Qual é o nome desta faca?",
    "picture": "https://res.cloudinary.com/dwm53cbu2/image/upload/a_320/a_hflip/w_1000,f_auto,q_auto:low,fl_lossy,fl_progressive,fl_strip_profile/v1760720856/M9_BAYONET-Gamma_Doppler_Phase_2_uher55.webp",
    "correct_answer": "M9 BAYONET Gamma Doppler Phase 2",
    "wrong_answers": [
      "M9 BAYONET Lore",
      "M9 BAYONET Black Laminate",
      "M9 BAYONET Autotronic"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Qual é o nome desta faca?",
    "picture": "https://res.cloudinary.com/dwm53cbu2/image/upload/a_320/a_hflip/w_1000,f_auto,q_auto:low,fl_lossy,fl_progressive,fl_strip_profile/v1760720855/M9_BAYONET-Doppler_Phase_2_y28dm6.webp",
    "correct_answer": "M9 BAYONET Doppler Phase 2",
    "wrong_answers": [
      "M9 BAYONET Lore",
      "M9 BAYONET Black Laminate",
      "M9 BAYONET Autotronic"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Qual é o nome desta faca?",
    "picture": "https://res.cloudinary.com/dwm53cbu2/image/upload/a_320/a_hflip/w_1000,f_auto,q_auto:low,fl_lossy,fl_progressive,fl_strip_profile/v1760720854/M9_BAYONET-Forest_DDPAT_pyqkal.webp",
    "correct_answer": "M9 BAYONET Forest DDPAT",
    "wrong_answers": [
      "M9 BAYONET Lore",
      "M9 BAYONET Black Laminate",
      "M9 BAYONET Autotronic"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Qual é o nome desta faca?",
    "picture": "https://res.cloudinary.com/dwm53cbu2/image/upload/a_320/a_hflip/w_1000,f_auto,q_auto:low,fl_lossy,fl_progressive,fl_strip_profile/v1760720853/FLIP_KNIFE-Crimson_Web_j5xe9d.webp",
    "correct_answer": "FLIP KNIFE Crimson Web",
    "wrong_answers": [
      "PARACORD KNIFE Crimson Web",
      "URSUS KNIFE Crimson Web",
      "HUNTSMAN KNIFE Crimson Web"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Qual é o nome desta faca?",
    "picture": "https://res.cloudinary.com/dwm53cbu2/image/upload/a_320/a_hflip/w_1000,f_auto,q_auto:low,fl_lossy,fl_progressive,fl_strip_profile/v1760720851/M9_BAYONET-Gamma_Doppler_Phase_1_yvd2r6.webp",
    "correct_answer": "M9 BAYONET Gamma Doppler Phase 1",
    "wrong_answers": [
      "M9 BAYONET Lore",
      "M9 BAYONET Black Laminate",
      "M9 BAYONET Autotronic"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Qual é o nome desta faca?",
    "picture": "https://res.cloudinary.com/dwm53cbu2/image/upload/a_320/a_hflip/w_1000,f_auto,q_auto:low,fl_lossy,fl_progressive,fl_strip_profile/v1760720850/M9_BAYONET-Crimson_Web_hwjnme.webp",
    "correct_answer": "M9 BAYONET Crimson Web",
    "wrong_answers": [
      "M9 BAYONET Lore",
      "M9 BAYONET Black Laminate",
      "M9 BAYONET Autotronic"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Qual é o nome desta faca?",
    "picture": "https://res.cloudinary.com/dwm53cbu2/image/upload/a_320/a_hflip/w_1000,f_auto,q_auto:low,fl_lossy,fl_progressive,fl_strip_profile/v1760720849/M9_BAYONET-Doppler_Sapphire_ksyhev.webp",
    "correct_answer": "M9 BAYONET Doppler Sapphire",
    "wrong_answers": [
      "M9 BAYONET Lore",
      "M9 BAYONET Black Laminate",
      "M9 BAYONET Autotronic"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Qual é o nome desta faca?",
    "picture": "https://res.cloudinary.com/dwm53cbu2/image/upload/a_320/a_hflip/w_1000,f_auto,q_auto:low,fl_lossy,fl_progressive,fl_strip_profile/v1760720848/BAYONET-Lore_ccj6fs.webp",
    "correct_answer": "BAYONET Lore",
    "wrong_answers": [
      "KARAMBIT Lore",
      "BAYONET Rust Coat",
      "BAYONET Freehand"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Qual é o nome desta faca?",
    "picture": "https://res.cloudinary.com/dwm53cbu2/image/upload/a_320/a_hflip/w_1000,f_auto,q_auto:low,fl_lossy,fl_progressive,fl_strip_profile/v1760720847/M9_BAYONET-Doppler_Ruby_oafuxo.webp",
    "correct_answer": "M9 BAYONET Doppler Ruby",
    "wrong_answers": [
      "M9 BAYONET Lore",
      "M9 BAYONET Black Laminate",
      "M9 BAYONET Autotronic"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Qual é o nome desta faca?",
    "picture": "https://res.cloudinary.com/dwm53cbu2/image/upload/a_320/a_hflip/w_1000,f_auto,q_auto:low,fl_lossy,fl_progressive,fl_strip_profile/v1760720845/M9_BAYONET-Damascus_Steel_ypw1m5.webp",
    "correct_answer": "M9 BAYONET Damascus Steel",
    "wrong_answers": [
      "M9 BAYONET Lore",
      "M9 BAYONET Black Laminate",
      "M9 BAYONET Autotronic"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Qual é o nome desta faca?",
    "picture": "https://res.cloudinary.com/dwm53cbu2/image/upload/a_320/a_hflip/w_1000,f_auto,q_auto:low,fl_lossy,fl_progressive,fl_strip_profile/v1760720844/M9_BAYONET-Doppler_Phase_4_j23rsy.webp",
    "correct_answer": "M9 BAYONET Doppler Phase 4",
    "wrong_answers": [
      "M9 BAYONET Lore",
      "M9 BAYONET Black Laminate",
      "M9 BAYONET Autotronic"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Qual é o nome desta faca?",
    "picture": "https://res.cloudinary.com/dwm53cbu2/image/upload/a_320/a_hflip/w_1000,f_auto,q_auto:low,fl_lossy,fl_progressive,fl_strip_profile/v1760720843/M9_BAYONET-Case_Hardened_yzy8u0.webp",
    "correct_answer": "M9 BAYONET Case Hardened",
    "wrong_answers": [
      "M9 BAYONET Lore",
      "M9 BAYONET Black Laminate",
      "M9 BAYONET Autotronic"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Qual é o nome desta faca?",
    "picture": "https://res.cloudinary.com/dwm53cbu2/image/upload/a_320/a_hflip/w_1000,f_auto,q_auto:low,fl_lossy,fl_progressive,fl_strip_profile/v1760720842/M9_BAYONET-Blue_Steel_iylygr.webp",
    "correct_answer": "M9 BAYONET Blue Steel",
    "wrong_answers": [
      "M9 BAYONET Lore",
      "M9 BAYONET Black Laminate",
      "M9 BAYONET Autotronic"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Qual é o nome desta faca?",
    "picture": "https://res.cloudinary.com/dwm53cbu2/image/upload/a_320/a_hflip/w_1000,f_auto,q_auto:low,fl_lossy,fl_progressive,fl_strip_profile/v1760720841/M9_BAYONET-Doppler_Phase_1_fpbwc5.webp",
    "correct_answer": "M9 BAYONET Doppler Phase 1",
    "wrong_answers": [
      "M9 BAYONET Lore",
      "M9 BAYONET Black Laminate",
      "M9 BAYONET Autotronic"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Qual é o nome desta faca?",
    "picture": "https://res.cloudinary.com/dwm53cbu2/image/upload/a_320/a_hflip/w_1000,f_auto,q_auto:low,fl_lossy,fl_progressive,fl_strip_profile/v1760720840/M9_BAYONET-Boreal_Forest_s37t2k.webp",
    "correct_answer": "M9 BAYONET Boreal Forest",
    "wrong_answers": [
      "M9 BAYONET Lore",
      "M9 BAYONET Black Laminate",
      "M9 BAYONET Autotronic"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Qual é o nome desta faca?",
    "picture": "https://res.cloudinary.com/dwm53cbu2/image/upload/a_320/a_hflip/w_1000,f_auto,q_auto:low,fl_lossy,fl_progressive,fl_strip_profile/v1760720838/KUKRI_KNIFE-Vanilla_qfhsdo.webp",
    "correct_answer": "KUKRI KNIFE Vanilla",
    "wrong_answers": [
      "URSUS KNIFE Vanilla",
      "PARACORD KNIFE Vanilla",
      "NAJAVA KNIFE Vanilla"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Qual é o nome desta faca?",
    "picture": "https://res.cloudinary.com/dwm53cbu2/image/upload/a_320/a_hflip/w_1000,f_auto,q_auto:low,fl_lossy,fl_progressive,fl_strip_profile/v1760720837/KUKRI_KNIFE-Slaughter_aep3x9.webp",
    "correct_answer": "KUKRI KNIFE Slaughter",
    "wrong_answers": [
      "URSUS KNIFE Slaughter",
      "PARACORD KNIFE Slaughter",
      "NAJAVA KNIFE Slaughter"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Qual é o nome desta faca?",
    "picture": "https://res.cloudinary.com/dwm53cbu2/image/upload/a_320/a_hflip/w_1000,f_auto,q_auto:low,fl_lossy,fl_progressive,fl_strip_profile/v1760720836/KUKRI_KNIFE-Forest_DDPAT_fbwj79.webp",
    "correct_answer": "KUKRI KNIFE Forest DDPAT",
    "wrong_answers": [
      "PARACORD KNIFE Forest DDPAT",
      "URSUS KNIFE Forest DDPAT",
      "TALON KNIFE Forest DDPAT"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Qual é o nome desta faca?",
    "picture": "https://res.cloudinary.com/dwm53cbu2/image/upload/a_320/a_hflip/w_1000,f_auto,q_auto:low,fl_lossy,fl_progressive,fl_strip_profile/v1760720835/FLIP_KNIFE-Fade_wnon0k.webp",
    "correct_answer": "FLIP KNIFE Fade",
    "wrong_answers": [
      "NAJAVA KNIFE Fade",
      "URSUS KNIFE Fade",
      "PARACORD KNIFE Fade"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Qual é o nome desta faca?",
    "picture": "https://res.cloudinary.com/dwm53cbu2/image/upload/a_320/a_hflip/w_1000,f_auto,q_auto:low,fl_lossy,fl_progressive,fl_strip_profile/v1760720834/KUKRI_KNIFE-Boreal_Forest_updtqe.webp",
    "correct_answer": "KUKRI KNIFE Boreal Forest",
    "wrong_answers": [
      "PARACORD KNIFE Boreal Forest",
      "URSUS KNIFE Boreal Forest",
      "NOMAD KNIFE Boreal Forest"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Qual é o nome desta faca?",
    "picture": "https://res.cloudinary.com/dwm53cbu2/image/upload/a_320/a_hflip/w_1000,f_auto,q_auto:low,fl_lossy,fl_progressive,fl_strip_profile/v1760720832/KARAMBIT-Ultraviolet_igzz9q.webp",
    "correct_answer": "KARAMBIT Ultraviolet",
    "wrong_answers": [
      "SKELETON Ultraviolet",
      "BAYONET Ultraviolet",
      "KARAMBIT Lore"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Qual é o nome desta faca?",
    "picture": "https://res.cloudinary.com/dwm53cbu2/image/upload/a_320/a_hflip/w_1000,f_auto,q_auto:low,fl_lossy,fl_progressive,fl_strip_profile/v1760720831/KUKRI_KNIFE-Case_Hardened_y2vfoq.webp",
    "correct_answer": "KUKRI KNIFE Case Hardened",
    "wrong_answers": [
      "NAJAVA KNIFE Case Hardened",
      "URSUS KNIFE Case Hardened",
      "TALON KNIFE Case Hardened"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Qual é o nome desta faca?",
    "picture": "https://res.cloudinary.com/dwm53cbu2/image/upload/a_320/a_hflip/w_1000,f_auto,q_auto:low,fl_lossy,fl_progressive,fl_strip_profile/v1760720830/KUKRI_KNIFE-Crimson_Web_gjnwv8.webp",
    "correct_answer": "KUKRI KNIFE Crimson Web",
    "wrong_answers": [
      "PARACORD KNIFE Crimson Web",
      "URSUS KNIFE Crimson Web",
      "HUNTSMAN KNIFE Crimson Web"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Qual é o nome desta faca?",
    "picture": "https://res.cloudinary.com/dwm53cbu2/image/upload/a_320/a_hflip/w_1000,f_auto,q_auto:low,fl_lossy,fl_progressive,fl_strip_profile/v1760720829/KARAMBIT-Scorched_d89uon.webp",
    "correct_answer": "KARAMBIT Scorched",
    "wrong_answers": [
      "SKELETON Scorched",
      "BAYONET Scorched",
      "KARAMBIT Lore"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Qual é o nome desta faca?",
    "picture": "https://res.cloudinary.com/dwm53cbu2/image/upload/a_320/a_hflip/w_1000,f_auto,q_auto:low,fl_lossy,fl_progressive,fl_strip_profile/v1760720828/KARAMBIT-Safari_Mesh_pchwp6.webp",
    "correct_answer": "KARAMBIT Safari Mesh",
    "wrong_answers": [
      "SKELETON Safari Mesh",
      "BAYONET Safari Mesh",
      "KARAMBIT Lore"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Qual é o nome desta faca?",
    "picture": "https://res.cloudinary.com/dwm53cbu2/image/upload/a_320/a_hflip/w_1000,f_auto,q_auto:low,fl_lossy,fl_progressive,fl_strip_profile/v1760720827/FLIP_KNIFE-Autotronic_hamgzi.webp",
    "correct_answer": "FLIP KNIFE Autotronic",
    "wrong_answers": [
      "GUT KNIFE Autotronic",
      "HUNTSMAN KNIFE Autotronic",
      "FALCHION KNIFE Autotronic"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Qual é o nome desta faca?",
    "picture": "https://res.cloudinary.com/dwm53cbu2/image/upload/a_320/a_hflip/w_1000,f_auto,q_auto:low,fl_lossy,fl_progressive,fl_strip_profile/v1760720825/KARAMBIT-Night_afwbnk.webp",
    "correct_answer": "KARAMBIT Night",
    "wrong_answers": [
      "BAYONET Night",
      "KARAMBIT Lore",
      "KARAMBIT Black Laminate"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Qual é o nome desta faca?",
    "picture": "https://res.cloudinary.com/dwm53cbu2/image/upload/a_320/a_hflip/w_1000,f_auto,q_auto:low,fl_lossy,fl_progressive,fl_strip_profile/v1760720824/TALON_KNIFE-Night_Stripe_scuuy7.webp",
    "correct_answer": "TALON KNIFE Night Stripe",
    "wrong_answers": [
      "NOMAD KNIFE Night Stripe",
      "URSUS KNIFE Night Stripe",
      "PARACORD KNIFE Night Stripe"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Qual é o nome desta faca?",
    "picture": "https://res.cloudinary.com/dwm53cbu2/image/upload/a_320/a_hflip/w_1000,f_auto,q_auto:low,fl_lossy,fl_progressive,fl_strip_profile/v1760720823/SURVIVAL_KNIFE-Urban_Masked_kxwklh.webp",
    "correct_answer": "SURVIVAL KNIFE Urban Masked",
    "wrong_answers": [
      "PARACORD KNIFE Urban Masked",
      "NOMAD KNIFE Urban Masked",
      "URSUS KNIFE Urban Masked"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Qual é o nome desta faca?",
    "picture": "https://res.cloudinary.com/dwm53cbu2/image/upload/a_320/a_hflip/w_1000,f_auto,q_auto:low,fl_lossy,fl_progressive,fl_strip_profile/v1760720822/SURVIVAL_KNIFE-Tiger_Tooth_egemrt.webp",
    "correct_answer": "SURVIVAL KNIFE Tiger Tooth",
    "wrong_answers": [
      "URSUS KNIFE Tiger Tooth",
      "NAJAVA KNIFE Tiger Tooth",
      "PARACORD KNIFE Tiger Tooth"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Qual é o nome desta faca?",
    "picture": "https://res.cloudinary.com/dwm53cbu2/image/upload/a_320/a_hflip/w_1000,f_auto,q_auto:low,fl_lossy,fl_progressive,fl_strip_profile/v1760720821/SURVIVAL_KNIFE-Vanilla_enpgzy.webp",
    "correct_answer": "SURVIVAL KNIFE Vanilla",
    "wrong_answers": [
      "URSUS KNIFE Vanilla",
      "PARACORD KNIFE Vanilla",
      "NAJAVA KNIFE Vanilla"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Qual é o nome desta faca?",
    "picture": "https://res.cloudinary.com/dwm53cbu2/image/upload/a_320/a_hflip/w_1000,f_auto,q_auto:low,fl_lossy,fl_progressive,fl_strip_profile/v1760720819/SURVIVAL_KNIFE-Scorched_ldvuzv.webp",
    "correct_answer": "SURVIVAL KNIFE Scorched",
    "wrong_answers": [
      "URSUS KNIFE Scorched",
      "PARACORD KNIFE Scorched",
      "NOMAD KNIFE Scorched"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Qual é o nome desta faca?",
    "picture": "https://res.cloudinary.com/dwm53cbu2/image/upload/a_320/a_hflip/w_1000,f_auto,q_auto:low,fl_lossy,fl_progressive,fl_strip_profile/v1760720819/SURVIVAL_KNIFE-Doppler_Ruby_bw1nqo.webp",
    "correct_answer": "SURVIVAL KNIFE Doppler Ruby",
    "wrong_answers": [
      "URSUS KNIFE Doppler Ruby",
      "NAJAVA KNIFE Doppler Ruby",
      "TALON KNIFE Doppler Ruby"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Qual é o nome desta faca?",
    "picture": "https://res.cloudinary.com/dwm53cbu2/image/upload/a_320/a_hflip/w_1000,f_auto,q_auto:low,fl_lossy,fl_progressive,fl_strip_profile/v1760720817/SURVIVAL_KNIFE-Slaughter_ese4sv.webp",
    "correct_answer": "SURVIVAL KNIFE Slaughter",
    "wrong_answers": [
      "URSUS KNIFE Slaughter",
      "PARACORD KNIFE Slaughter",
      "NAJAVA KNIFE Slaughter"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Qual é o nome desta faca?",
    "picture": "https://res.cloudinary.com/dwm53cbu2/image/upload/a_320/a_hflip/w_1000,f_auto,q_auto:low,fl_lossy,fl_progressive,fl_strip_profile/v1760720816/SURVIVAL_KNIFE-Safari_Mesh_c7agwl.webp",
    "correct_answer": "SURVIVAL KNIFE Safari Mesh",
    "wrong_answers": [
      "PARACORD KNIFE Safari Mesh",
      "NOMAD KNIFE Safari Mesh",
      "URSUS KNIFE Safari Mesh"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Qual é o nome desta faca?",
    "picture": "https://res.cloudinary.com/dwm53cbu2/image/upload/a_320/a_hflip/w_1000,f_auto,q_auto:low,fl_lossy,fl_progressive,fl_strip_profile/v1760720815/SURVIVAL_KNIFE-Marble_Fade_jqi7zn.webp",
    "correct_answer": "SURVIVAL KNIFE Marble Fade",
    "wrong_answers": [
      "URSUS KNIFE Marble Fade",
      "PARACORD KNIFE Marble Fade",
      "NAJAVA KNIFE Marble Fade"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Qual é o nome desta faca?",
    "picture": "https://res.cloudinary.com/dwm53cbu2/image/upload/a_320/a_hflip/w_1000,f_auto,q_auto:low,fl_lossy,fl_progressive,fl_strip_profile/v1760720814/SURVIVAL_KNIFE-Fade_kte2sz.webp",
    "correct_answer": "SURVIVAL KNIFE Fade",
    "wrong_answers": [
      "NAJAVA KNIFE Fade",
      "URSUS KNIFE Fade",
      "PARACORD KNIFE Fade"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Qual é o nome desta faca?",
    "picture": "https://res.cloudinary.com/dwm53cbu2/image/upload/a_320/a_hflip/w_1000,f_auto,q_auto:low,fl_lossy,fl_progressive,fl_strip_profile/v1760720812/SURVIVAL_KNIFE-Doppler_Sapphire_xuau6z.webp",
    "correct_answer": "SURVIVAL KNIFE Doppler Sapphire",
    "wrong_answers": [
      "URSUS KNIFE Doppler Sapphire",
      "NAJAVA KNIFE Doppler Sapphire",
      "TALON KNIFE Doppler Sapphire"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Qual é o nome desta faca?",
    "picture": "https://res.cloudinary.com/dwm53cbu2/image/upload/a_320/a_hflip/w_1000,f_auto,q_auto:low,fl_lossy,fl_progressive,fl_strip_profile/v1760720811/SURVIVAL_KNIFE-Forest_DDPAT_aoizna.webp",
    "correct_answer": "SURVIVAL KNIFE Forest DDPAT",
    "wrong_answers": [
      "PARACORD KNIFE Forest DDPAT",
      "URSUS KNIFE Forest DDPAT",
      "TALON KNIFE Forest DDPAT"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Qual é o nome desta faca?",
    "picture": "https://res.cloudinary.com/dwm53cbu2/image/upload/a_320/a_hflip/w_1000,f_auto,q_auto:low,fl_lossy,fl_progressive,fl_strip_profile/v1760720810/FALCHION_KNIFE-Gamma_Doppler_Phase_3_iiau2w.webp",
    "correct_answer": "FALCHION KNIFE Gamma Doppler Phase 3",
    "wrong_answers": [
      "HUNTSMAN KNIFE Gamma Doppler Phase 3",
      "GUT KNIFE Gamma Doppler Phase 3",
      "FLIP KNIFE Gamma Doppler Phase 3"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Qual é o nome desta faca?",
    "picture": "https://res.cloudinary.com/dwm53cbu2/image/upload/a_320/a_hflip/w_1000,f_auto,q_auto:low,fl_lossy,fl_progressive,fl_strip_profile/v1760720809/SURVIVAL_KNIFE-Doppler_Phase_4_ynkgqn.webp",
    "correct_answer": "SURVIVAL KNIFE Doppler Phase 4",
    "wrong_answers": [
      "TALON KNIFE Doppler Phase 4",
      "URSUS KNIFE Doppler Phase 4",
      "PARACORD KNIFE Doppler Phase 4"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Qual é o nome desta faca?",
    "picture": "https://res.cloudinary.com/dwm53cbu2/image/upload/a_320/a_hflip/w_1000,f_auto,q_auto:low,fl_lossy,fl_progressive,fl_strip_profile/v1760720808/SURVIVAL_KNIFE-Doppler_Phase_1_o57aeh.webp",
    "correct_answer": "SURVIVAL KNIFE Doppler Phase 1",
    "wrong_answers": [
      "URSUS KNIFE Doppler Phase 1",
      "NAJAVA KNIFE Doppler Phase 1",
      "PARACORD KNIFE Doppler Phase 1"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Qual é o nome desta faca?",
    "picture": "https://res.cloudinary.com/dwm53cbu2/image/upload/a_320/a_hflip/w_1000,f_auto,q_auto:low,fl_lossy,fl_progressive,fl_strip_profile/v1760720806/SURVIVAL_KNIFE-Doppler_Phase_2_amkaff.webp",
    "correct_answer": "SURVIVAL KNIFE Doppler Phase 2",
    "wrong_answers": [
      "NAJAVA KNIFE Doppler Phase 2",
      "URSUS KNIFE Doppler Phase 2",
      "TALON KNIFE Doppler Phase 2"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Qual é o nome desta faca?",
    "picture": "https://res.cloudinary.com/dwm53cbu2/image/upload/a_320/a_hflip/w_1000,f_auto,q_auto:low,fl_lossy,fl_progressive,fl_strip_profile/v1760720805/FALCHION_KNIFE-Gamma_Doppler_Phase_1_hfnqtw.webp",
    "correct_answer": "FALCHION KNIFE Gamma Doppler Phase 1",
    "wrong_answers": [
      "HUNTSMAN KNIFE Gamma Doppler Phase 1",
      "GUT KNIFE Gamma Doppler Phase 1",
      "FLIP KNIFE Gamma Doppler Phase 1"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Qual é o nome desta faca?",
    "picture": "https://res.cloudinary.com/dwm53cbu2/image/upload/a_320/a_hflip/w_1000,f_auto,q_auto:low,fl_lossy,fl_progressive,fl_strip_profile/v1760720804/SURVIVAL_KNIFE-Damascus_Steel_scngb5.webp",
    "correct_answer": "SURVIVAL KNIFE Damascus Steel",
    "wrong_answers": [
      "NAJAVA KNIFE Damascus Steel",
      "GUT KNIFE Damascus Steel",
      "URSUS KNIFE Damascus Steel"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Qual é o nome desta faca?",
    "picture": "https://res.cloudinary.com/dwm53cbu2/image/upload/a_320/a_hflip/w_1000,f_auto,q_auto:low,fl_lossy,fl_progressive,fl_strip_profile/v1760720803/SURVIVAL_KNIFE-Case_Hardened_mzcudn.webp",
    "correct_answer": "SURVIVAL KNIFE Case Hardened",
    "wrong_answers": [
      "NAJAVA KNIFE Case Hardened",
      "URSUS KNIFE Case Hardened",
      "TALON KNIFE Case Hardened"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Qual é o nome desta faca?",
    "picture": "https://res.cloudinary.com/dwm53cbu2/image/upload/a_320/a_hflip/w_1000,f_auto,q_auto:low,fl_lossy,fl_progressive,fl_strip_profile/v1760720789/FALCHION_KNIFE-Freehand_bkxup3.webp",
    "correct_answer": "FALCHION KNIFE Freehand",
    "wrong_answers": [
      "GUT KNIFE Freehand",
      "HUNTSMAN KNIFE Freehand",
      "FLIP KNIFE Freehand"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Qual é o nome desta faca?",
    "picture": "https://res.cloudinary.com/dwm53cbu2/image/upload/a_320/a_hflip/w_1000,f_auto,q_auto:low,fl_lossy,fl_progressive,fl_strip_profile/v1760720787/SURVIVAL_KNIFE-Boreal_Forest_xyrsi3.webp",
    "correct_answer": "SURVIVAL KNIFE Boreal Forest",
    "wrong_answers": [
      "PARACORD KNIFE Boreal Forest",
      "URSUS KNIFE Boreal Forest",
      "NOMAD KNIFE Boreal Forest"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Qual é o nome desta faca?",
    "picture": "https://res.cloudinary.com/dwm53cbu2/image/upload/a_320/a_hflip/w_1000,f_auto,q_auto:low,fl_lossy,fl_progressive,fl_strip_profile/v1760720786/FALCHION_KNIFE-Gamma_Doppler_Phase_4_oqndlb.webp",
    "correct_answer": "FALCHION KNIFE Gamma Doppler Phase 4",
    "wrong_answers": [
      "GUT KNIFE Gamma Doppler Phase 4",
      "FLIP KNIFE Gamma Doppler Phase 4",
      "HUNTSMAN KNIFE Gamma Doppler Phase 4"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Qual é o nome desta faca?",
    "picture": "https://res.cloudinary.com/dwm53cbu2/image/upload/a_320/a_hflip/w_1000,f_auto,q_auto:low,fl_lossy,fl_progressive,fl_strip_profile/v1760720785/STILETTO_KNIFE-Vanilla_mdfqai.webp",
    "correct_answer": "STILETTO KNIFE Vanilla",
    "wrong_answers": [
      "URSUS KNIFE Vanilla",
      "PARACORD KNIFE Vanilla",
      "NAJAVA KNIFE Vanilla"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Qual é o nome desta faca?",
    "picture": "https://res.cloudinary.com/dwm53cbu2/image/upload/a_320/a_hflip/w_1000,f_auto,q_auto:low,fl_lossy,fl_progressive,fl_strip_profile/v1760720784/FALCHION_KNIFE-Gamma_Doppler_Emerald_vdmsh5.webp",
    "correct_answer": "FALCHION KNIFE Gamma Doppler Emerald",
    "wrong_answers": [
      "GUT KNIFE Gamma Doppler Emerald",
      "FLIP KNIFE Gamma Doppler Emerald",
      "HUNTSMAN KNIFE Gamma Doppler Emerald"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Qual é o nome desta faca?",
    "picture": "https://res.cloudinary.com/dwm53cbu2/image/upload/a_320/a_hflip/w_1000,f_auto,q_auto:low,fl_lossy,fl_progressive,fl_strip_profile/v1760720783/STILETTO_KNIFE-Tiger_Tooth_rczfdy.webp",
    "correct_answer": "STILETTO KNIFE Tiger Tooth",
    "wrong_answers": [
      "URSUS KNIFE Tiger Tooth",
      "NAJAVA KNIFE Tiger Tooth",
      "PARACORD KNIFE Tiger Tooth"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Qual é o nome desta faca?",
    "picture": "https://res.cloudinary.com/dwm53cbu2/image/upload/a_320/a_hflip/w_1000,f_auto,q_auto:low,fl_lossy,fl_progressive,fl_strip_profile/v1760720782/STILETTO_KNIFE-Marble_Fade_ygs5lh.webp",
    "correct_answer": "STILETTO KNIFE Marble Fade",
    "wrong_answers": [
      "URSUS KNIFE Marble Fade",
      "PARACORD KNIFE Marble Fade",
      "NAJAVA KNIFE Marble Fade"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Qual é o nome desta faca?",
    "picture": "https://res.cloudinary.com/dwm53cbu2/image/upload/a_320/a_hflip/w_1000,f_auto,q_auto:low,fl_lossy,fl_progressive,fl_strip_profile/v1760720780/STILETTO_KNIFE-Slaughter_bqlslg.webp",
    "correct_answer": "STILETTO KNIFE Slaughter",
    "wrong_answers": [
      "URSUS KNIFE Slaughter",
      "PARACORD KNIFE Slaughter",
      "NAJAVA KNIFE Slaughter"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Qual é o nome desta faca?",
    "picture": "https://res.cloudinary.com/dwm53cbu2/image/upload/a_320/a_hflip/w_1000,f_auto,q_auto:low,fl_lossy,fl_progressive,fl_strip_profile/v1760720779/STILETTO_KNIFE-Stained_avbkph.webp",
    "correct_answer": "STILETTO KNIFE Stained",
    "wrong_answers": [
      "NAJAVA KNIFE Stained",
      "PARACORD KNIFE Stained",
      "URSUS KNIFE Stained"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Qual é o nome desta faca?",
    "picture": "https://res.cloudinary.com/dwm53cbu2/image/upload/a_320/a_hflip/w_1000,f_auto,q_auto:low,fl_lossy,fl_progressive,fl_strip_profile/v1760720778/FALCHION_KNIFE-Gamma_Doppler_Phase_2_qt1tcl.webp",
    "correct_answer": "FALCHION KNIFE Gamma Doppler Phase 2",
    "wrong_answers": [
      "GUT KNIFE Gamma Doppler Phase 2",
      "FLIP KNIFE Gamma Doppler Phase 2",
      "HUNTSMAN KNIFE Gamma Doppler Phase 2"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Qual é o nome desta faca?",
    "picture": "https://res.cloudinary.com/dwm53cbu2/image/upload/a_320/a_hflip/w_1000,f_auto,q_auto:low,fl_lossy,fl_progressive,fl_strip_profile/v1760720776/HUNTSMAN_KNIFE-Scorched_lxymfx.webp",
    "correct_answer": "HUNTSMAN KNIFE Scorched",
    "wrong_answers": [
      "URSUS KNIFE Scorched",
      "PARACORD KNIFE Scorched",
      "NOMAD KNIFE Scorched"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Qual é o nome desta faca?",
    "picture": "https://res.cloudinary.com/dwm53cbu2/image/upload/a_320/a_hflip/w_1000,f_auto,q_auto:low,fl_lossy,fl_progressive,fl_strip_profile/v1760720774/SKELETON-Safari_Mesh_ozmpvt.webp",
    "correct_answer": "SKELETON Safari Mesh",
    "wrong_answers": [
      "KARAMBIT Safari Mesh",
      "BAYONET Safari Mesh",
      "SKELETON Rust Coat"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Qual é o nome desta faca?",
    "picture": "https://res.cloudinary.com/dwm53cbu2/image/upload/a_320/a_hflip/w_1000,f_auto,q_auto:low,fl_lossy,fl_progressive,fl_strip_profile/v1760720773/STILETTO_KNIFE-Fade_n6ubyv.webp",
    "correct_answer": "STILETTO KNIFE Fade",
    "wrong_answers": [
      "NAJAVA KNIFE Fade",
      "URSUS KNIFE Fade",
      "PARACORD KNIFE Fade"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Qual é o nome desta faca?",
    "picture": "https://res.cloudinary.com/dwm53cbu2/image/upload/a_320/a_hflip/w_1000,f_auto,q_auto:low,fl_lossy,fl_progressive,fl_strip_profile/v1760720772/HUNTSMAN_KNIFE-Urban_Masked_zq9in7.webp",
    "correct_answer": "HUNTSMAN KNIFE Urban Masked",
    "wrong_answers": [
      "PARACORD KNIFE Urban Masked",
      "NOMAD KNIFE Urban Masked",
      "URSUS KNIFE Urban Masked"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Qual é o nome desta faca?",
    "picture": "https://res.cloudinary.com/dwm53cbu2/image/upload/a_320/a_hflip/w_1000,f_auto,q_auto:low,fl_lossy,fl_progressive,fl_strip_profile/v1760720771/STILETTO_KNIFE-Doppler_Phase_3_dbqprx.webp",
    "correct_answer": "STILETTO KNIFE Doppler Phase 3",
    "wrong_answers": [
      "NAJAVA KNIFE Doppler Phase 3",
      "URSUS KNIFE Doppler Phase 3",
      "PARACORD KNIFE Doppler Phase 3"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Qual é o nome desta faca?",
    "picture": "https://res.cloudinary.com/dwm53cbu2/image/upload/a_320/a_hflip/w_1000,f_auto,q_auto:low,fl_lossy,fl_progressive,fl_strip_profile/v1760720770/STILETTO_KNIFE-Doppler_Black_Pearl_ovjxmt.webp",
    "correct_answer": "STILETTO KNIFE Doppler Black Pearl",
    "wrong_answers": [
      "NAJAVA KNIFE Doppler Black Pearl",
      "URSUS KNIFE Doppler Black Pearl",
      "TALON KNIFE Doppler Black Pearl"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Qual é o nome desta faca?",
    "picture": "https://res.cloudinary.com/dwm53cbu2/image/upload/a_320/a_hflip/w_1000,f_auto,q_auto:low,fl_lossy,fl_progressive,fl_strip_profile/v1760720768/STILETTO_KNIFE-Damascus_Steel_mwzilf.webp",
    "correct_answer": "STILETTO KNIFE Damascus Steel",
    "wrong_answers": [
      "NAJAVA KNIFE Damascus Steel",
      "GUT KNIFE Damascus Steel",
      "URSUS KNIFE Damascus Steel"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Qual é o nome desta faca?",
    "picture": "https://res.cloudinary.com/dwm53cbu2/image/upload/a_320/a_hflip/w_1000,f_auto,q_auto:low,fl_lossy,fl_progressive,fl_strip_profile/v1760720767/STILETTO_KNIFE-Doppler_Phase_4_fnalzm.webp",
    "correct_answer": "STILETTO KNIFE Doppler Phase 4",
    "wrong_answers": [
      "TALON KNIFE Doppler Phase 4",
      "URSUS KNIFE Doppler Phase 4",
      "PARACORD KNIFE Doppler Phase 4"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Qual é o nome desta faca?",
    "picture": "https://res.cloudinary.com/dwm53cbu2/image/upload/a_320/a_hflip/w_1000,f_auto,q_auto:low,fl_lossy,fl_progressive,fl_strip_profile/v1760720766/HUNTSMAN_KNIFE-Safari_Mesh_y2gpvl.webp",
    "correct_answer": "HUNTSMAN KNIFE Safari Mesh",
    "wrong_answers": [
      "PARACORD KNIFE Safari Mesh",
      "NOMAD KNIFE Safari Mesh",
      "URSUS KNIFE Safari Mesh"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Qual é o nome desta faca?",
    "picture": "https://res.cloudinary.com/dwm53cbu2/image/upload/a_320/a_hflip/w_1000,f_auto,q_auto:low,fl_lossy,fl_progressive,fl_strip_profile/v1760720765/HUNTSMAN_KNIFE-Stained_tzeuqb.webp",
    "correct_answer": "HUNTSMAN KNIFE Stained",
    "wrong_answers": [
      "NAJAVA KNIFE Stained",
      "PARACORD KNIFE Stained",
      "URSUS KNIFE Stained"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Qual é o nome desta faca?",
    "picture": "https://res.cloudinary.com/dwm53cbu2/image/upload/a_320/a_hflip/w_1000,f_auto,q_auto:low,fl_lossy,fl_progressive,fl_strip_profile/v1760720764/SKELETON-Doppler_Phase_4_bgfwpz.webp",
    "correct_answer": "SKELETON Doppler Phase 4",
    "wrong_answers": [
      "KARAMBIT Doppler Phase 4",
      "BAYONET Doppler Phase 4",
      "SKELETON Doppler Ruby"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Qual é o nome desta faca?",
    "picture": "https://res.cloudinary.com/dwm53cbu2/image/upload/a_320/a_hflip/w_1000,f_auto,q_auto:low,fl_lossy,fl_progressive,fl_strip_profile/v1760720762/STILETTO_KNIFE-Blue_Steel_lmnvcs.webp",
    "correct_answer": "STILETTO KNIFE Blue Steel",
    "wrong_answers": [
      "NAJAVA KNIFE Blue Steel",
      "URSUS KNIFE Blue Steel",
      "TALON KNIFE Blue Steel"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Qual é o nome desta faca?",
    "picture": "https://res.cloudinary.com/dwm53cbu2/image/upload/a_320/a_hflip/w_1000,f_auto,q_auto:low,fl_lossy,fl_progressive,fl_strip_profile/v1760720761/SKELETON-Scorched_gpdzgi.webp",
    "correct_answer": "SKELETON Scorched",
    "wrong_answers": [
      "KARAMBIT Scorched",
      "BAYONET Scorched",
      "SKELETON Rust Coat"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Qual é o nome desta faca?",
    "picture": "https://res.cloudinary.com/dwm53cbu2/image/upload/a_320/a_hflip/w_1000,f_auto,q_auto:low,fl_lossy,fl_progressive,fl_strip_profile/v1760720760/FALCHION_KNIFE-Doppler_Ruby_vybjm0.webp",
    "correct_answer": "FALCHION KNIFE Doppler Ruby",
    "wrong_answers": [
      "URSUS KNIFE Doppler Ruby",
      "NAJAVA KNIFE Doppler Ruby",
      "TALON KNIFE Doppler Ruby"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Qual é o nome desta faca?",
    "picture": "https://res.cloudinary.com/dwm53cbu2/image/upload/a_320/a_hflip/w_1000,f_auto,q_auto:low,fl_lossy,fl_progressive,fl_strip_profile/v1760720759/HUNTSMAN_KNIFE-Marble_Fade_qhvdvh.webp",
    "correct_answer": "HUNTSMAN KNIFE Marble Fade",
    "wrong_answers": [
      "URSUS KNIFE Marble Fade",
      "PARACORD KNIFE Marble Fade",
      "NAJAVA KNIFE Marble Fade"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Qual é o nome desta faca?",
    "picture": "https://res.cloudinary.com/dwm53cbu2/image/upload/a_320/a_hflip/w_1000,f_auto,q_auto:low,fl_lossy,fl_progressive,fl_strip_profile/v1760720758/SKELETON-Slaughter_g11lyx.webp",
    "correct_answer": "SKELETON Slaughter",
    "wrong_answers": [
      "KARAMBIT Slaughter",
      "BAYONET Slaughter",
      "SKELETON Rust Coat"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Qual é o nome desta faca?",
    "picture": "https://res.cloudinary.com/dwm53cbu2/image/upload/a_320/a_hflip/w_1000,f_auto,q_auto:low,fl_lossy,fl_progressive,fl_strip_profile/v1760720758/STILETTO_KNIFE-Doppler_Sapphire_kvcbfl.webp",
    "correct_answer": "STILETTO KNIFE Doppler Sapphire",
    "wrong_answers": [
      "URSUS KNIFE Doppler Sapphire",
      "NAJAVA KNIFE Doppler Sapphire",
      "TALON KNIFE Doppler Sapphire"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Qual é o nome desta faca?",
    "picture": "https://res.cloudinary.com/dwm53cbu2/image/upload/a_320/a_hflip/w_1000,f_auto,q_auto:low,fl_lossy,fl_progressive,fl_strip_profile/v1760720756/SKELETON-Tiger_Tooth_psypn4.webp",
    "correct_answer": "SKELETON Tiger Tooth",
    "wrong_answers": [
      "KARAMBIT Tiger Tooth",
      "BAYONET Tiger Tooth",
      "SKELETON Rust Coat"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Qual é o nome desta faca?",
    "picture": "https://res.cloudinary.com/dwm53cbu2/image/upload/a_320/a_hflip/w_1000,f_auto,q_auto:low,fl_lossy,fl_progressive,fl_strip_profile/v1760720755/HUNTSMAN_KNIFE-Slaughter_z3ulbk.webp",
    "correct_answer": "HUNTSMAN KNIFE Slaughter",
    "wrong_answers": [
      "URSUS KNIFE Slaughter",
      "PARACORD KNIFE Slaughter",
      "NAJAVA KNIFE Slaughter"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Qual é o nome desta faca?",
    "picture": "https://res.cloudinary.com/dwm53cbu2/image/upload/a_320/a_hflip/w_1000,f_auto,q_auto:low,fl_lossy,fl_progressive,fl_strip_profile/v1760720753/SKELETON-Forest_DDPAT_xuqghc.webp",
    "correct_answer": "SKELETON Forest DDPAT",
    "wrong_answers": [
      "KARAMBIT Forest DDPAT",
      "BAYONET Forest DDPAT",
      "SKELETON Rust Coat"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Qual é o nome desta faca?",
    "picture": "https://res.cloudinary.com/dwm53cbu2/image/upload/a_320/a_hflip/w_1000,f_auto,q_auto:low,fl_lossy,fl_progressive,fl_strip_profile/v1760720752/SKELETON-Doppler_Sapphire_nwf60s.webp",
    "correct_answer": "SKELETON Doppler Sapphire",
    "wrong_answers": [
      "KARAMBIT Doppler Sapphire",
      "BAYONET Doppler Sapphire",
      "SKELETON Doppler Ruby"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Qual é o nome desta faca?",
    "picture": "https://res.cloudinary.com/dwm53cbu2/image/upload/a_320/a_hflip/w_1000,f_auto,q_auto:low,fl_lossy,fl_progressive,fl_strip_profile/v1760720752/SKELETON-Marble_Fade_uhsnzx.webp",
    "correct_answer": "SKELETON Marble Fade",
    "wrong_answers": [
      "KARAMBIT Marble Fade",
      "BAYONET Marble Fade",
      "SKELETON Rust Coat"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Qual é o nome desta faca?",
    "picture": "https://res.cloudinary.com/dwm53cbu2/image/upload/a_320/a_hflip/w_1000,f_auto,q_auto:low,fl_lossy,fl_progressive,fl_strip_profile/v1760720750/SKELETON-Fade_ah18ld.webp",
    "correct_answer": "SKELETON Fade",
    "wrong_answers": [
      "KARAMBIT Fade",
      "BAYONET Fade",
      "SKELETON Rust Coat"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Qual é o nome desta faca?",
    "picture": "https://res.cloudinary.com/dwm53cbu2/image/upload/a_320/a_hflip/w_1000,f_auto,q_auto:low,fl_lossy,fl_progressive,fl_strip_profile/v1760720749/SKELETON-Doppler_Phase_1_hg9ixw.webp",
    "correct_answer": "SKELETON Doppler Phase 1",
    "wrong_answers": [
      "KARAMBIT Doppler Phase 1",
      "BAYONET Doppler Phase 1",
      "SKELETON Doppler Ruby"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Qual é o nome desta faca?",
    "picture": "https://res.cloudinary.com/dwm53cbu2/image/upload/a_320/a_hflip/w_1000,f_auto,q_auto:low,fl_lossy,fl_progressive,fl_strip_profile/v1760720748/SKELETON-Doppler_Phase_3_mzp0xr.webp",
    "correct_answer": "SKELETON Doppler Phase 3",
    "wrong_answers": [
      "KARAMBIT Doppler Phase 3",
      "SKELETON Doppler Ruby",
      "SKELETON Doppler Phase 4"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Qual é o nome desta faca?",
    "picture": "https://res.cloudinary.com/dwm53cbu2/image/upload/a_320/a_hflip/w_1000,f_auto,q_auto:low,fl_lossy,fl_progressive,fl_strip_profile/v1760720746/SKELETON-Urban_Masked_dqile5.webp",
    "correct_answer": "SKELETON Urban Masked",
    "wrong_answers": [
      "KARAMBIT Urban Masked",
      "BAYONET Urban Masked",
      "SKELETON Rust Coat"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Qual é o nome desta faca?",
    "picture": "https://res.cloudinary.com/dwm53cbu2/image/upload/a_320/a_hflip/w_1000,f_auto,q_auto:low,fl_lossy,fl_progressive,fl_strip_profile/v1760720745/SKELETON-Case_Hardened_uqtzal.webp",
    "correct_answer": "SKELETON Case Hardened",
    "wrong_answers": [
      "KARAMBIT Case Hardened",
      "BAYONET Case Hardened",
      "SKELETON Rust Coat"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Qual é o nome desta faca?",
    "picture": "https://res.cloudinary.com/dwm53cbu2/image/upload/a_320/a_hflip/w_1000,f_auto,q_auto:low,fl_lossy,fl_progressive,fl_strip_profile/v1760720743/SKELETON-Doppler_Phase_2_mhpmut.webp",
    "correct_answer": "SKELETON Doppler Phase 2",
    "wrong_answers": [
      "KARAMBIT Doppler Phase 2",
      "BAYONET Doppler Phase 2",
      "SKELETON Doppler Ruby"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Qual é o nome desta faca?",
    "picture": "https://res.cloudinary.com/dwm53cbu2/image/upload/a_320/a_hflip/w_1000,f_auto,q_auto:low,fl_lossy,fl_progressive,fl_strip_profile/v1760720742/SKELETON-Boreal_Forest_rq2nza.webp",
    "correct_answer": "SKELETON Boreal Forest",
    "wrong_answers": [
      "KARAMBIT Boreal Forest",
      "BAYONET Boreal Forest",
      "SKELETON Rust Coat"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Qual é o nome desta faca?",
    "picture": "https://res.cloudinary.com/dwm53cbu2/image/upload/a_320/a_hflip/w_1000,f_auto,q_auto:low,fl_lossy,fl_progressive,fl_strip_profile/v1760720737/BOWIE_KNIFE-Autotronic_vsnvup.webp",
    "correct_answer": "BOWIE KNIFE Autotronic",
    "wrong_answers": [
      "GUT KNIFE Autotronic",
      "HUNTSMAN KNIFE Autotronic",
      "FALCHION KNIFE Autotronic"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Qual é o nome desta faca?",
    "picture": "https://res.cloudinary.com/dwm53cbu2/image/upload/a_320/a_hflip/w_1000,f_auto,q_auto:low,fl_lossy,fl_progressive,fl_strip_profile/v1760720736/SKELETON-Crimson_Web_fetofn.webp",
    "correct_answer": "SKELETON Crimson Web",
    "wrong_answers": [
      "KARAMBIT Crimson Web",
      "BAYONET Crimson Web",
      "SKELETON Rust Coat"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Qual é o nome desta faca?",
    "picture": "https://res.cloudinary.com/dwm53cbu2/image/upload/a_320/a_hflip/w_1000,f_auto,q_auto:low,fl_lossy,fl_progressive,fl_strip_profile/v1760720562/BUTTERFLY_KNIFE-Autotronic_nycz9i.webp",
    "correct_answer": "BUTTERFLY KNIFE Autotronic",
    "wrong_answers": [
      "GUT KNIFE Autotronic",
      "HUNTSMAN KNIFE Autotronic",
      "FALCHION KNIFE Autotronic"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Qual é o nome desta faca?",
    "picture": "https://res.cloudinary.com/dwm53cbu2/image/upload/a_320/a_hflip/w_1000,f_auto,q_auto:low,fl_lossy,fl_progressive,fl_strip_profile/v1760720561/SKELETON-Damascus_Steel_s37dxw.webp",
    "correct_answer": "SKELETON Damascus Steel",
    "wrong_answers": [
      "KARAMBIT Damascus Steel",
      "BAYONET Damascus Steel",
      "SKELETON Rust Coat"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Qual é o nome desta faca?",
    "picture": "https://res.cloudinary.com/dwm53cbu2/image/upload/a_320/a_hflip/w_1000,f_auto,q_auto:low,fl_lossy,fl_progressive,fl_strip_profile/v1760720559/HUNTSMAN_KNIFE-Forest_DDPAT_plhn3f.webp",
    "correct_answer": "HUNTSMAN KNIFE Forest DDPAT",
    "wrong_answers": [
      "PARACORD KNIFE Forest DDPAT",
      "URSUS KNIFE Forest DDPAT",
      "TALON KNIFE Forest DDPAT"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Qual é o nome desta faca?",
    "picture": "https://res.cloudinary.com/dwm53cbu2/image/upload/a_320/a_hflip/w_1000,f_auto,q_auto:low,fl_lossy,fl_progressive,fl_strip_profile/v1760720557/HUNTSMAN_KNIFE-Fade_nkwtoh.webp",
    "correct_answer": "HUNTSMAN KNIFE Fade",
    "wrong_answers": [
      "NAJAVA KNIFE Fade",
      "URSUS KNIFE Fade",
      "PARACORD KNIFE Fade"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Qual é o nome desta faca?",
    "picture": "https://res.cloudinary.com/dwm53cbu2/image/upload/a_320/a_hflip/w_1000,f_auto,q_auto:low,fl_lossy,fl_progressive,fl_strip_profile/v1760720556/FALCHION_KNIFE-Case_Hardened_juher5.webp",
    "correct_answer": "FALCHION KNIFE Case Hardened",
    "wrong_answers": [
      "NAJAVA KNIFE Case Hardened",
      "URSUS KNIFE Case Hardened",
      "TALON KNIFE Case Hardened"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Qual é o nome desta faca?",
    "picture": "https://res.cloudinary.com/dwm53cbu2/image/upload/a_320/a_hflip/w_1000,f_auto,q_auto:low,fl_lossy,fl_progressive,fl_strip_profile/v1760720553/SKELETON-Doppler_Black_Pearl_ybmrlf.webp",
    "correct_answer": "SKELETON Doppler Black Pearl",
    "wrong_answers": [
      "KARAMBIT Doppler Black Pearl",
      "SKELETON Doppler Ruby",
      "SKELETON Doppler Phase 4"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Qual é o nome desta faca?",
    "picture": "https://res.cloudinary.com/dwm53cbu2/image/upload/a_320/a_hflip/w_1000,f_auto,q_auto:low,fl_lossy,fl_progressive,fl_strip_profile/v1760720552/HUNTSMAN_KNIFE-Doppler_Phase_4_ju0r1o.webp",
    "correct_answer": "HUNTSMAN KNIFE Doppler Phase 4",
    "wrong_answers": [
      "TALON KNIFE Doppler Phase 4",
      "URSUS KNIFE Doppler Phase 4",
      "PARACORD KNIFE Doppler Phase 4"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Qual é o nome desta faca?",
    "picture": "https://res.cloudinary.com/dwm53cbu2/image/upload/a_320/a_hflip/w_1000,f_auto,q_auto:low,fl_lossy,fl_progressive,fl_strip_profile/v1760720549/HUNTSMAN_KNIFE-Doppler_Phase_3_k7tio6.webp",
    "correct_answer": "HUNTSMAN KNIFE Doppler Phase 3",
    "wrong_answers": [
      "NAJAVA KNIFE Doppler Phase 3",
      "URSUS KNIFE Doppler Phase 3",
      "PARACORD KNIFE Doppler Phase 3"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Qual é o nome desta faca?",
    "picture": "https://res.cloudinary.com/dwm53cbu2/image/upload/a_320/a_hflip/w_1000,f_auto,q_auto:low,fl_lossy,fl_progressive,fl_strip_profile/v1760720548/HUNTSMAN_KNIFE-Doppler_Black_Pearl_ztsctr.webp",
    "correct_answer": "HUNTSMAN KNIFE Doppler Black Pearl",
    "wrong_answers": [
      "NAJAVA KNIFE Doppler Black Pearl",
      "URSUS KNIFE Doppler Black Pearl",
      "TALON KNIFE Doppler Black Pearl"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Qual é o nome desta faca?",
    "picture": "https://res.cloudinary.com/dwm53cbu2/image/upload/a_320/a_hflip/w_1000,f_auto,q_auto:low,fl_lossy,fl_progressive,fl_strip_profile/v1760720546/HUNTSMAN_KNIFE-Blue_Steel_zuhzfy.webp",
    "correct_answer": "HUNTSMAN KNIFE Blue Steel",
    "wrong_answers": [
      "NAJAVA KNIFE Blue Steel",
      "URSUS KNIFE Blue Steel",
      "TALON KNIFE Blue Steel"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Qual é o nome desta faca?",
    "picture": "https://res.cloudinary.com/dwm53cbu2/image/upload/a_320/a_hflip/w_1000,f_auto,q_auto:low,fl_lossy,fl_progressive,fl_strip_profile/v1760720544/GUT_KNIFE-Urban_Masked_uvc2lq.webp",
    "correct_answer": "GUT KNIFE Urban Masked",
    "wrong_answers": [
      "PARACORD KNIFE Urban Masked",
      "NOMAD KNIFE Urban Masked",
      "URSUS KNIFE Urban Masked"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Qual é o nome desta faca?",
    "picture": "https://res.cloudinary.com/dwm53cbu2/image/upload/a_320/a_hflip/w_1000,f_auto,q_auto:low,fl_lossy,fl_progressive,fl_strip_profile/v1760720542/GUT_KNIFE-Safari_Mesh_pndolx.webp",
    "correct_answer": "GUT KNIFE Safari Mesh",
    "wrong_answers": [
      "PARACORD KNIFE Safari Mesh",
      "NOMAD KNIFE Safari Mesh",
      "URSUS KNIFE Safari Mesh"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Qual é o nome desta faca?",
    "picture": "https://res.cloudinary.com/dwm53cbu2/image/upload/a_320/a_hflip/w_1000,f_auto,q_auto:low,fl_lossy,fl_progressive,fl_strip_profile/v1760720540/BOWIE_KNIFE-Lore_earfyx.webp",
    "correct_answer": "BOWIE KNIFE Lore",
    "wrong_answers": [
      "GUT KNIFE Lore",
      "FLIP KNIFE Lore",
      "HUNTSMAN KNIFE Lore"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Qual é o nome desta faca?",
    "picture": "https://res.cloudinary.com/dwm53cbu2/image/upload/a_320/a_hflip/w_1000,f_auto,q_auto:low,fl_lossy,fl_progressive,fl_strip_profile/v1760720538/NAJAVA_KNIFE-Urban_Masked_lwtkjy.webp",
    "correct_answer": "NAJAVA KNIFE Urban Masked",
    "wrong_answers": [
      "PARACORD KNIFE Urban Masked",
      "NOMAD KNIFE Urban Masked",
      "URSUS KNIFE Urban Masked"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Qual é o nome desta faca?",
    "picture": "https://res.cloudinary.com/dwm53cbu2/image/upload/a_320/a_hflip/w_1000,f_auto,q_auto:low,fl_lossy,fl_progressive,fl_strip_profile/v1760720537/GUT_KNIFE-Bright_Water_wkmlhb.webp",
    "correct_answer": "GUT KNIFE Bright Water",
    "wrong_answers": [
      "HUNTSMAN KNIFE Bright Water",
      "FLIP KNIFE Bright Water",
      "FALCHION KNIFE Bright Water"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Qual é o nome desta faca?",
    "picture": "https://res.cloudinary.com/dwm53cbu2/image/upload/a_320/a_hflip/w_1000,f_auto,q_auto:low,fl_lossy,fl_progressive,fl_strip_profile/v1760720534/NAJAVA_KNIFE-Forest_DDPAT_vnhngx.webp",
    "correct_answer": "NAJAVA KNIFE Forest DDPAT",
    "wrong_answers": [
      "PARACORD KNIFE Forest DDPAT",
      "URSUS KNIFE Forest DDPAT",
      "TALON KNIFE Forest DDPAT"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Qual é o nome desta faca?",
    "picture": "https://res.cloudinary.com/dwm53cbu2/image/upload/a_320/a_hflip/w_1000,f_auto,q_auto:low,fl_lossy,fl_progressive,fl_strip_profile/v1760720533/NAJAVA_KNIFE-Boreal_Forest_eyry8w.webp",
    "correct_answer": "NAJAVA KNIFE Boreal Forest",
    "wrong_answers": [
      "PARACORD KNIFE Boreal Forest",
      "URSUS KNIFE Boreal Forest",
      "NOMAD KNIFE Boreal Forest"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Qual é o nome desta faca?",
    "picture": "https://res.cloudinary.com/dwm53cbu2/image/upload/a_320/a_hflip/w_1000,f_auto,q_auto:low,fl_lossy,fl_progressive,fl_strip_profile/v1760720531/M9_BAYONET-Urban_Masked_yhddzl.webp",
    "correct_answer": "M9 BAYONET Urban Masked",
    "wrong_answers": [
      "M9 BAYONET Lore",
      "M9 BAYONET Black Laminate",
      "M9 BAYONET Autotronic"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Qual é o nome desta faca?",
    "picture": "https://res.cloudinary.com/dwm53cbu2/image/upload/a_320/a_hflip/w_1000,f_auto,q_auto:low,fl_lossy,fl_progressive,fl_strip_profile/v1760720529/NAJAVA_KNIFE-Crimson_Web_mlkkyn.webp",
    "correct_answer": "NAJAVA KNIFE Crimson Web",
    "wrong_answers": [
      "PARACORD KNIFE Crimson Web",
      "URSUS KNIFE Crimson Web",
      "HUNTSMAN KNIFE Crimson Web"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Qual é o nome desta faca?",
    "picture": "https://res.cloudinary.com/dwm53cbu2/image/upload/a_320/a_hflip/w_1000,f_auto,q_auto:low,fl_lossy,fl_progressive,fl_strip_profile/v1760720527/M9_BAYONET-Ultraviolet_xyexib.webp",
    "correct_answer": "M9 BAYONET Ultraviolet",
    "wrong_answers": [
      "M9 BAYONET Lore",
      "M9 BAYONET Black Laminate",
      "M9 BAYONET Autotronic"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Qual é o nome desta faca?",
    "picture": "https://res.cloudinary.com/dwm53cbu2/image/upload/a_320/a_hflip/w_1000,f_auto,q_auto:low,fl_lossy,fl_progressive,fl_strip_profile/v1760720525/FLIP_KNIFE-Vanilla_mrpi9i.webp",
    "correct_answer": "FLIP KNIFE Vanilla",
    "wrong_answers": [
      "URSUS KNIFE Vanilla",
      "PARACORD KNIFE Vanilla",
      "NAJAVA KNIFE Vanilla"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Qual é o nome desta faca?",
    "picture": "https://res.cloudinary.com/dwm53cbu2/image/upload/a_320/a_hflip/w_1000,f_auto,q_auto:low,fl_lossy,fl_progressive,fl_strip_profile/v1760720523/M9_BAYONET-Night_ovnghi.webp",
    "correct_answer": "M9 BAYONET Night",
    "wrong_answers": [
      "M9 BAYONET Lore",
      "M9 BAYONET Black Laminate",
      "M9 BAYONET Autotronic"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Qual é o nome desta faca?",
    "picture": "https://res.cloudinary.com/dwm53cbu2/image/upload/a_320/a_hflip/w_1000,f_auto,q_auto:low,fl_lossy,fl_progressive,fl_strip_profile/v1760720521/FLIP_KNIFE-Ultraviolet_qwjdek.webp",
    "correct_answer": "FLIP KNIFE Ultraviolet",
    "wrong_answers": [
      "PARACORD KNIFE Ultraviolet",
      "NOMAD KNIFE Ultraviolet",
      "URSUS KNIFE Ultraviolet"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Qual é o nome desta faca?",
    "picture": "https://res.cloudinary.com/dwm53cbu2/image/upload/a_320/a_hflip/w_1000,f_auto,q_auto:low,fl_lossy,fl_progressive,fl_strip_profile/v1760720520/BAYONET-Rust_Coat_laqwuu.webp",
    "correct_answer": "BAYONET Rust Coat",
    "wrong_answers": [
      "KARAMBIT Rust Coat",
      "SKELETON Rust Coat",
      "BAYONET Lore"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Qual é o nome desta faca?",
    "picture": "https://res.cloudinary.com/dwm53cbu2/image/upload/a_320/a_hflip/w_1000,f_auto,q_auto:low,fl_lossy,fl_progressive,fl_strip_profile/v1760720518/FLIP_KNIFE-Urban_Masked_kgjr8f.webp",
    "correct_answer": "FLIP KNIFE Urban Masked",
    "wrong_answers": [
      "PARACORD KNIFE Urban Masked",
      "NOMAD KNIFE Urban Masked",
      "URSUS KNIFE Urban Masked"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Qual é o nome desta faca?",
    "picture": "https://res.cloudinary.com/dwm53cbu2/image/upload/a_320/a_hflip/w_1000,f_auto,q_auto:low,fl_lossy,fl_progressive,fl_strip_profile/v1760720516/FLIP_KNIFE-Slaughter_ddbrin.webp",
    "correct_answer": "FLIP KNIFE Slaughter",
    "wrong_answers": [
      "URSUS KNIFE Slaughter",
      "PARACORD KNIFE Slaughter",
      "NAJAVA KNIFE Slaughter"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Qual é o nome desta faca?",
    "picture": "https://res.cloudinary.com/dwm53cbu2/image/upload/a_320/a_hflip/w_1000,f_auto,q_auto:low,fl_lossy,fl_progressive,fl_strip_profile/v1760720514/FLIP_KNIFE-Stained_kxcalz.webp",
    "correct_answer": "FLIP KNIFE Stained",
    "wrong_answers": [
      "NAJAVA KNIFE Stained",
      "PARACORD KNIFE Stained",
      "URSUS KNIFE Stained"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Qual é o nome desta faca?",
    "picture": "https://res.cloudinary.com/dwm53cbu2/image/upload/a_320/a_hflip/w_1000,f_auto,q_auto:low,fl_lossy,fl_progressive,fl_strip_profile/v1760720512/FLIP_KNIFE-Marble_Fade_afrmni.webp",
    "correct_answer": "FLIP KNIFE Marble Fade",
    "wrong_answers": [
      "URSUS KNIFE Marble Fade",
      "PARACORD KNIFE Marble Fade",
      "NAJAVA KNIFE Marble Fade"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Qual é o nome desta faca?",
    "picture": "https://res.cloudinary.com/dwm53cbu2/image/upload/a_320/a_hflip/w_1000,f_auto,q_auto:low,fl_lossy,fl_progressive,fl_strip_profile/v1760720510/M9_BAYONET-Doppler_Black_Pearl_d4xnal.webp",
    "correct_answer": "M9 BAYONET Doppler Black Pearl",
    "wrong_answers": [
      "M9 BAYONET Lore",
      "M9 BAYONET Black Laminate",
      "M9 BAYONET Autotronic"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Qual é o nome desta faca?",
    "picture": "https://res.cloudinary.com/dwm53cbu2/image/upload/a_320/a_hflip/w_1000,f_auto,q_auto:low,fl_lossy,fl_progressive,fl_strip_profile/v1760720508/FLIP_KNIFE-Gamma_Doppler_Phase_3_fydwff.webp",
    "correct_answer": "FLIP KNIFE Gamma Doppler Phase 3",
    "wrong_answers": [
      "HUNTSMAN KNIFE Gamma Doppler Phase 3",
      "GUT KNIFE Gamma Doppler Phase 3",
      "FALCHION KNIFE Gamma Doppler Phase 3"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Qual é o nome desta faca?",
    "picture": "https://res.cloudinary.com/dwm53cbu2/image/upload/a_320/a_hflip/w_1000,f_auto,q_auto:low,fl_lossy,fl_progressive,fl_strip_profile/v1760720506/FLIP_KNIFE-Gamma_Doppler_Phase_1_vulgql.webp",
    "correct_answer": "FLIP KNIFE Gamma Doppler Phase 1",
    "wrong_answers": [
      "HUNTSMAN KNIFE Gamma Doppler Phase 1",
      "GUT KNIFE Gamma Doppler Phase 1",
      "FALCHION KNIFE Gamma Doppler Phase 1"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Qual é o nome desta faca?",
    "picture": "https://res.cloudinary.com/dwm53cbu2/image/upload/a_320/a_hflip/w_1000,f_auto,q_auto:low,fl_lossy,fl_progressive,fl_strip_profile/v1760720504/M9_BAYONET-Bright_Water_vgmync.webp",
    "correct_answer": "M9 BAYONET Bright Water",
    "wrong_answers": [
      "M9 BAYONET Lore",
      "M9 BAYONET Black Laminate",
      "M9 BAYONET Autotronic"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Qual é o nome desta faca?",
    "picture": "https://res.cloudinary.com/dwm53cbu2/image/upload/a_320/a_hflip/w_1000,f_auto,q_auto:low,fl_lossy,fl_progressive,fl_strip_profile/v1760720502/KUKRI_KNIFE-Urban_Masked_pxm5qx.webp",
    "correct_answer": "KUKRI KNIFE Urban Masked",
    "wrong_answers": [
      "PARACORD KNIFE Urban Masked",
      "NOMAD KNIFE Urban Masked",
      "URSUS KNIFE Urban Masked"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Qual é o nome desta faca?",
    "picture": "https://res.cloudinary.com/dwm53cbu2/image/upload/a_320/a_hflip/w_1000,f_auto,q_auto:low,fl_lossy,fl_progressive,fl_strip_profile/v1760720501/FLIP_KNIFE-Forest_DDPAT_v4vcym.webp",
    "correct_answer": "FLIP KNIFE Forest DDPAT",
    "wrong_answers": [
      "PARACORD KNIFE Forest DDPAT",
      "URSUS KNIFE Forest DDPAT",
      "TALON KNIFE Forest DDPAT"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Qual é o nome desta faca?",
    "picture": "https://res.cloudinary.com/dwm53cbu2/image/upload/a_320/a_hflip/w_1000,f_auto,q_auto:low,fl_lossy,fl_progressive,fl_strip_profile/v1760720499/FLIP_KNIFE-Doppler_Phase_2_xjxohr.webp",
    "correct_answer": "FLIP KNIFE Doppler Phase 2",
    "wrong_answers": [
      "NAJAVA KNIFE Doppler Phase 2",
      "URSUS KNIFE Doppler Phase 2",
      "TALON KNIFE Doppler Phase 2"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Qual é o nome desta faca?",
    "picture": "https://res.cloudinary.com/dwm53cbu2/image/upload/a_320/a_hflip/w_1000,f_auto,q_auto:low,fl_lossy,fl_progressive,fl_strip_profile/v1760720497/KUKRI_KNIFE-Stained_jg6oio.webp",
    "correct_answer": "KUKRI KNIFE Stained",
    "wrong_answers": [
      "NAJAVA KNIFE Stained",
      "PARACORD KNIFE Stained",
      "URSUS KNIFE Stained"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Qual é o nome desta faca?",
    "picture": "https://res.cloudinary.com/dwm53cbu2/image/upload/a_320/a_hflip/w_1000,f_auto,q_auto:low,fl_lossy,fl_progressive,fl_strip_profile/v1760720495/FLIP_KNIFE-Doppler_Ruby_nqte77.webp",
    "correct_answer": "FLIP KNIFE Doppler Ruby",
    "wrong_answers": [
      "URSUS KNIFE Doppler Ruby",
      "NAJAVA KNIFE Doppler Ruby",
      "TALON KNIFE Doppler Ruby"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Qual é o nome desta faca?",
    "picture": "https://res.cloudinary.com/dwm53cbu2/image/upload/a_320/a_hflip/w_1000,f_auto,q_auto:low,fl_lossy,fl_progressive,fl_strip_profile/v1760720492/FLIP_KNIFE-Doppler_Phase_4_xav08o.webp",
    "correct_answer": "FLIP KNIFE Doppler Phase 4",
    "wrong_answers": [
      "TALON KNIFE Doppler Phase 4",
      "URSUS KNIFE Doppler Phase 4",
      "PARACORD KNIFE Doppler Phase 4"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Qual é o nome desta faca?",
    "picture": "https://res.cloudinary.com/dwm53cbu2/image/upload/a_320/a_hflip/w_1000,f_auto,q_auto:low,fl_lossy,fl_progressive,fl_strip_profile/v1760720491/FLIP_KNIFE-Doppler_Sapphire_ankak4.webp",
    "correct_answer": "FLIP KNIFE Doppler Sapphire",
    "wrong_answers": [
      "URSUS KNIFE Doppler Sapphire",
      "NAJAVA KNIFE Doppler Sapphire",
      "TALON KNIFE Doppler Sapphire"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Qual é o nome desta faca?",
    "picture": "https://res.cloudinary.com/dwm53cbu2/image/upload/a_320/a_hflip/w_1000,f_auto,q_auto:low,fl_lossy,fl_progressive,fl_strip_profile/v1760720489/KUKRI_KNIFE-Fade_wkh6c7.webp",
    "correct_answer": "KUKRI KNIFE Fade",
    "wrong_answers": [
      "NAJAVA KNIFE Fade",
      "URSUS KNIFE Fade",
      "PARACORD KNIFE Fade"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Qual é o nome desta faca?",
    "picture": "https://res.cloudinary.com/dwm53cbu2/image/upload/a_320/a_hflip/w_1000,f_auto,q_auto:low,fl_lossy,fl_progressive,fl_strip_profile/v1760720487/FLIP_KNIFE-Doppler_Phase_1_z1nyav.webp",
    "correct_answer": "FLIP KNIFE Doppler Phase 1",
    "wrong_answers": [
      "URSUS KNIFE Doppler Phase 1",
      "NAJAVA KNIFE Doppler Phase 1",
      "PARACORD KNIFE Doppler Phase 1"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Qual é o nome desta faca?",
    "picture": "https://res.cloudinary.com/dwm53cbu2/image/upload/a_320/a_hflip/w_1000,f_auto,q_auto:low,fl_lossy,fl_progressive,fl_strip_profile/v1760720485/KUKRI_KNIFE-Blue_Steel_oene2d.webp",
    "correct_answer": "KUKRI KNIFE Blue Steel",
    "wrong_answers": [
      "NAJAVA KNIFE Blue Steel",
      "URSUS KNIFE Blue Steel",
      "TALON KNIFE Blue Steel"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Qual é o nome desta faca?",
    "picture": "https://res.cloudinary.com/dwm53cbu2/image/upload/a_320/a_hflip/w_1000,f_auto,q_auto:low,fl_lossy,fl_progressive,fl_strip_profile/v1760720484/FLIP_KNIFE-Doppler_Phase_3_qyttks.webp",
    "correct_answer": "FLIP KNIFE Doppler Phase 3",
    "wrong_answers": [
      "NAJAVA KNIFE Doppler Phase 3",
      "URSUS KNIFE Doppler Phase 3",
      "PARACORD KNIFE Doppler Phase 3"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Qual é o nome desta faca?",
    "picture": "https://res.cloudinary.com/dwm53cbu2/image/upload/a_320/a_hflip/w_1000,f_auto,q_auto:low,fl_lossy,fl_progressive,fl_strip_profile/v1760720481/FLIP_KNIFE-Doppler_Black_Pearl_qkbfsd.webp",
    "correct_answer": "FLIP KNIFE Doppler Black Pearl",
    "wrong_answers": [
      "NAJAVA KNIFE Doppler Black Pearl",
      "URSUS KNIFE Doppler Black Pearl",
      "TALON KNIFE Doppler Black Pearl"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Qual é o nome desta faca?",
    "picture": "https://res.cloudinary.com/dwm53cbu2/image/upload/a_320/a_hflip/w_1000,f_auto,q_auto:low,fl_lossy,fl_progressive,fl_strip_profile/v1760720480/KUKRI_KNIFE-Safari_Mesh_e0c3fr.webp",
    "correct_answer": "KUKRI KNIFE Safari Mesh",
    "wrong_answers": [
      "PARACORD KNIFE Safari Mesh",
      "NOMAD KNIFE Safari Mesh",
      "URSUS KNIFE Safari Mesh"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Qual é o nome desta faca?",
    "picture": "https://res.cloudinary.com/dwm53cbu2/image/upload/a_320/a_hflip/w_1000,f_auto,q_auto:low,fl_lossy,fl_progressive,fl_strip_profile/v1760720478/KUKRI_KNIFE-Scorched_lowq5q.webp",
    "correct_answer": "KUKRI KNIFE Scorched",
    "wrong_answers": [
      "URSUS KNIFE Scorched",
      "PARACORD KNIFE Scorched",
      "NOMAD KNIFE Scorched"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Qual é o nome desta faca?",
    "picture": "https://res.cloudinary.com/dwm53cbu2/image/upload/a_320/a_hflip/w_1000,f_auto,q_auto:low,fl_lossy,fl_progressive,fl_strip_profile/v1760720476/KUKRI_KNIFE-Night_Stripe_cehfs2.webp",
    "correct_answer": "KUKRI KNIFE Night Stripe",
    "wrong_answers": [
      "NOMAD KNIFE Night Stripe",
      "URSUS KNIFE Night Stripe",
      "PARACORD KNIFE Night Stripe"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Qual é o nome desta faca?",
    "picture": "https://res.cloudinary.com/dwm53cbu2/image/upload/a_320/a_hflip/w_1000,f_auto,q_auto:low,fl_lossy,fl_progressive,fl_strip_profile/v1760720475/FLIP_KNIFE-Bright_Water_cgd7re.webp",
    "correct_answer": "FLIP KNIFE Bright Water",
    "wrong_answers": [
      "HUNTSMAN KNIFE Bright Water",
      "GUT KNIFE Bright Water",
      "FALCHION KNIFE Bright Water"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Qual é o nome desta faca?",
    "picture": "https://res.cloudinary.com/dwm53cbu2/image/upload/a_320/a_hflip/w_1000,f_auto,q_auto:low,fl_lossy,fl_progressive,fl_strip_profile/v1760720473/FLIP_KNIFE-Boreal_Forest_rtempg.webp",
    "correct_answer": "FLIP KNIFE Boreal Forest",
    "wrong_answers": [
      "PARACORD KNIFE Boreal Forest",
      "URSUS KNIFE Boreal Forest",
      "NOMAD KNIFE Boreal Forest"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Qual é o nome desta faca?",
    "picture": "https://res.cloudinary.com/dwm53cbu2/image/upload/a_320/a_hflip/w_1000,f_auto,q_auto:low,fl_lossy,fl_progressive,fl_strip_profile/v1760720471/FLIP_KNIFE-Blue_Steel_vxog6i.webp",
    "correct_answer": "FLIP KNIFE Blue Steel",
    "wrong_answers": [
      "NAJAVA KNIFE Blue Steel",
      "URSUS KNIFE Blue Steel",
      "TALON KNIFE Blue Steel"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Qual é o nome desta faca?",
    "picture": "https://res.cloudinary.com/dwm53cbu2/image/upload/a_320/a_hflip/w_1000,f_auto,q_auto:low,fl_lossy,fl_progressive,fl_strip_profile/v1760720469/FLIP_KNIFE-Case_Hardened_shrzcg.webp",
    "correct_answer": "FLIP KNIFE Case Hardened",
    "wrong_answers": [
      "NAJAVA KNIFE Case Hardened",
      "URSUS KNIFE Case Hardened",
      "TALON KNIFE Case Hardened"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Qual é o nome desta faca?",
    "picture": "https://res.cloudinary.com/dwm53cbu2/image/upload/a_320/a_hflip/w_1000,f_auto,q_auto:low,fl_lossy,fl_progressive,fl_strip_profile/v1760720468/FLIP_KNIFE-Damascus_Steel_bdj7s2.webp",
    "correct_answer": "FLIP KNIFE Damascus Steel",
    "wrong_answers": [
      "NAJAVA KNIFE Damascus Steel",
      "GUT KNIFE Damascus Steel",
      "URSUS KNIFE Damascus Steel"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Qual é o nome desta faca?",
    "picture": "https://res.cloudinary.com/dwm53cbu2/image/upload/a_320/a_hflip/w_1000,f_auto,q_auto:low,fl_lossy,fl_progressive,fl_strip_profile/v1760720465/FALCHION_KNIFE-Vanilla_pb4bbh.webp",
    "correct_answer": "FALCHION KNIFE Vanilla",
    "wrong_answers": [
      "URSUS KNIFE Vanilla",
      "PARACORD KNIFE Vanilla",
      "NAJAVA KNIFE Vanilla"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Qual é o nome desta faca?",
    "picture": "https://res.cloudinary.com/dwm53cbu2/image/upload/a_320/a_hflip/w_1000,f_auto,q_auto:low,fl_lossy,fl_progressive,fl_strip_profile/v1760720464/FALCHION_KNIFE-Tiger_Tooth_wawvej.webp",
    "correct_answer": "FALCHION KNIFE Tiger Tooth",
    "wrong_answers": [
      "URSUS KNIFE Tiger Tooth",
      "NAJAVA KNIFE Tiger Tooth",
      "PARACORD KNIFE Tiger Tooth"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Qual é o nome desta faca?",
    "picture": "https://res.cloudinary.com/dwm53cbu2/image/upload/a_320/a_hflip/w_1000,f_auto,q_auto:low,fl_lossy,fl_progressive,fl_strip_profile/v1760720462/FALCHION_KNIFE-Stained_adcj9x.webp",
    "correct_answer": "FALCHION KNIFE Stained",
    "wrong_answers": [
      "NAJAVA KNIFE Stained",
      "PARACORD KNIFE Stained",
      "URSUS KNIFE Stained"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Qual é o nome desta faca?",
    "picture": "https://res.cloudinary.com/dwm53cbu2/image/upload/a_320/a_hflip/w_1000,f_auto,q_auto:low,fl_lossy,fl_progressive,fl_strip_profile/v1760720461/SURVIVAL_KNIFE-Night_Stripe_fsbv6r.webp",
    "correct_answer": "SURVIVAL KNIFE Night Stripe",
    "wrong_answers": [
      "NOMAD KNIFE Night Stripe",
      "URSUS KNIFE Night Stripe",
      "PARACORD KNIFE Night Stripe"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Qual é o nome desta faca?",
    "picture": "https://res.cloudinary.com/dwm53cbu2/image/upload/a_320/a_hflip/w_1000,f_auto,q_auto:low,fl_lossy,fl_progressive,fl_strip_profile/v1760720459/SURVIVAL_KNIFE-Doppler_Phase_3_zcoeqk.webp",
    "correct_answer": "SURVIVAL KNIFE Doppler Phase 3",
    "wrong_answers": [
      "NAJAVA KNIFE Doppler Phase 3",
      "URSUS KNIFE Doppler Phase 3",
      "PARACORD KNIFE Doppler Phase 3"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Qual é o nome desta faca?",
    "picture": "https://res.cloudinary.com/dwm53cbu2/image/upload/a_320/a_hflip/w_1000,f_auto,q_auto:low,fl_lossy,fl_progressive,fl_strip_profile/v1760720457/FALCHION_KNIFE-Marble_Fade_mxi9w8.webp",
    "correct_answer": "FALCHION KNIFE Marble Fade",
    "wrong_answers": [
      "URSUS KNIFE Marble Fade",
      "PARACORD KNIFE Marble Fade",
      "NAJAVA KNIFE Marble Fade"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Qual é o nome desta faca?",
    "picture": "https://res.cloudinary.com/dwm53cbu2/image/upload/a_320/a_hflip/w_1000,f_auto,q_auto:low,fl_lossy,fl_progressive,fl_strip_profile/v1760720455/SURVIVAL_KNIFE-Doppler_Black_Pearl_i03lyx.webp",
    "correct_answer": "SURVIVAL KNIFE Doppler Black Pearl",
    "wrong_answers": [
      "NAJAVA KNIFE Doppler Black Pearl",
      "URSUS KNIFE Doppler Black Pearl",
      "TALON KNIFE Doppler Black Pearl"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Qual é o nome desta faca?",
    "picture": "https://res.cloudinary.com/dwm53cbu2/image/upload/a_320/a_hflip/w_1000,f_auto,q_auto:low,fl_lossy,fl_progressive,fl_strip_profile/v1760720453/SURVIVAL_KNIFE-Blue_Steel_uovio8.webp",
    "correct_answer": "SURVIVAL KNIFE Blue Steel",
    "wrong_answers": [
      "NAJAVA KNIFE Blue Steel",
      "URSUS KNIFE Blue Steel",
      "TALON KNIFE Blue Steel"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Qual é o nome desta faca?",
    "picture": "https://res.cloudinary.com/dwm53cbu2/image/upload/a_320/a_hflip/w_1000,f_auto,q_auto:low,fl_lossy,fl_progressive,fl_strip_profile/v1760720451/HUNTSMAN_KNIFE-Ultraviolet_cuofhx.webp",
    "correct_answer": "HUNTSMAN KNIFE Ultraviolet",
    "wrong_answers": [
      "PARACORD KNIFE Ultraviolet",
      "NOMAD KNIFE Ultraviolet",
      "URSUS KNIFE Ultraviolet"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Qual é o nome desta faca?",
    "picture": "https://res.cloudinary.com/dwm53cbu2/image/upload/a_320/a_hflip/w_1000,f_auto,q_auto:low,fl_lossy,fl_progressive,fl_strip_profile/v1760720450/STILETTO_KNIFE-Urban_Masked_lzkkxw.webp",
    "correct_answer": "STILETTO KNIFE Urban Masked",
    "wrong_answers": [
      "PARACORD KNIFE Urban Masked",
      "NOMAD KNIFE Urban Masked",
      "URSUS KNIFE Urban Masked"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Qual é o nome desta faca?",
    "picture": "https://res.cloudinary.com/dwm53cbu2/image/upload/a_320/a_hflip/w_1000,f_auto,q_auto:low,fl_lossy,fl_progressive,fl_strip_profile/v1760720447/STILETTO_KNIFE-Safari_Mesh_fhzf7h.webp",
    "correct_answer": "STILETTO KNIFE Safari Mesh",
    "wrong_answers": [
      "PARACORD KNIFE Safari Mesh",
      "NOMAD KNIFE Safari Mesh",
      "URSUS KNIFE Safari Mesh"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Qual é o nome desta faca?",
    "picture": "https://res.cloudinary.com/dwm53cbu2/image/upload/a_320/a_hflip/w_1000,f_auto,q_auto:low,fl_lossy,fl_progressive,fl_strip_profile/v1760720445/STILETTO_KNIFE-Scorched_lqyrhi.webp",
    "correct_answer": "STILETTO KNIFE Scorched",
    "wrong_answers": [
      "URSUS KNIFE Scorched",
      "PARACORD KNIFE Scorched",
      "NOMAD KNIFE Scorched"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Qual é o nome desta faca?",
    "picture": "https://res.cloudinary.com/dwm53cbu2/image/upload/a_320/a_hflip/w_1000,f_auto,q_auto:low,fl_lossy,fl_progressive,fl_strip_profile/v1760720444/BUTTERFLY_KNIFE-Black_Laminate_fzshw2.webp",
    "correct_answer": "BUTTERFLY KNIFE Black Laminate",
    "wrong_answers": [
      "HUNTSMAN KNIFE Black Laminate",
      "GUT KNIFE Black Laminate",
      "FALCHION KNIFE Black Laminate"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Qual é o nome desta faca?",
    "picture": "https://res.cloudinary.com/dwm53cbu2/image/upload/a_320/a_hflip/w_1000,f_auto,q_auto:low,fl_lossy,fl_progressive,fl_strip_profile/v1760720443/STILETTO_KNIFE-Forest_DDPAT_lrjfqo.webp",
    "correct_answer": "STILETTO KNIFE Forest DDPAT",
    "wrong_answers": [
      "PARACORD KNIFE Forest DDPAT",
      "URSUS KNIFE Forest DDPAT",
      "TALON KNIFE Forest DDPAT"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Qual é o nome desta faca?",
    "picture": "https://res.cloudinary.com/dwm53cbu2/image/upload/a_320/a_hflip/w_1000,f_auto,q_auto:low,fl_lossy,fl_progressive,fl_strip_profile/v1760720442/HUNTSMAN_KNIFE-Night_bsjkiq.webp",
    "correct_answer": "HUNTSMAN KNIFE Night",
    "wrong_answers": [
      "GUT KNIFE Night",
      "FLIP KNIFE Night",
      "FALCHION KNIFE Night"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Qual é o nome desta faca?",
    "picture": "https://res.cloudinary.com/dwm53cbu2/image/upload/a_320/a_hflip/w_1000,f_auto,q_auto:low,fl_lossy,fl_progressive,fl_strip_profile/v1760720439/FALCHION_KNIFE-Forest_DDPAT_oms2yk.webp",
    "correct_answer": "FALCHION KNIFE Forest DDPAT",
    "wrong_answers": [
      "PARACORD KNIFE Forest DDPAT",
      "URSUS KNIFE Forest DDPAT",
      "TALON KNIFE Forest DDPAT"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Qual é o nome desta faca?",
    "picture": "https://res.cloudinary.com/dwm53cbu2/image/upload/a_320/a_hflip/w_1000,f_auto,q_auto:low,fl_lossy,fl_progressive,fl_strip_profile/v1760720437/FALCHION_KNIFE-Doppler_Sapphire_hn40do.webp",
    "correct_answer": "FALCHION KNIFE Doppler Sapphire",
    "wrong_answers": [
      "URSUS KNIFE Doppler Sapphire",
      "NAJAVA KNIFE Doppler Sapphire",
      "TALON KNIFE Doppler Sapphire"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Qual é o nome desta faca?",
    "picture": "https://res.cloudinary.com/dwm53cbu2/image/upload/a_320/a_hflip/w_1000,f_auto,q_auto:low,fl_lossy,fl_progressive,fl_strip_profile/v1760720436/STILETTO_KNIFE-Crimson_Web_ne4r3n.webp",
    "correct_answer": "STILETTO KNIFE Crimson Web",
    "wrong_answers": [
      "PARACORD KNIFE Crimson Web",
      "URSUS KNIFE Crimson Web",
      "HUNTSMAN KNIFE Crimson Web"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Qual é o nome desta faca?",
    "picture": "https://res.cloudinary.com/dwm53cbu2/image/upload/a_320/a_hflip/w_1000,f_auto,q_auto:low,fl_lossy,fl_progressive,fl_strip_profile/v1760720433/STILETTO_KNIFE-Boreal_Forest_copr5l.webp",
    "correct_answer": "STILETTO KNIFE Boreal Forest",
    "wrong_answers": [
      "PARACORD KNIFE Boreal Forest",
      "URSUS KNIFE Boreal Forest",
      "NOMAD KNIFE Boreal Forest"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Qual é o nome desta faca?",
    "picture": "https://res.cloudinary.com/dwm53cbu2/image/upload/a_320/a_hflip/w_1000,f_auto,q_auto:low,fl_lossy,fl_progressive,fl_strip_profile/v1760720431/BOWIE_KNIFE-Black_Laminate_sbcydl.webp",
    "correct_answer": "BOWIE KNIFE Black Laminate",
    "wrong_answers": [
      "HUNTSMAN KNIFE Black Laminate",
      "GUT KNIFE Black Laminate",
      "FALCHION KNIFE Black Laminate"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Qual é o nome desta faca?",
    "picture": "https://res.cloudinary.com/dwm53cbu2/image/upload/a_320/a_hflip/w_1000,f_auto,q_auto:low,fl_lossy,fl_progressive,fl_strip_profile/v1760720431/SKELETON-Ultraviolet_w4gudw.webp",
    "correct_answer": "SKELETON Ultraviolet",
    "wrong_answers": [
      "KARAMBIT Ultraviolet",
      "BAYONET Ultraviolet",
      "SKELETON Rust Coat"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Qual é o nome desta faca?",
    "picture": "https://res.cloudinary.com/dwm53cbu2/image/upload/a_320/a_hflip/w_1000,f_auto,q_auto:low,fl_lossy,fl_progressive,fl_strip_profile/v1760720428/SKELETON-Stained_k1d1wk.webp",
    "correct_answer": "SKELETON Stained",
    "wrong_answers": [
      "KARAMBIT Stained",
      "BAYONET Stained",
      "SKELETON Rust Coat"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Qual é o nome desta faca?",
    "picture": "https://res.cloudinary.com/dwm53cbu2/image/upload/a_320/a_hflip/w_1000,f_auto,q_auto:low,fl_lossy,fl_progressive,fl_strip_profile/v1760720427/FALCHION_KNIFE-Doppler_Phase_2_nsbah0.webp",
    "correct_answer": "FALCHION KNIFE Doppler Phase 2",
    "wrong_answers": [
      "NAJAVA KNIFE Doppler Phase 2",
      "URSUS KNIFE Doppler Phase 2",
      "TALON KNIFE Doppler Phase 2"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Qual é o nome desta faca?",
    "picture": "https://res.cloudinary.com/dwm53cbu2/image/upload/a_320/a_hflip/w_1000,f_auto,q_auto:low,fl_lossy,fl_progressive,fl_strip_profile/v1760720424/BOWIE_KNIFE-Vanilla_ysubcv.webp",
    "correct_answer": "BOWIE KNIFE Vanilla",
    "wrong_answers": [
      "URSUS KNIFE Vanilla",
      "PARACORD KNIFE Vanilla",
      "NAJAVA KNIFE Vanilla"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Qual é o nome desta faca?",
    "picture": "https://res.cloudinary.com/dwm53cbu2/image/upload/a_320/a_hflip/w_1000,f_auto,q_auto:low,fl_lossy,fl_progressive,fl_strip_profile/v1760720423/SKELETON-Night_Stripe_cvesnv.webp",
    "correct_answer": "SKELETON Night Stripe",
    "wrong_answers": [
      "SKELETON Rust Coat",
      "SKELETON Vanilla",
      "SKELETON Doppler Ruby"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Qual é o nome desta faca?",
    "picture": "https://res.cloudinary.com/dwm53cbu2/image/upload/a_320/a_hflip/w_1000,f_auto,q_auto:low,fl_lossy,fl_progressive,fl_strip_profile/v1760720421/FALCHION_KNIFE-Doppler_Phase_1_ans4iu.webp",
    "correct_answer": "FALCHION KNIFE Doppler Phase 1",
    "wrong_answers": [
      "URSUS KNIFE Doppler Phase 1",
      "NAJAVA KNIFE Doppler Phase 1",
      "PARACORD KNIFE Doppler Phase 1"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Qual é o nome desta faca?",
    "picture": "https://res.cloudinary.com/dwm53cbu2/image/upload/a_320/a_hflip/w_1000,f_auto,q_auto:low,fl_lossy,fl_progressive,fl_strip_profile/v1760720419/SKELETON-Blue_Steel_qy37wx.webp",
    "correct_answer": "SKELETON Blue Steel",
    "wrong_answers": [
      "KARAMBIT Blue Steel",
      "BAYONET Blue Steel",
      "SKELETON Rust Coat"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Qual é o nome desta faca?",
    "picture": "https://res.cloudinary.com/dwm53cbu2/image/upload/a_320/a_hflip/w_1000,f_auto,q_auto:low,fl_lossy,fl_progressive,fl_strip_profile/v1760720418/FALCHION_KNIFE-Damascus_Steel_l7wkal.webp",
    "correct_answer": "FALCHION KNIFE Damascus Steel",
    "wrong_answers": [
      "NAJAVA KNIFE Damascus Steel",
      "GUT KNIFE Damascus Steel",
      "URSUS KNIFE Damascus Steel"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Qual é o nome desta faca?",
    "picture": "https://res.cloudinary.com/dwm53cbu2/image/upload/a_320/a_hflip/w_1000,f_auto,q_auto:low,fl_lossy,fl_progressive,fl_strip_profile/v1760720416/BOWIE_KNIFE-Tiger_Tooth_mwz3rl.webp",
    "correct_answer": "BOWIE KNIFE Tiger Tooth",
    "wrong_answers": [
      "URSUS KNIFE Tiger Tooth",
      "NAJAVA KNIFE Tiger Tooth",
      "PARACORD KNIFE Tiger Tooth"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Qual é o nome desta faca?",
    "picture": "https://res.cloudinary.com/dwm53cbu2/image/upload/a_320/a_hflip/w_1000,f_auto,q_auto:low,fl_lossy,fl_progressive,fl_strip_profile/v1760720414/FALCHION_KNIFE-Boreal_Forest_u9imzu.webp",
    "correct_answer": "FALCHION KNIFE Boreal Forest",
    "wrong_answers": [
      "PARACORD KNIFE Boreal Forest",
      "URSUS KNIFE Boreal Forest",
      "NOMAD KNIFE Boreal Forest"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Qual é o nome desta faca?",
    "picture": "https://res.cloudinary.com/dwm53cbu2/image/upload/a_320/a_hflip/w_1000,f_auto,q_auto:low,fl_lossy,fl_progressive,fl_strip_profile/v1760720412/FALCHION_KNIFE-Crimson_Web_n8tcrh.webp",
    "correct_answer": "FALCHION KNIFE Crimson Web",
    "wrong_answers": [
      "PARACORD KNIFE Crimson Web",
      "URSUS KNIFE Crimson Web",
      "HUNTSMAN KNIFE Crimson Web"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Qual é o nome desta faca?",
    "picture": "https://res.cloudinary.com/dwm53cbu2/image/upload/a_320/a_hflip/w_1000,f_auto,q_auto:low,fl_lossy,fl_progressive,fl_strip_profile/v1760720410/CLASSIC_KNIFE-Urban_Masked_mdgbu5.webp",
    "correct_answer": "CLASSIC KNIFE Urban Masked",
    "wrong_answers": [
      "PARACORD KNIFE Urban Masked",
      "NOMAD KNIFE Urban Masked",
      "URSUS KNIFE Urban Masked"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Qual é o nome desta faca?",
    "picture": "https://res.cloudinary.com/dwm53cbu2/image/upload/a_320/a_hflip/w_1000,f_auto,q_auto:low,fl_lossy,fl_progressive,fl_strip_profile/v1760720408/CLASSIC_KNIFE-Vanilla_jaim7w.webp",
    "correct_answer": "CLASSIC KNIFE Vanilla",
    "wrong_answers": [
      "URSUS KNIFE Vanilla",
      "PARACORD KNIFE Vanilla",
      "NAJAVA KNIFE Vanilla"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Qual é o nome desta faca?",
    "picture": "https://res.cloudinary.com/dwm53cbu2/image/upload/a_320/a_hflip/w_1000,f_auto,q_auto:low,fl_lossy,fl_progressive,fl_strip_profile/v1760720407/CLASSIC_KNIFE-Slaughter_yr5hot.webp",
    "correct_answer": "CLASSIC KNIFE Slaughter",
    "wrong_answers": [
      "URSUS KNIFE Slaughter",
      "PARACORD KNIFE Slaughter",
      "NAJAVA KNIFE Slaughter"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Qual é o nome desta faca?",
    "picture": "https://res.cloudinary.com/dwm53cbu2/image/upload/a_320/a_hflip/w_1000,f_auto,q_auto:low,fl_lossy,fl_progressive,fl_strip_profile/v1760720405/GUT_KNIFE-Ultraviolet_mqjlq0.webp",
    "correct_answer": "GUT KNIFE Ultraviolet",
    "wrong_answers": [
      "PARACORD KNIFE Ultraviolet",
      "NOMAD KNIFE Ultraviolet",
      "URSUS KNIFE Ultraviolet"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Qual é o nome desta faca?",
    "picture": "https://res.cloudinary.com/dwm53cbu2/image/upload/a_320/a_hflip/w_1000,f_auto,q_auto:low,fl_lossy,fl_progressive,fl_strip_profile/v1760720403/GUT_KNIFE-Scorched_phmljr.webp",
    "correct_answer": "GUT KNIFE Scorched",
    "wrong_answers": [
      "URSUS KNIFE Scorched",
      "PARACORD KNIFE Scorched",
      "NOMAD KNIFE Scorched"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Qual é o nome desta faca?",
    "picture": "https://res.cloudinary.com/dwm53cbu2/image/upload/a_320/a_hflip/w_1000,f_auto,q_auto:low,fl_lossy,fl_progressive,fl_strip_profile/v1760720401/CLASSIC_KNIFE-Scorched_fxbqiy.webp",
    "correct_answer": "CLASSIC KNIFE Scorched",
    "wrong_answers": [
      "URSUS KNIFE Scorched",
      "PARACORD KNIFE Scorched",
      "NOMAD KNIFE Scorched"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Qual é o nome desta faca?",
    "picture": "https://res.cloudinary.com/dwm53cbu2/image/upload/a_320/a_hflip/w_1000,f_auto,q_auto:low,fl_lossy,fl_progressive,fl_strip_profile/v1760720399/GUT_KNIFE-Night_yxi85j.webp",
    "correct_answer": "GUT KNIFE Night",
    "wrong_answers": [
      "HUNTSMAN KNIFE Night",
      "FLIP KNIFE Night",
      "FALCHION KNIFE Night"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Qual é o nome desta faca?",
    "picture": "https://res.cloudinary.com/dwm53cbu2/image/upload/a_320/a_hflip/w_1000,f_auto,q_auto:low,fl_lossy,fl_progressive,fl_strip_profile/v1760720398/CLASSIC_KNIFE-Forest_DDPAT_vpvget.webp",
    "correct_answer": "CLASSIC KNIFE Forest DDPAT",
    "wrong_answers": [
      "PARACORD KNIFE Forest DDPAT",
      "URSUS KNIFE Forest DDPAT",
      "TALON KNIFE Forest DDPAT"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Qual é o nome desta faca?",
    "picture": "https://res.cloudinary.com/dwm53cbu2/image/upload/a_320/a_hflip/w_1000,f_auto,q_auto:low,fl_lossy,fl_progressive,fl_strip_profile/v1760720396/CLASSIC_KNIFE-Crimson_Web_tg4ssn.webp",
    "correct_answer": "CLASSIC KNIFE Crimson Web",
    "wrong_answers": [
      "PARACORD KNIFE Crimson Web",
      "URSUS KNIFE Crimson Web",
      "HUNTSMAN KNIFE Crimson Web"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Qual é o nome desta faca?",
    "picture": "https://res.cloudinary.com/dwm53cbu2/image/upload/a_320/a_hflip/w_1000,f_auto,q_auto:low,fl_lossy,fl_progressive,fl_strip_profile/v1760720393/BOWIE_KNIFE-Marble_Fade_i524jt.webp",
    "correct_answer": "BOWIE KNIFE Marble Fade",
    "wrong_answers": [
      "URSUS KNIFE Marble Fade",
      "PARACORD KNIFE Marble Fade",
      "NAJAVA KNIFE Marble Fade"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Qual é o nome desta faca?",
    "picture": "https://res.cloudinary.com/dwm53cbu2/image/upload/a_320/a_hflip/w_1000,f_auto,q_auto:low,fl_lossy,fl_progressive,fl_strip_profile/v1760720392/CLASSIC_KNIFE-Boreal_Forest_chmtw8.webp",
    "correct_answer": "CLASSIC KNIFE Boreal Forest",
    "wrong_answers": [
      "PARACORD KNIFE Boreal Forest",
      "URSUS KNIFE Boreal Forest",
      "NOMAD KNIFE Boreal Forest"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Qual é o nome desta faca?",
    "picture": "https://res.cloudinary.com/dwm53cbu2/image/upload/a_320/a_hflip/w_1000,f_auto,q_auto:low,fl_lossy,fl_progressive,fl_strip_profile/v1760720390/BOWIE_KNIFE-Gamma_Doppler_Phase_3_kpvdy6.webp",
    "correct_answer": "BOWIE KNIFE Gamma Doppler Phase 3",
    "wrong_answers": [
      "HUNTSMAN KNIFE Gamma Doppler Phase 3",
      "GUT KNIFE Gamma Doppler Phase 3",
      "FALCHION KNIFE Gamma Doppler Phase 3"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Qual é o nome desta faca?",
    "picture": "https://res.cloudinary.com/dwm53cbu2/image/upload/a_320/a_hflip/w_1000,f_auto,q_auto:low,fl_lossy,fl_progressive,fl_strip_profile/v1760720389/BOWIE_KNIFE-Gamma_Doppler_Phase_4_vwnqmx.webp",
    "correct_answer": "BOWIE KNIFE Gamma Doppler Phase 4",
    "wrong_answers": [
      "GUT KNIFE Gamma Doppler Phase 4",
      "FLIP KNIFE Gamma Doppler Phase 4",
      "HUNTSMAN KNIFE Gamma Doppler Phase 4"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Qual é o nome desta faca?",
    "picture": "https://res.cloudinary.com/dwm53cbu2/image/upload/a_320/a_hflip/w_1000,f_auto,q_auto:low,fl_lossy,fl_progressive,fl_strip_profile/v1760720387/CLASSIC_KNIFE-Case_Hardened_eks2li.webp",
    "correct_answer": "CLASSIC KNIFE Case Hardened",
    "wrong_answers": [
      "NAJAVA KNIFE Case Hardened",
      "URSUS KNIFE Case Hardened",
      "TALON KNIFE Case Hardened"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Qual é o nome desta faca?",
    "picture": "https://res.cloudinary.com/dwm53cbu2/image/upload/a_320/a_hflip/w_1000,f_auto,q_auto:low,fl_lossy,fl_progressive,fl_strip_profile/v1760720385/BOWIE_KNIFE-Gamma_Doppler_Phase_2_g8bwt0.webp",
    "correct_answer": "BOWIE KNIFE Gamma Doppler Phase 2",
    "wrong_answers": [
      "GUT KNIFE Gamma Doppler Phase 2",
      "FLIP KNIFE Gamma Doppler Phase 2",
      "HUNTSMAN KNIFE Gamma Doppler Phase 2"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Qual é o nome desta faca?",
    "picture": "https://res.cloudinary.com/dwm53cbu2/image/upload/a_320/a_hflip/w_1000,f_auto,q_auto:low,fl_lossy,fl_progressive,fl_strip_profile/v1760720383/BUTTERFLY_KNIFE-Tiger_Tooth_jzosid.webp",
    "correct_answer": "BUTTERFLY KNIFE Tiger Tooth",
    "wrong_answers": [
      "URSUS KNIFE Tiger Tooth",
      "NAJAVA KNIFE Tiger Tooth",
      "PARACORD KNIFE Tiger Tooth"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Qual é o nome desta faca?",
    "picture": "https://res.cloudinary.com/dwm53cbu2/image/upload/a_320/a_hflip/w_1000,f_auto,q_auto:low,fl_lossy,fl_progressive,fl_strip_profile/v1760720381/BOWIE_KNIFE-Gamma_Doppler_Phase_1_iol3h1.webp",
    "correct_answer": "BOWIE KNIFE Gamma Doppler Phase 1",
    "wrong_answers": [
      "HUNTSMAN KNIFE Gamma Doppler Phase 1",
      "GUT KNIFE Gamma Doppler Phase 1",
      "FALCHION KNIFE Gamma Doppler Phase 1"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Qual é o nome desta faca?",
    "picture": "https://res.cloudinary.com/dwm53cbu2/image/upload/a_320/a_hflip/w_1000,f_auto,q_auto:low,fl_lossy,fl_progressive,fl_strip_profile/v1760720380/NAJAVA_KNIFE-Ultraviolet_vecjzo.webp",
    "correct_answer": "NAJAVA KNIFE Ultraviolet",
    "wrong_answers": [
      "PARACORD KNIFE Ultraviolet",
      "NOMAD KNIFE Ultraviolet",
      "URSUS KNIFE Ultraviolet"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Qual é o nome desta faca?",
    "picture": "https://res.cloudinary.com/dwm53cbu2/image/upload/a_320/a_hflip/w_1000,f_auto,q_auto:low,fl_lossy,fl_progressive,fl_strip_profile/v1760720378/BOWIE_KNIFE-Gamma_Doppler_Emerald_ayzvhv.webp",
    "correct_answer": "BOWIE KNIFE Gamma Doppler Emerald",
    "wrong_answers": [
      "GUT KNIFE Gamma Doppler Emerald",
      "FLIP KNIFE Gamma Doppler Emerald",
      "HUNTSMAN KNIFE Gamma Doppler Emerald"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Qual é o nome desta faca?",
    "picture": "https://res.cloudinary.com/dwm53cbu2/image/upload/a_320/a_hflip/w_1000,f_auto,q_auto:low,fl_lossy,fl_progressive,fl_strip_profile/v1760720376/NAJAVA_KNIFE-Safari_Mesh_zrldo4.webp",
    "correct_answer": "NAJAVA KNIFE Safari Mesh",
    "wrong_answers": [
      "PARACORD KNIFE Safari Mesh",
      "NOMAD KNIFE Safari Mesh",
      "URSUS KNIFE Safari Mesh"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Qual é o nome desta faca?",
    "picture": "https://res.cloudinary.com/dwm53cbu2/image/upload/a_320/a_hflip/w_1000,f_auto,q_auto:low,fl_lossy,fl_progressive,fl_strip_profile/v1760720374/NAJAVA_KNIFE-Scorched_jjjhma.webp",
    "correct_answer": "NAJAVA KNIFE Scorched",
    "wrong_answers": [
      "URSUS KNIFE Scorched",
      "PARACORD KNIFE Scorched",
      "NOMAD KNIFE Scorched"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Qual é o nome desta faca?",
    "picture": "https://res.cloudinary.com/dwm53cbu2/image/upload/a_320/a_hflip/w_1000,f_auto,q_auto:low,fl_lossy,fl_progressive,fl_strip_profile/v1760720372/NAJAVA_KNIFE-Night_Stripe_lrjliq.webp",
    "correct_answer": "NAJAVA KNIFE Night Stripe",
    "wrong_answers": [
      "NOMAD KNIFE Night Stripe",
      "URSUS KNIFE Night Stripe",
      "PARACORD KNIFE Night Stripe"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Qual é o nome desta faca?",
    "picture": "https://res.cloudinary.com/dwm53cbu2/image/upload/a_320/a_hflip/w_1000,f_auto,q_auto:low,fl_lossy,fl_progressive,fl_strip_profile/v1760720371/BOWIE_KNIFE-Freehand_wiiyit.webp",
    "correct_answer": "BOWIE KNIFE Freehand",
    "wrong_answers": [
      "GUT KNIFE Freehand",
      "HUNTSMAN KNIFE Freehand",
      "FLIP KNIFE Freehand"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Qual é o nome desta faca?",
    "picture": "https://res.cloudinary.com/dwm53cbu2/image/upload/a_320/a_hflip/w_1000,f_auto,q_auto:low,fl_lossy,fl_progressive,fl_strip_profile/v1760720369/BUTTERFLY_KNIFE-Marble_Fade_ifqxez.webp",
    "correct_answer": "BUTTERFLY KNIFE Marble Fade",
    "wrong_answers": [
      "URSUS KNIFE Marble Fade",
      "PARACORD KNIFE Marble Fade",
      "NAJAVA KNIFE Marble Fade"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Qual é o nome desta faca?",
    "picture": "https://res.cloudinary.com/dwm53cbu2/image/upload/a_320/a_hflip/w_1000,f_auto,q_auto:low,fl_lossy,fl_progressive,fl_strip_profile/v1760720367/BUTTERFLY_KNIFE-Gamma_Doppler_Phase_3_blcctv.webp",
    "correct_answer": "BUTTERFLY KNIFE Gamma Doppler Phase 3",
    "wrong_answers": [
      "HUNTSMAN KNIFE Gamma Doppler Phase 3",
      "GUT KNIFE Gamma Doppler Phase 3",
      "FALCHION KNIFE Gamma Doppler Phase 3"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Qual é o nome desta faca?",
    "picture": "https://res.cloudinary.com/dwm53cbu2/image/upload/a_320/a_hflip/w_1000,f_auto,q_auto:low,fl_lossy,fl_progressive,fl_strip_profile/v1760720365/BUTTERFLY_KNIFE-Gamma_Doppler_Phase_1_hhjwja.webp",
    "correct_answer": "BUTTERFLY KNIFE Gamma Doppler Phase 1",
    "wrong_answers": [
      "HUNTSMAN KNIFE Gamma Doppler Phase 1",
      "GUT KNIFE Gamma Doppler Phase 1",
      "FALCHION KNIFE Gamma Doppler Phase 1"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Qual é o nome desta faca?",
    "picture": "https://res.cloudinary.com/dwm53cbu2/image/upload/a_320/a_hflip/w_1000,f_auto,q_auto:low,fl_lossy,fl_progressive,fl_strip_profile/v1760720363/BUTTERFLY_KNIFE-Gamma_Doppler_Emerald_c9w6cq.webp",
    "correct_answer": "BUTTERFLY KNIFE Gamma Doppler Emerald",
    "wrong_answers": [
      "GUT KNIFE Gamma Doppler Emerald",
      "FLIP KNIFE Gamma Doppler Emerald",
      "HUNTSMAN KNIFE Gamma Doppler Emerald"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Qual é o nome desta faca?",
    "picture": "https://res.cloudinary.com/dwm53cbu2/image/upload/a_320/a_hflip/w_1000,f_auto,q_auto:low,fl_lossy,fl_progressive,fl_strip_profile/v1760720361/BUTTERFLY_KNIFE-Gamma_Doppler_Phase_2_swh3pg.webp",
    "correct_answer": "BUTTERFLY KNIFE Gamma Doppler Phase 2",
    "wrong_answers": [
      "GUT KNIFE Gamma Doppler Phase 2",
      "FLIP KNIFE Gamma Doppler Phase 2",
      "HUNTSMAN KNIFE Gamma Doppler Phase 2"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Qual é o nome desta faca?",
    "picture": "https://res.cloudinary.com/dwm53cbu2/image/upload/a_320/a_hflip/w_1000,f_auto,q_auto:low,fl_lossy,fl_progressive,fl_strip_profile/v1760720360/BOWIE_KNIFE-Doppler_Phase_2_rax5ss.webp",
    "correct_answer": "BOWIE KNIFE Doppler Phase 2",
    "wrong_answers": [
      "NAJAVA KNIFE Doppler Phase 2",
      "URSUS KNIFE Doppler Phase 2",
      "TALON KNIFE Doppler Phase 2"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Qual é o nome desta faca?",
    "picture": "https://res.cloudinary.com/dwm53cbu2/image/upload/a_320/a_hflip/w_1000,f_auto,q_auto:low,fl_lossy,fl_progressive,fl_strip_profile/v1760720358/FLIP_KNIFE-Night_fce5ek.webp",
    "correct_answer": "FLIP KNIFE Night",
    "wrong_answers": [
      "HUNTSMAN KNIFE Night",
      "GUT KNIFE Night",
      "FALCHION KNIFE Night"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Qual é o nome desta faca?",
    "picture": "https://res.cloudinary.com/dwm53cbu2/image/upload/a_320/a_hflip/w_1000,f_auto,q_auto:low,fl_lossy,fl_progressive,fl_strip_profile/v1760720356/BUTTERFLY_KNIFE-Freehand_x9mqok.webp",
    "correct_answer": "BUTTERFLY KNIFE Freehand",
    "wrong_answers": [
      "GUT KNIFE Freehand",
      "HUNTSMAN KNIFE Freehand",
      "FLIP KNIFE Freehand"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Qual é o nome desta faca?",
    "picture": "https://res.cloudinary.com/dwm53cbu2/image/upload/a_320/a_hflip/w_1000,f_auto,q_auto:low,fl_lossy,fl_progressive,fl_strip_profile/v1760720354/BUTTERFLY_KNIFE-Doppler_Sapphire_lwgacj.webp",
    "correct_answer": "BUTTERFLY KNIFE Doppler Sapphire",
    "wrong_answers": [
      "URSUS KNIFE Doppler Sapphire",
      "NAJAVA KNIFE Doppler Sapphire",
      "TALON KNIFE Doppler Sapphire"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Qual é o nome desta faca?",
    "picture": "https://res.cloudinary.com/dwm53cbu2/image/upload/a_320/a_hflip/w_1000,f_auto,q_auto:low,fl_lossy,fl_progressive,fl_strip_profile/v1760720353/BOWIE_KNIFE-Doppler_Phase_1_zxifrj.webp",
    "correct_answer": "BOWIE KNIFE Doppler Phase 1",
    "wrong_answers": [
      "URSUS KNIFE Doppler Phase 1",
      "NAJAVA KNIFE Doppler Phase 1",
      "PARACORD KNIFE Doppler Phase 1"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Qual é o nome desta faca?",
    "picture": "https://res.cloudinary.com/dwm53cbu2/image/upload/a_320/a_hflip/w_1000,f_auto,q_auto:low,fl_lossy,fl_progressive,fl_strip_profile/v1760720350/BUTTERFLY_KNIFE-Doppler_Ruby_viphg3.webp",
    "correct_answer": "BUTTERFLY KNIFE Doppler Ruby",
    "wrong_answers": [
      "URSUS KNIFE Doppler Ruby",
      "NAJAVA KNIFE Doppler Ruby",
      "TALON KNIFE Doppler Ruby"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Qual é o nome desta faca?",
    "picture": "https://res.cloudinary.com/dwm53cbu2/image/upload/a_320/a_hflip/w_1000,f_auto,q_auto:low,fl_lossy,fl_progressive,fl_strip_profile/v1760720349/BUTTERFLY_KNIFE-Doppler_Phase_2_btc8cp.webp",
    "correct_answer": "BUTTERFLY KNIFE Doppler Phase 2",
    "wrong_answers": [
      "NAJAVA KNIFE Doppler Phase 2",
      "URSUS KNIFE Doppler Phase 2",
      "TALON KNIFE Doppler Phase 2"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Qual é o nome desta faca?",
    "picture": "https://res.cloudinary.com/dwm53cbu2/image/upload/a_320/a_hflip/w_1000,f_auto,q_auto:low,fl_lossy,fl_progressive,fl_strip_profile/v1760720347/BOWIE_KNIFE-Damascus_Steel_aijwd3.webp",
    "correct_answer": "BOWIE KNIFE Damascus Steel",
    "wrong_answers": [
      "NAJAVA KNIFE Damascus Steel",
      "GUT KNIFE Damascus Steel",
      "URSUS KNIFE Damascus Steel"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Qual é o nome desta faca?",
    "picture": "https://res.cloudinary.com/dwm53cbu2/image/upload/a_320/a_hflip/w_1000,f_auto,q_auto:low,fl_lossy,fl_progressive,fl_strip_profile/v1760720345/BUTTERFLY_KNIFE-Doppler_Phase_1_xazwjr.webp",
    "correct_answer": "BUTTERFLY KNIFE Doppler Phase 1",
    "wrong_answers": [
      "URSUS KNIFE Doppler Phase 1",
      "NAJAVA KNIFE Doppler Phase 1",
      "PARACORD KNIFE Doppler Phase 1"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Qual é o nome desta faca?",
    "picture": "https://res.cloudinary.com/dwm53cbu2/image/upload/a_320/a_hflip/w_1000,f_auto,q_auto:low,fl_lossy,fl_progressive,fl_strip_profile/v1760720344/BUTTERFLY_KNIFE-Case_Hardened_gyml7h.webp",
    "correct_answer": "BUTTERFLY KNIFE Case Hardened",
    "wrong_answers": [
      "NAJAVA KNIFE Case Hardened",
      "URSUS KNIFE Case Hardened",
      "TALON KNIFE Case Hardened"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Qual é o nome desta faca?",
    "picture": "https://res.cloudinary.com/dwm53cbu2/image/upload/a_320/a_hflip/w_1000,f_auto,q_auto:low,fl_lossy,fl_progressive,fl_strip_profile/v1760720342/BUTTERFLY_KNIFE-Damascus_Steel_hcvxxd.webp",
    "correct_answer": "BUTTERFLY KNIFE Damascus Steel",
    "wrong_answers": [
      "NAJAVA KNIFE Damascus Steel",
      "GUT KNIFE Damascus Steel",
      "URSUS KNIFE Damascus Steel"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Qual é o nome desta faca?",
    "picture": "https://res.cloudinary.com/dwm53cbu2/image/upload/a_320/a_hflip/w_1000,f_auto,q_auto:low,fl_lossy,fl_progressive,fl_strip_profile/v1760720339/BOWIE_KNIFE-Case_Hardened_zdbsqw.webp",
    "correct_answer": "BOWIE KNIFE Case Hardened",
    "wrong_answers": [
      "NAJAVA KNIFE Case Hardened",
      "URSUS KNIFE Case Hardened",
      "TALON KNIFE Case Hardened"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Qual é o nome desta faca?",
    "picture": "https://res.cloudinary.com/dwm53cbu2/image/upload/a_320/a_hflip/w_1000,f_auto,q_auto:low,fl_lossy,fl_progressive,fl_strip_profile/v1760720339/FALCHION_KNIFE-Urban_Masked_rqiyj3.webp",
    "correct_answer": "FALCHION KNIFE Urban Masked",
    "wrong_answers": [
      "PARACORD KNIFE Urban Masked",
      "NOMAD KNIFE Urban Masked",
      "URSUS KNIFE Urban Masked"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Qual é o nome desta faca?",
    "picture": "https://res.cloudinary.com/dwm53cbu2/image/upload/a_320/a_hflip/w_1000,f_auto,q_auto:low,fl_lossy,fl_progressive,fl_strip_profile/v1760720336/FALCHION_KNIFE-Slaughter_ye8cea.webp",
    "correct_answer": "FALCHION KNIFE Slaughter",
    "wrong_answers": [
      "URSUS KNIFE Slaughter",
      "PARACORD KNIFE Slaughter",
      "NAJAVA KNIFE Slaughter"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Qual é o nome desta faca?",
    "picture": "https://res.cloudinary.com/dwm53cbu2/image/upload/a_320/a_hflip/w_1000,f_auto,q_auto:low,fl_lossy,fl_progressive,fl_strip_profile/v1760720334/BUTTERFLY_KNIFE-Boreal_Forest_tdvfzm.webp",
    "correct_answer": "BUTTERFLY KNIFE Boreal Forest",
    "wrong_answers": [
      "PARACORD KNIFE Boreal Forest",
      "URSUS KNIFE Boreal Forest",
      "NOMAD KNIFE Boreal Forest"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Qual é o nome desta faca?",
    "picture": "https://res.cloudinary.com/dwm53cbu2/image/upload/a_320/a_hflip/w_1000,f_auto,q_auto:low,fl_lossy,fl_progressive,fl_strip_profile/v1760720333/BAYONET-Freehand_tgc1gm.webp",
    "correct_answer": "BAYONET Freehand",
    "wrong_answers": [
      "KARAMBIT Freehand",
      "BAYONET Lore",
      "BAYONET Rust Coat"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Qual é o nome desta faca?",
    "picture": "https://res.cloudinary.com/dwm53cbu2/image/upload/a_320/a_hflip/w_1000,f_auto,q_auto:low,fl_lossy,fl_progressive,fl_strip_profile/v1760720331/FALCHION_KNIFE-Safari_Mesh_lgmhta.webp",
    "correct_answer": "FALCHION KNIFE Safari Mesh",
    "wrong_answers": [
      "PARACORD KNIFE Safari Mesh",
      "NOMAD KNIFE Safari Mesh",
      "URSUS KNIFE Safari Mesh"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Qual é o nome desta faca?",
    "picture": "https://res.cloudinary.com/dwm53cbu2/image/upload/a_320/a_hflip/w_1000,f_auto,q_auto:low,fl_lossy,fl_progressive,fl_strip_profile/v1760720329/FALCHION_KNIFE-Scorched_wsxovt.webp",
    "correct_answer": "FALCHION KNIFE Scorched",
    "wrong_answers": [
      "URSUS KNIFE Scorched",
      "PARACORD KNIFE Scorched",
      "NOMAD KNIFE Scorched"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Qual é o nome desta faca?",
    "picture": "https://res.cloudinary.com/dwm53cbu2/image/upload/a_320/a_hflip/w_1000,f_auto,q_auto:low,fl_lossy,fl_progressive,fl_strip_profile/v1760720327/STILETTO_KNIFE-Ultraviolet_wvxnx3.webp",
    "correct_answer": "STILETTO KNIFE Ultraviolet",
    "wrong_answers": [
      "PARACORD KNIFE Ultraviolet",
      "NOMAD KNIFE Ultraviolet",
      "URSUS KNIFE Ultraviolet"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Qual é o nome desta faca?",
    "picture": "https://res.cloudinary.com/dwm53cbu2/image/upload/a_320/a_hflip/w_1000,f_auto,q_auto:low,fl_lossy,fl_progressive,fl_strip_profile/v1760720326/STILETTO_KNIFE-Night_Stripe_oixqxe.webp",
    "correct_answer": "STILETTO KNIFE Night Stripe",
    "wrong_answers": [
      "NOMAD KNIFE Night Stripe",
      "URSUS KNIFE Night Stripe",
      "PARACORD KNIFE Night Stripe"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Qual é o nome desta faca?",
    "picture": "https://res.cloudinary.com/dwm53cbu2/image/upload/a_320/a_hflip/w_1000,f_auto,q_auto:low,fl_lossy,fl_progressive,fl_strip_profile/v1760720324/BOWIE_KNIFE-Urban_Masked_zrm9hg.webp",
    "correct_answer": "BOWIE KNIFE Urban Masked",
    "wrong_answers": [
      "PARACORD KNIFE Urban Masked",
      "NOMAD KNIFE Urban Masked",
      "URSUS KNIFE Urban Masked"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Qual é o nome desta faca?",
    "picture": "https://res.cloudinary.com/dwm53cbu2/image/upload/a_320/a_hflip/w_1000,f_auto,q_auto:low,fl_lossy,fl_progressive,fl_strip_profile/v1760720322/FALCHION_KNIFE-Fade_n5d8bt.webp",
    "correct_answer": "FALCHION KNIFE Fade",
    "wrong_answers": [
      "NAJAVA KNIFE Fade",
      "URSUS KNIFE Fade",
      "PARACORD KNIFE Fade"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Qual é o nome desta faca?",
    "picture": "https://res.cloudinary.com/dwm53cbu2/image/upload/a_320/a_hflip/w_1000,f_auto,q_auto:low,fl_lossy,fl_progressive,fl_strip_profile/v1760720320/FALCHION_KNIFE-Doppler_Phase_4_mxpqc1.webp",
    "correct_answer": "FALCHION KNIFE Doppler Phase 4",
    "wrong_answers": [
      "TALON KNIFE Doppler Phase 4",
      "URSUS KNIFE Doppler Phase 4",
      "PARACORD KNIFE Doppler Phase 4"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Qual é o nome desta faca?",
    "picture": "https://res.cloudinary.com/dwm53cbu2/image/upload/a_320/a_hflip/w_1000,f_auto,q_auto:low,fl_lossy,fl_progressive,fl_strip_profile/v1760720319/BAYONET-Vanilla_q6ndro.webp",
    "correct_answer": "BAYONET Vanilla",
    "wrong_answers": [
      "KARAMBIT Vanilla",
      "SKELETON Vanilla",
      "BAYONET Lore"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Qual é o nome desta faca?",
    "picture": "https://res.cloudinary.com/dwm53cbu2/image/upload/a_320/a_hflip/w_1000,f_auto,q_auto:low,fl_lossy,fl_progressive,fl_strip_profile/v1760720317/FALCHION_KNIFE-Doppler_Black_Pearl_sfl9gb.webp",
    "correct_answer": "FALCHION KNIFE Doppler Black Pearl",
    "wrong_answers": [
      "NAJAVA KNIFE Doppler Black Pearl",
      "URSUS KNIFE Doppler Black Pearl",
      "TALON KNIFE Doppler Black Pearl"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Qual é o nome desta faca?",
    "picture": "https://res.cloudinary.com/dwm53cbu2/image/upload/a_320/a_hflip/w_1000,f_auto,q_auto:low,fl_lossy,fl_progressive,fl_strip_profile/v1760720315/FALCHION_KNIFE-Doppler_Phase_3_ifjoqs.webp",
    "correct_answer": "FALCHION KNIFE Doppler Phase 3",
    "wrong_answers": [
      "NAJAVA KNIFE Doppler Phase 3",
      "URSUS KNIFE Doppler Phase 3",
      "PARACORD KNIFE Doppler Phase 3"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Qual é o nome desta faca?",
    "picture": "https://res.cloudinary.com/dwm53cbu2/image/upload/a_320/a_hflip/w_1000,f_auto,q_auto:low,fl_lossy,fl_progressive,fl_strip_profile/v1760720313/FALCHION_KNIFE-Bright_Water_rzsbuf.webp",
    "correct_answer": "FALCHION KNIFE Bright Water",
    "wrong_answers": [
      "HUNTSMAN KNIFE Bright Water",
      "GUT KNIFE Bright Water",
      "FLIP KNIFE Bright Water"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Qual é o nome desta faca?",
    "picture": "https://res.cloudinary.com/dwm53cbu2/image/upload/a_320/a_hflip/w_1000,f_auto,q_auto:low,fl_lossy,fl_progressive,fl_strip_profile/v1760720312/FALCHION_KNIFE-Blue_Steel_nx2c52.webp",
    "correct_answer": "FALCHION KNIFE Blue Steel",
    "wrong_answers": [
      "NAJAVA KNIFE Blue Steel",
      "URSUS KNIFE Blue Steel",
      "TALON KNIFE Blue Steel"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Qual é o nome desta faca?",
    "picture": "https://res.cloudinary.com/dwm53cbu2/image/upload/a_320/a_hflip/w_1000,f_auto,q_auto:low,fl_lossy,fl_progressive,fl_strip_profile/v1760720310/BOWIE_KNIFE-Stained_cdh95g.webp",
    "correct_answer": "BOWIE KNIFE Stained",
    "wrong_answers": [
      "NAJAVA KNIFE Stained",
      "PARACORD KNIFE Stained",
      "URSUS KNIFE Stained"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Qual é o nome desta faca?",
    "picture": "https://res.cloudinary.com/dwm53cbu2/image/upload/a_320/a_hflip/w_1000,f_auto,q_auto:low,fl_lossy,fl_progressive,fl_strip_profile/v1760720308/BOWIE_KNIFE-Slaughter_jfqaxk.webp",
    "correct_answer": "BOWIE KNIFE Slaughter",
    "wrong_answers": [
      "URSUS KNIFE Slaughter",
      "PARACORD KNIFE Slaughter",
      "NAJAVA KNIFE Slaughter"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Qual é o nome desta faca?",
    "picture": "https://res.cloudinary.com/dwm53cbu2/image/upload/a_320/a_hflip/w_1000,f_auto,q_auto:low,fl_lossy,fl_progressive,fl_strip_profile/v1760720306/BAYONET-Tiger_Tooth_edfa2u.webp",
    "correct_answer": "BAYONET Tiger Tooth",
    "wrong_answers": [
      "KARAMBIT Tiger Tooth",
      "SKELETON Tiger Tooth",
      "BAYONET Lore"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Qual é o nome desta faca?",
    "picture": "https://res.cloudinary.com/dwm53cbu2/image/upload/a_320/a_hflip/w_1000,f_auto,q_auto:low,fl_lossy,fl_progressive,fl_strip_profile/v1760720304/CLASSIC_KNIFE-Stained_tloiuo.webp",
    "correct_answer": "CLASSIC KNIFE Stained",
    "wrong_answers": [
      "NAJAVA KNIFE Stained",
      "PARACORD KNIFE Stained",
      "URSUS KNIFE Stained"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Qual é o nome desta faca?",
    "picture": "https://res.cloudinary.com/dwm53cbu2/image/upload/a_320/a_hflip/w_1000,f_auto,q_auto:low,fl_lossy,fl_progressive,fl_strip_profile/v1760720303/BOWIE_KNIFE-Safari_Mesh_wsv5iq.webp",
    "correct_answer": "BOWIE KNIFE Safari Mesh",
    "wrong_answers": [
      "PARACORD KNIFE Safari Mesh",
      "NOMAD KNIFE Safari Mesh",
      "URSUS KNIFE Safari Mesh"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Qual é o nome desta faca?",
    "picture": "https://res.cloudinary.com/dwm53cbu2/image/upload/a_320/a_hflip/w_1000,f_auto,q_auto:low,fl_lossy,fl_progressive,fl_strip_profile/v1760720300/CLASSIC_KNIFE-Safari_Mesh_n6krb4.webp",
    "correct_answer": "CLASSIC KNIFE Safari Mesh",
    "wrong_answers": [
      "PARACORD KNIFE Safari Mesh",
      "NOMAD KNIFE Safari Mesh",
      "URSUS KNIFE Safari Mesh"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Qual é o nome desta faca?",
    "picture": "https://res.cloudinary.com/dwm53cbu2/image/upload/a_320/a_hflip/w_1000,f_auto,q_auto:low,fl_lossy,fl_progressive,fl_strip_profile/v1760720299/CLASSIC_KNIFE-Night_Stripe_qeefpm.webp",
    "correct_answer": "CLASSIC KNIFE Night Stripe",
    "wrong_answers": [
      "NOMAD KNIFE Night Stripe",
      "URSUS KNIFE Night Stripe",
      "PARACORD KNIFE Night Stripe"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Qual é o nome desta faca?",
    "picture": "https://res.cloudinary.com/dwm53cbu2/image/upload/a_320/a_hflip/w_1000,f_auto,q_auto:low,fl_lossy,fl_progressive,fl_strip_profile/v1760720297/CLASSIC_KNIFE-Fade_xhudqn.webp",
    "correct_answer": "CLASSIC KNIFE Fade",
    "wrong_answers": [
      "NAJAVA KNIFE Fade",
      "URSUS KNIFE Fade",
      "PARACORD KNIFE Fade"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Qual é o nome desta faca?",
    "picture": "https://res.cloudinary.com/dwm53cbu2/image/upload/a_320/a_hflip/w_1000,f_auto,q_auto:low,fl_lossy,fl_progressive,fl_strip_profile/v1760720295/CLASSIC_KNIFE-Blue_Steel_u63ush.webp",
    "correct_answer": "CLASSIC KNIFE Blue Steel",
    "wrong_answers": [
      "NAJAVA KNIFE Blue Steel",
      "URSUS KNIFE Blue Steel",
      "TALON KNIFE Blue Steel"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Qual é o nome desta faca?",
    "picture": "https://res.cloudinary.com/dwm53cbu2/image/upload/a_320/a_hflip/w_1000,f_auto,q_auto:low,fl_lossy,fl_progressive,fl_strip_profile/v1760720294/BUTTERFLY_KNIFE-Vanilla_dyqhqr.webp",
    "correct_answer": "BUTTERFLY KNIFE Vanilla",
    "wrong_answers": [
      "URSUS KNIFE Vanilla",
      "PARACORD KNIFE Vanilla",
      "NAJAVA KNIFE Vanilla"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Qual é o nome desta faca?",
    "picture": "https://res.cloudinary.com/dwm53cbu2/image/upload/a_320/a_hflip/w_1000,f_auto,q_auto:low,fl_lossy,fl_progressive,fl_strip_profile/v1760720292/BUTTERFLY_KNIFE-Stained_yi5ylb.webp",
    "correct_answer": "BUTTERFLY KNIFE Stained",
    "wrong_answers": [
      "NAJAVA KNIFE Stained",
      "PARACORD KNIFE Stained",
      "URSUS KNIFE Stained"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Qual é o nome desta faca?",
    "picture": "https://res.cloudinary.com/dwm53cbu2/image/upload/a_320/a_hflip/w_1000,f_auto,q_auto:low,fl_lossy,fl_progressive,fl_strip_profile/v1760720289/BUTTERFLY_KNIFE-Urban_Masked_i5muyo.webp",
    "correct_answer": "BUTTERFLY KNIFE Urban Masked",
    "wrong_answers": [
      "PARACORD KNIFE Urban Masked",
      "NOMAD KNIFE Urban Masked",
      "URSUS KNIFE Urban Masked"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Qual é o nome desta faca?",
    "picture": "https://res.cloudinary.com/dwm53cbu2/image/upload/a_320/a_hflip/w_1000,f_auto,q_auto:low,fl_lossy,fl_progressive,fl_strip_profile/v1760720289/BUTTERFLY_KNIFE-Ultraviolet_tgrzzy.webp",
    "correct_answer": "BUTTERFLY KNIFE Ultraviolet",
    "wrong_answers": [
      "PARACORD KNIFE Ultraviolet",
      "NOMAD KNIFE Ultraviolet",
      "URSUS KNIFE Ultraviolet"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Qual é o nome desta faca?",
    "picture": "https://res.cloudinary.com/dwm53cbu2/image/upload/a_320/a_hflip/w_1000,f_auto,q_auto:low,fl_lossy,fl_progressive,fl_strip_profile/v1760720286/BUTTERFLY_KNIFE-Slaughter_f3xqhz.webp",
    "correct_answer": "BUTTERFLY KNIFE Slaughter",
    "wrong_answers": [
      "URSUS KNIFE Slaughter",
      "PARACORD KNIFE Slaughter",
      "NAJAVA KNIFE Slaughter"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Qual é o nome desta faca?",
    "picture": "https://res.cloudinary.com/dwm53cbu2/image/upload/a_320/a_hflip/w_1000,f_auto,q_auto:low,fl_lossy,fl_progressive,fl_strip_profile/v1760720285/BUTTERFLY_KNIFE-Scorched_caoxgw.webp",
    "correct_answer": "BUTTERFLY KNIFE Scorched",
    "wrong_answers": [
      "URSUS KNIFE Scorched",
      "PARACORD KNIFE Scorched",
      "NOMAD KNIFE Scorched"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Qual é o nome desta faca?",
    "picture": "https://res.cloudinary.com/dwm53cbu2/image/upload/a_320/a_hflip/w_1000,f_auto,q_auto:low,fl_lossy,fl_progressive,fl_strip_profile/v1760720283/BUTTERFLY_KNIFE-Safari_Mesh_xjs5q4.webp",
    "correct_answer": "BUTTERFLY KNIFE Safari Mesh",
    "wrong_answers": [
      "PARACORD KNIFE Safari Mesh",
      "NOMAD KNIFE Safari Mesh",
      "URSUS KNIFE Safari Mesh"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Qual é o nome desta faca?",
    "picture": "https://res.cloudinary.com/dwm53cbu2/image/upload/a_320/a_hflip/w_1000,f_auto,q_auto:low,fl_lossy,fl_progressive,fl_strip_profile/v1760720280/BOWIE_KNIFE-Doppler_Sapphire_gyuaac.webp",
    "correct_answer": "BOWIE KNIFE Doppler Sapphire",
    "wrong_answers": [
      "URSUS KNIFE Doppler Sapphire",
      "NAJAVA KNIFE Doppler Sapphire",
      "TALON KNIFE Doppler Sapphire"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Qual é o nome desta faca?",
    "picture": "https://res.cloudinary.com/dwm53cbu2/image/upload/a_320/a_hflip/w_1000,f_auto,q_auto:low,fl_lossy,fl_progressive,fl_strip_profile/v1760720279/BOWIE_KNIFE-Fade_z5slym.webp",
    "correct_answer": "BOWIE KNIFE Fade",
    "wrong_answers": [
      "NAJAVA KNIFE Fade",
      "URSUS KNIFE Fade",
      "PARACORD KNIFE Fade"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Qual é o nome desta faca?",
    "picture": "https://res.cloudinary.com/dwm53cbu2/image/upload/a_320/a_hflip/w_1000,f_auto,q_auto:low,fl_lossy,fl_progressive,fl_strip_profile/v1760720277/BOWIE_KNIFE-Doppler_Ruby_elhg5r.webp",
    "correct_answer": "BOWIE KNIFE Doppler Ruby",
    "wrong_answers": [
      "URSUS KNIFE Doppler Ruby",
      "NAJAVA KNIFE Doppler Ruby",
      "TALON KNIFE Doppler Ruby"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Qual é o nome desta faca?",
    "picture": "https://res.cloudinary.com/dwm53cbu2/image/upload/a_320/a_hflip/w_1000,f_auto,q_auto:low,fl_lossy,fl_progressive,fl_strip_profile/v1760720275/BOWIE_KNIFE-Doppler_Phase_4_hkw21q.webp",
    "correct_answer": "BOWIE KNIFE Doppler Phase 4",
    "wrong_answers": [
      "TALON KNIFE Doppler Phase 4",
      "URSUS KNIFE Doppler Phase 4",
      "PARACORD KNIFE Doppler Phase 4"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Qual é o nome desta faca?",
    "picture": "https://res.cloudinary.com/dwm53cbu2/image/upload/a_320/a_hflip/w_1000,f_auto,q_auto:low,fl_lossy,fl_progressive,fl_strip_profile/v1760720273/BAYONET-Marble_Fade_frgdbg.webp",
    "correct_answer": "BAYONET Marble Fade",
    "wrong_answers": [
      "KARAMBIT Marble Fade",
      "SKELETON Marble Fade",
      "BAYONET Lore"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Qual é o nome desta faca?",
    "picture": "https://res.cloudinary.com/dwm53cbu2/image/upload/a_320/a_hflip/w_1000,f_auto,q_auto:low,fl_lossy,fl_progressive,fl_strip_profile/v1760720272/BOWIE_KNIFE-Doppler_Phase_3_renfsl.webp",
    "correct_answer": "BOWIE KNIFE Doppler Phase 3",
    "wrong_answers": [
      "NAJAVA KNIFE Doppler Phase 3",
      "URSUS KNIFE Doppler Phase 3",
      "PARACORD KNIFE Doppler Phase 3"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Qual é o nome desta faca?",
    "picture": "https://res.cloudinary.com/dwm53cbu2/image/upload/a_320/a_hflip/w_1000,f_auto,q_auto:low,fl_lossy,fl_progressive,fl_strip_profile/v1760720270/BAYONET-Gamma_Doppler_Phase_3_eedy8t.webp",
    "correct_answer": "BAYONET Gamma Doppler Phase 3",
    "wrong_answers": [
      "KARAMBIT Gamma Doppler Phase 3",
      "BAYONET Gamma Doppler Phase 1",
      "BAYONET Gama Doppler Emerald"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Qual é o nome desta faca?",
    "picture": "https://res.cloudinary.com/dwm53cbu2/image/upload/a_320/a_hflip/w_1000,f_auto,q_auto:low,fl_lossy,fl_progressive,fl_strip_profile/v1760720269/BUTTERFLY_KNIFE-Forest_DDPAT_rnosqm.webp",
    "correct_answer": "BUTTERFLY KNIFE Forest DDPAT",
    "wrong_answers": [
      "PARACORD KNIFE Forest DDPAT",
      "URSUS KNIFE Forest DDPAT",
      "TALON KNIFE Forest DDPAT"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Qual é o nome desta faca?",
    "picture": "https://res.cloudinary.com/dwm53cbu2/image/upload/a_320/a_hflip/w_1000,f_auto,q_auto:low,fl_lossy,fl_progressive,fl_strip_profile/v1760720268/BUTTERFLY_KNIFE-Fade_ilbsrx.webp",
    "correct_answer": "BUTTERFLY KNIFE Fade",
    "wrong_answers": [
      "NAJAVA KNIFE Fade",
      "URSUS KNIFE Fade",
      "PARACORD KNIFE Fade"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Qual é o nome desta faca?",
    "picture": "https://res.cloudinary.com/dwm53cbu2/image/upload/a_320/a_hflip/w_1000,f_auto,q_auto:low,fl_lossy,fl_progressive,fl_strip_profile/v1760720265/BAYONET-Gamma_Doppler_Phase_1_iukrsf.webp",
    "correct_answer": "BAYONET Gamma Doppler Phase 1",
    "wrong_answers": [
      "KARAMBIT Gamma Doppler Phase 1",
      "BAYONET Gamma Doppler Phase 3",
      "BAYONET Gama Doppler Emerald"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Qual é o nome desta faca?",
    "picture": "https://res.cloudinary.com/dwm53cbu2/image/upload/a_320/a_hflip/w_1000,f_auto,q_auto:low,fl_lossy,fl_progressive,fl_strip_profile/v1760720263/BAYONET-Gama_Doppler_Emerald_hyhoss.webp",
    "correct_answer": "BAYONET Gama Doppler Emerald",
    "wrong_answers": [
      "BAYONET Gamma Doppler Phase 3",
      "BAYONET Gamma Doppler Phase 1",
      "BAYONET Gamma Doppler Phase 1"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Qual é o nome desta faca?",
    "picture": "https://res.cloudinary.com/dwm53cbu2/image/upload/a_320/a_hflip/w_1000,f_auto,q_auto:low,fl_lossy,fl_progressive,fl_strip_profile/v1760720261/BOWIE_KNIFE-Doppler_Black_Pearl_p8acor.webp",
    "correct_answer": "BOWIE KNIFE Doppler Black Pearl",
    "wrong_answers": [
      "NAJAVA KNIFE Doppler Black Pearl",
      "URSUS KNIFE Doppler Black Pearl",
      "TALON KNIFE Doppler Black Pearl"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Qual é o nome desta faca?",
    "picture": "https://res.cloudinary.com/dwm53cbu2/image/upload/a_320/a_hflip/w_1000,f_auto,q_auto:low,fl_lossy,fl_progressive,fl_strip_profile/v1760720260/BOWIE_KNIFE-Crimson_Web_lkorj5.webp",
    "correct_answer": "BOWIE KNIFE Crimson Web",
    "wrong_answers": [
      "PARACORD KNIFE Crimson Web",
      "URSUS KNIFE Crimson Web",
      "HUNTSMAN KNIFE Crimson Web"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Qual é o nome desta faca?",
    "picture": "https://res.cloudinary.com/dwm53cbu2/image/upload/a_320/a_hflip/w_1000,f_auto,q_auto:low,fl_lossy,fl_progressive,fl_strip_profile/v1760720257/BUTTERFLY_KNIFE-Doppler_Phase_4_gody2e.webp",
    "correct_answer": "BUTTERFLY KNIFE Doppler Phase 4",
    "wrong_answers": [
      "TALON KNIFE Doppler Phase 4",
      "URSUS KNIFE Doppler Phase 4",
      "PARACORD KNIFE Doppler Phase 4"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Qual é o nome desta faca?",
    "picture": "https://res.cloudinary.com/dwm53cbu2/image/upload/a_320/a_hflip/w_1000,f_auto,q_auto:low,fl_lossy,fl_progressive,fl_strip_profile/v1760720256/BAYONET-Gamma_Doppler_Phase_1_hwkgel.webp",
    "correct_answer": "BAYONET Gamma Doppler Phase 1",
    "wrong_answers": [
      "KARAMBIT Gamma Doppler Phase 1",
      "BAYONET Gamma Doppler Phase 3",
      "BAYONET Gama Doppler Emerald"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Qual é o nome desta faca?",
    "picture": "https://res.cloudinary.com/dwm53cbu2/image/upload/a_320/a_hflip/w_1000,f_auto,q_auto:low,fl_lossy,fl_progressive,fl_strip_profile/v1760720254/BUTTERFLY_KNIFE-Doppler_Black_Pearl_kbwgwx.webp",
    "correct_answer": "BUTTERFLY KNIFE Doppler Black Pearl",
    "wrong_answers": [
      "NAJAVA KNIFE Doppler Black Pearl",
      "URSUS KNIFE Doppler Black Pearl",
      "TALON KNIFE Doppler Black Pearl"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Qual é o nome desta faca?",
    "picture": "https://res.cloudinary.com/dwm53cbu2/image/upload/a_320/a_hflip/w_1000,f_auto,q_auto:low,fl_lossy,fl_progressive,fl_strip_profile/v1760720252/FALCHION_KNIFE-Ultraviolet_xws2cd.webp",
    "correct_answer": "FALCHION KNIFE Ultraviolet",
    "wrong_answers": [
      "PARACORD KNIFE Ultraviolet",
      "NOMAD KNIFE Ultraviolet",
      "URSUS KNIFE Ultraviolet"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Qual é o nome desta faca?",
    "picture": "https://res.cloudinary.com/dwm53cbu2/image/upload/a_320/a_hflip/w_1000,f_auto,q_auto:low,fl_lossy,fl_progressive,fl_strip_profile/v1760720250/BUTTERFLY_KNIFE-Crimson_Web_qgils7.webp",
    "correct_answer": "BUTTERFLY KNIFE Crimson Web",
    "wrong_answers": [
      "PARACORD KNIFE Crimson Web",
      "URSUS KNIFE Crimson Web",
      "HUNTSMAN KNIFE Crimson Web"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Qual é o nome desta faca?",
    "picture": "https://res.cloudinary.com/dwm53cbu2/image/upload/a_320/a_hflip/w_1000,f_auto,q_auto:low,fl_lossy,fl_progressive,fl_strip_profile/v1760720249/BUTTERFLY_KNIFE-Bright_Water_iswdtc.webp",
    "correct_answer": "BUTTERFLY KNIFE Bright Water",
    "wrong_answers": [
      "HUNTSMAN KNIFE Bright Water",
      "GUT KNIFE Bright Water",
      "FLIP KNIFE Bright Water"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Qual é o nome desta faca?",
    "picture": "https://res.cloudinary.com/dwm53cbu2/image/upload/a_320/a_hflip/w_1000,f_auto,q_auto:low,fl_lossy,fl_progressive,fl_strip_profile/v1760720247/BOWIE_KNIFE-Blue_Steel_irycvi.webp",
    "correct_answer": "BOWIE KNIFE Blue Steel",
    "wrong_answers": [
      "NAJAVA KNIFE Blue Steel",
      "URSUS KNIFE Blue Steel",
      "TALON KNIFE Blue Steel"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Qual é o nome desta faca?",
    "picture": "https://res.cloudinary.com/dwm53cbu2/image/upload/a_320/a_hflip/w_1000,f_auto,q_auto:low,fl_lossy,fl_progressive,fl_strip_profile/v1760720246/FALCHION_KNIFE-Night_z1bm7o.webp",
    "correct_answer": "FALCHION KNIFE Night",
    "wrong_answers": [
      "HUNTSMAN KNIFE Night",
      "GUT KNIFE Night",
      "FLIP KNIFE Night"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Qual é o nome desta faca?",
    "picture": "https://res.cloudinary.com/dwm53cbu2/image/upload/a_320/a_hflip/w_1000,f_auto,q_auto:low,fl_lossy,fl_progressive,fl_strip_profile/v1760720244/BUTTERFLY_KNIFE-Blue_Steel_mflfba.webp",
    "correct_answer": "BUTTERFLY KNIFE Blue Steel",
    "wrong_answers": [
      "NAJAVA KNIFE Blue Steel",
      "URSUS KNIFE Blue Steel",
      "TALON KNIFE Blue Steel"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Qual é o nome desta faca?",
    "picture": "https://res.cloudinary.com/dwm53cbu2/image/upload/a_320/a_hflip/w_1000,f_auto,q_auto:low,fl_lossy,fl_progressive,fl_strip_profile/v1760720242/BAYONET-Doppler_rubi_vks08a.webp",
    "correct_answer": "BAYONET Doppler rubi",
    "wrong_answers": [
      "BAYONET Doppler Phase 2",
      "BAYONET Doppler Phase 4",
      "BAYONET Doppler Phase 1"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Qual é o nome desta faca?",
    "picture": "https://res.cloudinary.com/dwm53cbu2/image/upload/a_320/a_hflip/w_1000,f_auto,q_auto:low,fl_lossy,fl_progressive,fl_strip_profile/v1760720240/BOWIE_KNIFE-Scorched_bnwsjv.webp",
    "correct_answer": "BOWIE KNIFE Scorched",
    "wrong_answers": [
      "URSUS KNIFE Scorched",
      "PARACORD KNIFE Scorched",
      "NOMAD KNIFE Scorched"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Qual é o nome desta faca?",
    "picture": "https://res.cloudinary.com/dwm53cbu2/image/upload/a_320/a_hflip/w_1000,f_auto,q_auto:low,fl_lossy,fl_progressive,fl_strip_profile/v1760720239/BOWIE_KNIFE-Night_shkeoq.webp",
    "correct_answer": "BOWIE KNIFE Night",
    "wrong_answers": [
      "HUNTSMAN KNIFE Night",
      "GUT KNIFE Night",
      "FLIP KNIFE Night"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Qual é o nome desta faca?",
    "picture": "https://res.cloudinary.com/dwm53cbu2/image/upload/a_320/a_hflip/w_1000,f_auto,q_auto:low,fl_lossy,fl_progressive,fl_strip_profile/v1760720237/BAYONET-Stained_bopnjr.webp",
    "correct_answer": "BAYONET Stained",
    "wrong_answers": [
      "KARAMBIT Stained",
      "SKELETON Stained",
      "BAYONET Lore"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Qual é o nome desta faca?",
    "picture": "https://res.cloudinary.com/dwm53cbu2/image/upload/a_320/a_hflip/w_1000,f_auto,q_auto:low,fl_lossy,fl_progressive,fl_strip_profile/v1760720235/BAYONET-Doppler_Phase_2_kkmkv1.webp",
    "correct_answer": "BAYONET Doppler Phase 2",
    "wrong_answers": [
      "KARAMBIT Doppler Phase 2",
      "SKELETON Doppler Phase 2",
      "BAYONET Doppler rubi"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Qual é o nome desta faca?",
    "picture": "https://res.cloudinary.com/dwm53cbu2/image/upload/a_320/a_hflip/w_1000,f_auto,q_auto:low,fl_lossy,fl_progressive,fl_strip_profile/v1760720233/BAYONET-Slaughter_atezvc.webp",
    "correct_answer": "BAYONET Slaughter",
    "wrong_answers": [
      "KARAMBIT Slaughter",
      "SKELETON Slaughter",
      "BAYONET Lore"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Qual é o nome desta faca?",
    "picture": "https://res.cloudinary.com/dwm53cbu2/image/upload/a_320/a_hflip/w_1000,f_auto,q_auto:low,fl_lossy,fl_progressive,fl_strip_profile/v1760720232/BUTTERFLY_KNIFE-Night_rcodod.webp",
    "correct_answer": "BUTTERFLY KNIFE Night",
    "wrong_answers": [
      "HUNTSMAN KNIFE Night",
      "GUT KNIFE Night",
      "FLIP KNIFE Night"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Qual é o nome desta faca?",
    "picture": "https://res.cloudinary.com/dwm53cbu2/image/upload/a_320/a_hflip/w_1000,f_auto,q_auto:low,fl_lossy,fl_progressive,fl_strip_profile/v1760720230/BOWIE_KNIFE-Forest_DDPAT_b45kay.webp",
    "correct_answer": "BOWIE KNIFE Forest DDPAT",
    "wrong_answers": [
      "PARACORD KNIFE Forest DDPAT",
      "URSUS KNIFE Forest DDPAT",
      "TALON KNIFE Forest DDPAT"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Qual é o nome desta faca?",
    "picture": "https://res.cloudinary.com/dwm53cbu2/image/upload/a_320/a_hflip/w_1000,f_auto,q_auto:low,fl_lossy,fl_progressive,fl_strip_profile/v1760720228/BOWIE_KNIFE-Bright_Water_gdiu8h.webp",
    "correct_answer": "BOWIE KNIFE Bright Water",
    "wrong_answers": [
      "HUNTSMAN KNIFE Bright Water",
      "GUT KNIFE Bright Water",
      "FLIP KNIFE Bright Water"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Qual é o nome desta faca?",
    "picture": "https://res.cloudinary.com/dwm53cbu2/image/upload/a_320/a_hflip/w_1000,f_auto,q_auto:low,fl_lossy,fl_progressive,fl_strip_profile/v1760720227/BOWIE_KNIFE-Boreal_Forest_hgphzw.webp",
    "correct_answer": "BOWIE KNIFE Boreal Forest",
    "wrong_answers": [
      "PARACORD KNIFE Boreal Forest",
      "URSUS KNIFE Boreal Forest",
      "NOMAD KNIFE Boreal Forest"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Qual é o nome desta faca?",
    "picture": "https://res.cloudinary.com/dwm53cbu2/image/upload/a_320/a_hflip/w_1000,f_auto,q_auto:low,fl_lossy,fl_progressive,fl_strip_profile/v1760720225/BAYONET-Damascus_Steel_x7sgco.webp",
    "correct_answer": "BAYONET Damascus Steel",
    "wrong_answers": [
      "KARAMBIT Damascus Steel",
      "SKELETON Damascus Steel",
      "BAYONET Lore"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Qual é o nome desta faca?",
    "picture": "https://res.cloudinary.com/dwm53cbu2/image/upload/a_320/a_hflip/w_1000,f_auto,q_auto:low,fl_lossy,fl_progressive,fl_strip_profile/v1760720224/BAYONET-Fade_ltew9c.webp",
    "correct_answer": "BAYONET Fade",
    "wrong_answers": [
      "KARAMBIT Fade",
      "SKELETON Fade",
      "BAYONET Lore"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Qual é o nome desta faca?",
    "picture": "https://res.cloudinary.com/dwm53cbu2/image/upload/a_320/a_hflip/w_1000,f_auto,q_auto:low,fl_lossy,fl_progressive,fl_strip_profile/v1760720222/BOWIE_KNIFE-Ultraviolet_wf4ix4.webp",
    "correct_answer": "BOWIE KNIFE Ultraviolet",
    "wrong_answers": [
      "PARACORD KNIFE Ultraviolet",
      "NOMAD KNIFE Ultraviolet",
      "URSUS KNIFE Ultraviolet"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Qual é o nome desta faca?",
    "picture": "https://res.cloudinary.com/dwm53cbu2/image/upload/a_320/a_hflip/w_1000,f_auto,q_auto:low,fl_lossy,fl_progressive,fl_strip_profile/v1760720220/BAYONET-Urban_Masked_toy9jz.webp",
    "correct_answer": "BAYONET Urban Masked",
    "wrong_answers": [
      "KARAMBIT Urban Masked",
      "SKELETON Urban Masked",
      "BAYONET Lore"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Qual é o nome desta faca?",
    "picture": "https://res.cloudinary.com/dwm53cbu2/image/upload/a_320/a_hflip/w_1000,f_auto,q_auto:low,fl_lossy,fl_progressive,fl_strip_profile/v1760720219/BAYONET-Doppler_Phase_4_mxuckf.webp",
    "correct_answer": "BAYONET Doppler Phase 4",
    "wrong_answers": [
      "KARAMBIT Doppler Phase 4",
      "SKELETON Doppler Phase 4",
      "BAYONET Doppler rubi"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Qual é o nome desta faca?",
    "picture": "https://res.cloudinary.com/dwm53cbu2/image/upload/a_320/a_hflip/w_1000,f_auto,q_auto:low,fl_lossy,fl_progressive,fl_strip_profile/v1760720217/BAYONET-Safari_Mesh_cvapuv.webp",
    "correct_answer": "BAYONET Safari Mesh",
    "wrong_answers": [
      "KARAMBIT Safari Mesh",
      "SKELETON Safari Mesh",
      "BAYONET Lore"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Qual é o nome desta faca?",
    "picture": "https://res.cloudinary.com/dwm53cbu2/image/upload/a_320/a_hflip/w_1000,f_auto,q_auto:low,fl_lossy,fl_progressive,fl_strip_profile/v1760720216/BAYONET-Doppler_Phase_1_o9trm1.webp",
    "correct_answer": "BAYONET Doppler Phase 1",
    "wrong_answers": [
      "KARAMBIT Doppler Phase 1",
      "SKELETON Doppler Phase 1",
      "BAYONET Doppler rubi"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Qual é o nome desta faca?",
    "picture": "https://res.cloudinary.com/dwm53cbu2/image/upload/a_320/a_hflip/w_1000,f_auto,q_auto:low,fl_lossy,fl_progressive,fl_strip_profile/v1760720214/BAYONET-doppler_Black_pearl_idhbmy.webp",
    "correct_answer": "BAYONET doppler Black pearl",
    "wrong_answers": [
      "BAYONET Doppler rubi",
      "BAYONET Doppler Phase 2",
      "BAYONET Doppler Phase 4"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Qual é o nome desta faca?",
    "picture": "https://res.cloudinary.com/dwm53cbu2/image/upload/a_320/a_hflip/w_1000,f_auto,q_auto:low,fl_lossy,fl_progressive,fl_strip_profile/v1760720213/BAYONET-Case_Hardened_wb1ks1.webp",
    "correct_answer": "BAYONET Case Hardened",
    "wrong_answers": [
      "KARAMBIT Case Hardened",
      "SKELETON Case Hardened",
      "BAYONET Lore"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Qual é o nome desta faca?",
    "picture": "https://res.cloudinary.com/dwm53cbu2/image/upload/a_320/a_hflip/w_1000,f_auto,q_auto:low,fl_lossy,fl_progressive,fl_strip_profile/v1760720211/BAYONET-Doppler_Sapphire_gnpfzy.webp",
    "correct_answer": "BAYONET Doppler Sapphire",
    "wrong_answers": [
      "KARAMBIT Doppler Sapphire",
      "SKELETON Doppler Sapphire",
      "BAYONET Doppler rubi"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Qual é o nome desta faca?",
    "picture": "https://res.cloudinary.com/dwm53cbu2/image/upload/a_320/a_hflip/w_1000,f_auto,q_auto:low,fl_lossy,fl_progressive,fl_strip_profile/v1760720210/BAYONET-Dopple_Phase_4_hdnd2c.webp",
    "correct_answer": "BAYONET Dopple Phase 4",
    "wrong_answers": [
      "BAYONET Doppler rubi",
      "BAYONET Doppler Phase 2",
      "BAYONET Doppler Phase 4"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Qual é o nome desta faca?",
    "picture": "https://res.cloudinary.com/dwm53cbu2/image/upload/a_320/a_hflip/w_1000,f_auto,q_auto:low,fl_lossy,fl_progressive,fl_strip_profile/v1760720209/BAYONET-Dopple_Phase_3_gk3zbo.webp",
    "correct_answer": "BAYONET Dopple Phase 3",
    "wrong_answers": [
      "BAYONET Doppler rubi",
      "BAYONET Doppler Phase 2",
      "BAYONET Doppler Phase 4"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Qual é o nome desta faca?",
    "picture": "https://res.cloudinary.com/dwm53cbu2/image/upload/a_320/a_hflip/w_1000,f_auto,q_auto:low,fl_lossy,fl_progressive,fl_strip_profile/v1760720207/BAYONET-Forest_DDPAT_nsrtzq.webp",
    "correct_answer": "BAYONET Forest DDPAT",
    "wrong_answers": [
      "KARAMBIT Forest DDPAT",
      "SKELETON Forest DDPAT",
      "BAYONET Lore"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Qual é o nome desta faca?",
    "picture": "https://res.cloudinary.com/dwm53cbu2/image/upload/a_320/a_hflip/w_1000,f_auto,q_auto:low,fl_lossy,fl_progressive,fl_strip_profile/v1760720206/BAYONET-Black_Laminate_ul3ag7.webp",
    "correct_answer": "BAYONET Black Laminate",
    "wrong_answers": [
      "KARAMBIT Black Laminate",
      "BAYONET Lore",
      "BAYONET Rust Coat"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Qual é o nome desta faca?",
    "picture": "https://res.cloudinary.com/dwm53cbu2/image/upload/a_320/a_hflip/w_1000,f_auto,q_auto:low,fl_lossy,fl_progressive,fl_strip_profile/v1760720204/BAYONET-Ultraviolet_qszlus.webp",
    "correct_answer": "BAYONET Ultraviolet",
    "wrong_answers": [
      "KARAMBIT Ultraviolet",
      "SKELETON Ultraviolet",
      "BAYONET Lore"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Qual é o nome desta faca?",
    "picture": "https://res.cloudinary.com/dwm53cbu2/image/upload/a_320/a_hflip/w_1000,f_auto,q_auto:low,fl_lossy,fl_progressive,fl_strip_profile/v1760720203/BAYONET-Scorched_ifitex.webp",
    "correct_answer": "BAYONET Scorched",
    "wrong_answers": [
      "KARAMBIT Scorched",
      "SKELETON Scorched",
      "BAYONET Lore"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Qual é o nome desta faca?",
    "picture": "https://res.cloudinary.com/dwm53cbu2/image/upload/a_320/a_hflip/w_1000,f_auto,q_auto:low,fl_lossy,fl_progressive,fl_strip_profile/v1760720202/BAYONET-Autotronic_dewgpg.webp",
    "correct_answer": "BAYONET Autotronic",
    "wrong_answers": [
      "KARAMBIT Autotronic",
      "BAYONET Lore",
      "BAYONET Rust Coat"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Qual é o nome desta faca?",
    "picture": "https://res.cloudinary.com/dwm53cbu2/image/upload/a_320/a_hflip/w_1000,f_auto,q_auto:low,fl_lossy,fl_progressive,fl_strip_profile/v1760720200/BAYONET-Night_ajjk8c.webp",
    "correct_answer": "BAYONET Night",
    "wrong_answers": [
      "KARAMBIT Night",
      "BAYONET Lore",
      "BAYONET Rust Coat"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Qual é o nome desta faca?",
    "picture": "https://res.cloudinary.com/dwm53cbu2/image/upload/a_320/a_hflip/w_1000,f_auto,q_auto:low,fl_lossy,fl_progressive,fl_strip_profile/v1760720199/BAYONET-Blue_Steel_n66hm3.webp",
    "correct_answer": "BAYONET Blue Steel",
    "wrong_answers": [
      "KARAMBIT Blue Steel",
      "SKELETON Blue Steel",
      "BAYONET Lore"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Qual é o nome desta faca?",
    "picture": "https://res.cloudinary.com/dwm53cbu2/image/upload/a_320/a_hflip/w_1000,f_auto,q_auto:low,fl_lossy,fl_progressive,fl_strip_profile/v1760720198/BAYONET-Crimson_Web_weramq.webp",
    "correct_answer": "BAYONET Crimson Web",
    "wrong_answers": [
      "KARAMBIT Crimson Web",
      "SKELETON Crimson Web",
      "BAYONET Lore"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Qual é o nome desta faca?",
    "picture": "https://res.cloudinary.com/dwm53cbu2/image/upload/a_320/a_hflip/w_1000,f_auto,q_auto:low,fl_lossy,fl_progressive,fl_strip_profile/v1760720197/BAYONET-Bright_Water_dqxf8f.webp",
    "correct_answer": "BAYONET Bright Water",
    "wrong_answers": [
      "KARAMBIT Bright Water",
      "BAYONET Lore",
      "BAYONET Rust Coat"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Qual é o nome desta faca?",
    "picture": "https://res.cloudinary.com/dwm53cbu2/image/upload/a_320/a_hflip/w_1000,f_auto,q_auto:low,fl_lossy,fl_progressive,fl_strip_profile/v1760720196/BAYONET-Boreal_Forest_egjg7z.webp",
    "correct_answer": "BAYONET Boreal Forest",
    "wrong_answers": [
      "KARAMBIT Boreal Forest",
      "SKELETON Boreal Forest",
      "BAYONET Lore"
    ]
  }
]